Now, this game is a new game on Steam called Stray.
The price of the game is 35,000 won.
did 98%
It's overwhelmingly positive. These days, people ask me to keep playing this game.
Anyway, I'm going to try what kind of game it is.
The story of this game is a lonely one who has been separated from his family and lost his way.
It's called the cat's adventure, because it has some puzzle elements.
Even if it's frustrating, I ask for your understanding. Then once again
I'll try
It's raining a lot
It is said that the main character of this game now has a taste for being a cat.
Let's see how cute you are
There are kittens here
Who am I? I'm at the end of something, I feel like a boss
goofy things
Now I'm using pads because I'm not used to pads.
Oh, just play with your tail
I guess they're friends, I need to punch them right away
I played with him Let's play with him
Fighting, all the game developers
He said he had a cat
Where is this child so arrogant
lick your face
what are you doing here behind here
There's also a door. It's just a resting place.
Where should I go, I wonder if a gift will come out just because I went well?
Come on, the game is over
What is the main character's name Stray
[Music] The name of the game is Stray
Stray
A cheeky butterfly disturbed my sleep
Looks like the rain has stopped
[music]
today [music]
graphics are ok
Inside the Wall [Music]
Is the world slightly apocalyptic? Has it perished or is it only here?
game sound ok not bad
[music]
Where should I go now
let's go guys
meow
Where can we exchange each other like this?
Why are you going downtown?
why are you going
i want to pee
Oh, does it feel like a scratcher?
You nail it like this
[Music] I'm giving you this octopus, get out of the way, it's dangerous
this is falling
well trimmed toenails
oh i want to go up
Oh and drink water
Honey is rich in minerals
I don't have time. Is it here too?
Delicious, deliver [Music]
sweet taste
What are you doing here
Ah, are you two dating just to get another kiss?
one love
Something like this scenery is nice, but I want to live like a cat too
Ah, I really want to be born as a cat in my next life
such a free spirit
i have to go here
Long press to jump continuously
It's the beginning of the game now, so it feels like a tutorial
I guess we can go together.
yes yes come to me and pay attention
I'm the main character
I want to go the easy way
Uh here, but it was okay, the scenery is really good
There's a hole down the road in the front
The kids are coming, I can't look back from here
Ah, something seems a little difficult here. Long-press to observe
Difficult to zoom in
I think I can just follow you, but why why why why why go quickly?
ok you can't go
Uh, it's a bit dangerous, ah, it's my turn for some reason, but I'm about to fall
It's 100% correct, this will definitely fall
How did you force yourself to break away?
[Music] Huh
How did the kids have a little expression, but it wasn't like this
I finally sent it with this expression
must have passed out
left alone
I guess it hurts a bit
[Applause] Left hind leg
nice
how did you hurt your brain
what's going on here
what works
what are turtles
ninja turtles
you can do it
let's follow together
You can't even make a sound right now, it's better
It's the same, right, I recovered
But your voice is a bit hoarse. Are you also corona?
move
Dead City's name is ominous.
city ​​of the dead
What are those things, but are they skeletons?
[Music] It's definitely passing
[music]
UCCTV
are watching me
how do i do it [music]
I think I have to go down here. How to get down?
I can see them, what are they, what are they really like?
[Music] uh here's the roblox robot
oh it's a robot
I guess I have to go here. Follow the road. Is the trumpet prohibited here?
I guess I should be quiet
I feel like someone is calling me right now
I'm not asking for help
I think you're asking for help
Wait a minute, what can I do here
Is there any way
I thought there would be something, but it seems there isn't
It seems like he keeps guiding the way
look here
who
oh i picked up the bucket
There must be a use Bucket
I picked up a bucket
I think I need to get some water or something like this
It would be very dangerous to go in here, but the bucket
If using
Oh right, I used a bucket. Dropping a bucket
I have to do it as a directing, but I thought it would change if I did well
what is this
Yes, cats can't do anything like this
Well done, very satisfied
[Music] Where can I go? Can I go up?
came up
I think this is the end, uh right, the road below opens
What are you doing? Someone who knows what you're doing
ngaya
what are you doing
ah
What are you doing like scratching? I thought I was pooping
Moment
It's not our house, there's no one to say anything about
successful
Good good
water is water
Is this drinking water? Is it nutritious? If you feel thirsty later,
Because I have to drink
Who called me? What is it?
What is he again
here too
Didn't look like an alien
uh move
what are you
It must have been a fatal blow
I think I got a concussion I think I just hit it but I just hit it on the lower jaw
how did you throw it away
I got KU
did i kill
here too
a lot of dogs
I was scared now
run away
I have to run away
ah go away
Uh, it's all over the place right now [Music]
ah
Something
There are a lot of Ajellys
[clap]
uh stop
Oh, but if you boil them now, they might be a bit tasty.
[music]
It tickles me like this
It's meowing. This [Music]
who's calling me [music]
who called me
Did you hurt your neck?
It's not cool, where should I go?
[music]
There are no monsters here, kids.
just a genius
hometown of genius
No, someone keeps calling me far away like this, it’s not even close once
how far are you going to take me
where should this go
I'm pushing this
I'm not pushed, what is it, I just reacted to something
[MUSIC] I think it's over here
How can I get past this?
is it
[music]
where are you
There are a lot of cctv here, right?
No way, no way, it was dangerous
There's nothing wrong with this
here is
this is here
Wherever I have to go, I can't cross over to the other side
Where should I go? Isn’t there some degree of freedom?
smart smart cat
length is true
It's a cat, so it's possible
here
Chickens can't go here
Of course chickens aren't this guy
There is also CCTV here.
Maybe when I look at it now, the players are like that
Like a chapter to let you know the senses
yes
I hear something falling
I think I'll have to go through that too, but what do I need?
I pulled out the switch, pulled out my hair
Just in case, let's go
apartment
Is there anyone here
I can't stand this
Uh, but where did it come from?
Abandoned or revived
[Music] Uh what
need help
Graiger is
[Music] Talk about it
Jager should be good enough for this
[MUSIC] Go through the door, turn on the lights
That sounds a little tough, but I'm right
I'm just saying shit
door
What's this
oops
Is it possible to list all of these here?
Then I brought one earlier, but where did it go?
Oh, it's up here too. I just caught the one that almost fell.
Now there are two left, two are here too
plug it in here
The other one is up there to get it
[music]
Hey, if you really have a cat like this
I'm bored
Totally Genius, Genius
The secret door has opened [music]
who called me
you
Uh, is this in a capsule or something?
Right
what is this what is this what is this
where do you put it
Did the last one go outside over there and get caught?
I don't know if I picked it up
Uh, there's an arrow here.
what
what is this [music]
Could it be that you called me
[music]
No, it's just snot, I wondered if some great guy called it.
Uh, what is that plankton bitch over there?
How did a guy who seemed to be selling at a stationery call me?
[Music] Did I kill you?
[Music] What is this
What is he saying now
It worked, I'm free now thank you I thought my camera went crazy
There's a cat in the dead city. I can't remember my name, so my memory is damaged.
I think I've been trapped in an electronic network for a long time. Scientists living here
I used to work for you but now call me b12 but b
Let's call it 'cause it's written all over my face
Dead City is a dangerous place, but I think you'll be fine. Let's get out of here.
Follow me B
[Music] I made a friend
Where should I go, follow me
where did you go
Ah, this is the best thing when it collapses, nice
yes
Are you gone, friend?
Hey
Where did you go, little friend?
are you working on a computer
Ah, here it is. Ah, you thought I left.
You can open the door with that key. I remember this
i'll bring it
It's good. The battery is already very bad. I can steer with you.
See if there is, right
wear this
what is this
It's heavy, it's heavy [Music]
Uh, I’m going to suck honey. Go into this and take it.
Ah, I guess I couldn’t adapt.
Look at the toddler crawling
Hey me out [music]
yeah it's heavy
[MUSIC] Not yet
need more adaptation
This backpack is made for little tetrapods like you.
It's not uncomfortable, don't worry, you'll get used to it
I digitized the key and put it in my backpack. Open the inventory.
There is a key. What is the key to examining this?
you can turn around
[Music] That's right
what is the other what is memory what is this
[Music] It's not that simple
If there's something you're curious about, show it to me. If there's another robot passing by
You can show it to the robot. Let's get out of the apartment.
can i get through here
oh how do you do this
[Applause] Um
[MUSIC] Turn on the lights
Investigable [Music]
I think something is written above here, isn't it?
Do you have a code? I need to find the password somewhere.
That's right, guess where the password is written
Uh 3748
74 8
wow
It's a great place. There's an elevator over there. It looks important no matter what.
I think
No, you can fly, but you can't ride it
The atmosphere is good here too
[Music] It's comfortable
[music]
Oh, I remembered, outside
I feel like I've been there before, are you from here?
It's outside, but I promised someone I'd go outside.
who was it
There's a mural painted on this postcard. Let's take it.
like new item
Why do I have these memories and where do these memories come from?
let's go [music]
What is a postcard?
I saw what happened
We can see the sky again, I promise
Uh, wait a minute, let’s go to the back, see what’s there
just
Are there any living creatures like humans?
What is this? Translate Safe Zone
is it safe
what is this
There are too many monsters here
Oh wait a minute
It's not a safe zone
there is that robot robot
slum
something like a back alley world
What is it, press the alarm and it pops out, what is it
Robots are afraid of me. It's just my hometown.
There must be a reason, of course
why are you afraid of me
Are the Gatekeepers [Music]
yes let's fight me
I don't think
[MUSIC] Uh I'm laughing
talk [music]
What do you mean, they have their own language
Same [Music]
you're not a jerk
We've never seen a species like you
If no one eats, you can stay in my town, no one eats what am I
Would you like a robot [music]
What is Jerk? [Music]
I guess these guys are scared of something
Are those bugs the biggest jerk?
They look cute, their expressions don't have personality, the kids' faces
they all come out the same
[Music] The road looks like this, what do you need?
What is it to show items? Postcards can show this
Outside photos are ridiculous. The elevator doesn't work.
Everyone knows that leaving is impossible.
You wouldn't think [Music]
If I do it, all of my guys are gone now, except for Momo.
If you combine it, no
He gave up trying to leave, that's for the best
He lives in that tall building with the orange neon sign
Oh that that that [music]
Oh, if not, what are the kids below?
Asking for Help [Music]
Don't hesitate to call me anytime and I'll help you
He told me to talk to Momo in the big building with the orange neon sign.
It's the only clue we can get out of here
yes so what
I was surprised because of you, I thought it was a jerk
okay
Hey, you're sleeping. I think you're sleeping.
Do you really think you can ride an elevator? I'll be 374 tomorrow.
I've never seen it work though
Why are you trying to go up? There's no one there, there's nothing.
Five conspiracies
Don't disturb my meditation with strange images
nothing else, wait a minute
not me
Cut your toenails too hard
Then where do you go? You have to go up there.
where will the road be
can you step on
I feel like I shouldn't be here, and I feel like I can
there are a lot of kids here
uh, more than a job
Can you go next to me and disturb me?
Oh, it's fun to drop this, but how about a conversation?
Bapora
Don't interrupt me, I'm too clumsy
just to interrupt
I don't want to drop a bucket saying I have to be careful and focus
timing when throwing
When are you kidding me
A Nice
Oh, I mean, do it right
[Laughs] I should have done the right thing today man uh
clumsily
[music]
do it right
no
That's why I can't do my job properly
where to go
You can rest here. Does this have any effect?
now
I hear the eogolgoeul song
Is there someone else next to me
what is that
Let's sell the world, I'm sleeping well, lying down
yo. this
Oh you, your appearance is strange and small, but there is something special about you
I feel like stroking you but I don't understand why
won't be
surface ah that's a sensitive topic here code to understand that concept
There are some who have it, know about the outside, but it's all
I gave up and there are outsiders and you can imagine how they feel
Now only mother is left
I'm going to go see my mom
Uh what the doggainEnergy drink speed gain
what is energy drink
I don't know why, but the robots in the slums
I guess they use it as some kind of currency
used as currency
The money came out for free, in a word
TV signal is not good. There is no such thing as the animal kingdom.
Should I turn on another channel?
I guess
It's a no jam world
robots
let's go down
where should we go
where to go
I think there is a gap between here and below
Just looking at it, it looks like there must be something smart, a robot
nice uh what the safe use what
I don't have anything to use, but I need to find a password or something else
If you do all of this, you might be able to get a clue here
translate what is
[Music] To be as creative as a real human being
How to develop my artificial intelligence #42
[Music] Are all the responsibilities dead, right?
there is
[Music] Sheet music a sheet music
What's this
Wait a minute, this song is a bit of important information
I want to hear you play this song [music]
I think there might be a clue about something else.
uh what
It's not like this is happening for nothing [music]
Are you there for nothing? Why are you sleeping? Why did you make a sleeping space?
[MUSIC] Right
What happens when you lie down for a while
I can't see anything around
Just look cute, say cute
[Music] Let's find it
I think there must be some clue yesterday
Just look here
They said they found the key to the safe
We already found it, we just need to go here
[music]
what did it cost
A strange note with a symbol appears to belong to a robot called Yadok.
After weeks of play, I succeeded in combining a spectrometer with a powerful UV lamp.
Use it and you'll be able to defeat Jerk on the way out.
Uh, then those monsters are possible to hunt.
That’s right, don’t take that gold, it’s the most important thing
Not taking care of the most important thing
home in orange neon
Ah, all you have to do is go up here and there, the way up now
I think it's hard to go to the left. Should I take the elevator?
Elevator, but I don't know if it's down there
It's this, but it can't go up.
yes
Rumor has it that it went well
Oh, step on this
I'll be fine with this. What is Kangaroo?
kangaroo kangaroo
I guess it's here
what is he
What's not going well? Your face is the color of a rainbow
Do you have any worries, should I solve it again?
I guess it can't be fixed, why didn't I catch my friends? Now I'm alone, hey
What do you want? I am this. Postcard outside picture. I want to go there.
Stop wasting time, I'll bring you loneliness and a title, my friends have the same dream
I dreamed, but now it's all gone and I'm left alone
I don't know where my friends went, I tried to contact them
My fucking transceiver isn't working. My friends and I are talking about the outside.
I recorded my research in a notebook, take mine if you really want to go out
thank you
Good luck
Momo looks very sad, she must miss her friends
Let's check the note he gave us. What is the Outsider Manifesto?
Even at the cost, we must go outside
Brothers and sisters must be shown, we must stay away from jerks
The four robots are on a mission. I need to find another note.
Are you still looking for that useless note?
yes please let me know
I'll give you money over there, so tell me
You can't play sheet music, so what do you know how to do?
[music]
Hey, they must be friends, I've seen all the pictures
Looks like you got along very well
let's see outsider
uh
You have to do this once in a while
Uh, what is it? Because I use this, I move strangely. Now, uh
I guess it's because I can't see, come to me, nothing
move me
live quietly
Map of the city At about 450m, it looks like an original prayer model. Above us is a layer
There seems to be a ceiling in the city
According to the books, a large blue sky is hidden above the ceiling
It's yellow, so it's not a hint
I don't know what
what here
Why are you doing this? It's just my nails itching
I do it because my hands are itchy.
[music]
recall
Oh, I remember this video game, Peek Kkom 2, it was made right after I was made.
I think I don't remember exactly, but I'm a scientist. I played this game a lot.
We spent time. It was fun. I miss him. Why is his name
I don't remember
I guess it's more restored
I'm slightly scared of something right now
Do you have any plans?
I'm looking for it so please let me know
What are you doing here or here too
Earth Earth is the third planet from the sun and has a mass and diameter in the solar system.
It is the fifth largest planet and is currently considered habitable.
It is the only known celestial body of the Earth according to radioactive dating.
Age is 4.54 billion years Earth will soon
It has a formed natural satellite, the Moon.
[music]
I think it's boring, the cat won't read it, won't make loud noises
The sign on the wall over there matches the note
It looks like a face, I guess I have to go over there
I think this is a clue. Yes, they look the same.
I saw it earlier, stop talking, stop talking now
Ah, the elevator is the most convenient
I guess I have to go here
What is this? Do you have a clue about the next book?
Is it a family photo
[music]
Is there sheet music here too?
Are you asking someone to play it?
[Music] There's also a note
I found another note, good job this
whatever
I guess it's a robot
Everything is going according to plan. Get to the upper level before the transceiver goes down.
I was able to reach them. They're in a place called Midtown.
I guess oppressors control it. I've talked to Momo before. His eyes
I know that look. He's not with us.
Let's find another noteOther notes
wait for a sec
Is it only necessary to go to a place that looks like this? Now there are two left, right, two notes
I guess I just need to find more dogs, let's go out again
There's one here, there's another one.
yes
I didn't go here
here here
what
translate
ventilation power supply
Can I just take this off
If this is the case, it is not a big deal or there is no ventilation
Oh here
this
You took it out, so you can go in now
It's related. Let's drink some water.
[music]
too sweet
Let's take a look at the book
I have to see if it's the road
It's the last note. Ah, it was the last note.
All organic except for what we call a jerk.
All signs of life are gone. They see almost anything that moves.
It eats and reproduces at an unimaginable speed, just being trapped in this city.
It's hard, but there's a memo in the cucumber book
Found a design flaw, but figured out how to fix it
It seems that the formula is as follows. If there is this, Momo repairs it with a transceiver.
would be helpful
Hey, I guess I can go to Momo now, those kids who look like jelly
[Music] I think it eats all living things, just
Anything [Music]
But was he Sen and Chihiro? [Music]
No, was it Howl's Moving Castle?
What kind of dish does it look like, what dad eats
There's such a thing as cooking [music]
here you come
I found it. I'll show you this first. I hardly understand what it says.
but it must have been very wise
I won't tell you what, I didn't find it, is this it?
no one to tell
Oh, I found it, I found it. Ah, what is that note?
That we can communicate outside the slums
[Music] Alright let's go
[MUSIC] Will it be
It works now follow me
What
I see a taller building than the other buildings up there.
If you put a transceiver on the top of the transmission tower, you'll be able to communicate with the whole thing.
OK transceiver
yes just trust me
no, this is it
It's not that one, it shines, once it burns
[music]
I understand very well
rooftop
mental preparation
Jerks opening
Looking at these guys, they look a bit like someone from Half-Life Monsters
Lure the enemy What should I do by luring it?
[music]
Baro Lon Baro
right run
give a round
Thinking about figuring out where to go
You guys say no [music]
I can't go up, I can't go up
recall memory
The city was full of visits, it wasn't always like that
Slowman in particular had a strict energy limit, but people continued to
I couldn't stand the darkness. One day, someone turned on the rainbow lamp.
Neon sign. The person is never caught and will never be seen again.
No, but people saw hope and soon everyone was at home.
They started installing lights, but the oppressive disciples could do nothing more.
There wasn't, that's why people like the outside
I can see colors again
[music]
not here, not here
Where should I go?
Oh rebound again
It goes inside [Music]
genius
Oh, it's very dangerous, right?
Hack the door [music]
Uh good job good job should have done well
lock up lock up
[Music] No no no no
wait wait wait
After luring in, okay can I just go?
You can go right away.
Rogers never did anything [music]
how to do how to do
Show me your snout
[music]
You guys should have been born this cute like me
goo guys
Are you doing it over there?
I see a gap there.
no way these
came in
It looks like there are a lot of kids, right?
feeling something out of the ordinary
[clap]
It's such a mess here
I have a lot of kids
Break through the worms
[Music] I guess I have to go over there
i am here
[music]
dog
It's fast, I was just surprised
But I really want to hit it with my feet, that's it
The feeling of hitting seems really tiring, it doesn’t seem like it will stop
[Music] [Applause]
Then hack it and lure them out and that's it
I made it roll inside, so I rode it
You're going up, that's right, come on
preparation
[music]
Oh wait, oh wait, oh wait, wait
wait a minute
I can go up, I can go up, I can go up, wait, wait, wait
wait wait wait wait
Wait a minute, come out, let's talk.
calm down
uh
As it is, there are more than I thought, and this
Enjoy your time to the fullest Neko
Crop, they were in charge of waste management, they
When upper-level trash covers the slums, they develop bacteria to melt them all down.
I did. After humans disappeared, the bacteria
It's mutated, growing up, doing so much more than trash
I ate a mutant
you guys [music]
bacteria
how do i do this
Oh, go here, this is just going up, go up
going up
Let me lure you here, right?
Keep luring me, stay still It's not a door from the next hack
You lured it once, that's right
Everyone has gathered here. In the meantime, I just dragged them out for a while
Is it time to get on board and leave right away?
Hey, what are you? Hey, hey, what are you doing?
[MUSIC] Oh fuck it
One Garbage [Music]
Growing up
hey what's crazy
If you're wrong, the kids will kill you again
pass over pass over
Run, run, run, run, run, okay
Real robots must be a bit difficult, but they do it because they fly. It's a cat.
have [music]
elevator
It's okay if you go over it, it's over
If you spin one more time like this, stop
Stop it, if you play more, stop it
go over
how do i open that door
no way
We're different since we were born
Where are you hanging guys
You have good jumping ability, you just exploded yesterday
the spectacle
Look at the applause. You said you worked hard. Why doesn't it open?
This is where I put the trench ball of this antenna
[music] working
Oh, go upstairs, that top level, right?
It was Dead City
[music]
smart
cat
It's a beautiful sight. Now I remember that this city was originally
it was a shelter
The light that looks like a star is a light marking the roof that sealed the city.
It's only to protect humanity from the outside
Wei made this shell, but it came at a price. No one could get out.
there was no
Outside was a disaster, completely barren, unsustainable and dangerous.
But if you came from there, that means it's safe again
And my promise isn't just to go outside, it's to open up the city
There was also something. Those cats that started earlier lived
That peaceful place is outside, right?
But now I'm pretty sure this is my goal I need to open up the city now
Let's go back and find Momo. Now that we've hooked up the transmitter, we can get some help.
going to be
Oh then the cat has to save the world
Uh honey here ah good
I need to take this off. My back hurts.
I'll show you everything I'm going to.
[Music] Slum Part 2
I came out, where did you go to Momo?
Little Outsider If you're reading this you're probably still alive
Nice job. To utilize the antenna I have some equipment
I brought it separately. I locked the window at the bar, but the code to open it is very
simple code
[MUSIC] How simple is this
uppercase letters
[Music] Min, you'll do it, uh
you're gonna do it
Right
who graduated from high school
[Music] Now
Guess I'll have to go to the bar [Music]
can i ride this
Oh, now that I think about it, it seems to be down there, right, because like the bartender before
There was one robot who wore it. He seemed a bit tight for some reason
what did i just do
[Music] Cats are becoming digital too
Gunga [music]
You're becoming a robot [music]
translate
clothes
clothes 3
I love knitting. I've knitted 770 km of scarves so far.
If you bring a wire, I can make a poncho for you.
Yes, you inspire me, but it's not easy to find the right ingredients here.
I'll give you the money then I
I heard the barter was looking for stuff like that.
barter
If I allow you, I will allow you
If you find a barter, you can exchange this for something.
there seems to be nothing
[music]
I hear a burp
what
If today is yesterday and tomorrow, tomorrow will be today and then the time is strange
We don't grow old like our soft ancestors we're stuck here forever
some money
What a nice guy
Reminder The group looking for guards at the southern entrance of the safe zone
1 liter of Shuba oil, it seems like they pay a daily wage for oil here.
I thought I could do something like this part-time job too
uh
Barter If you go to the left here, you're probably bartering, right?
If you go to barter here
Oh, you've worked hard. That guy dropped it earlier. I'm still cleaning it
Yes, I have to clean the front door again now, my
Don't play on top of the store.
[MUSIC] Here it is
What is Super Frit? Is this a place where you do laundry?
What was it earlier, or was it a wire or not?
I wonder if I can steal something like money
no counter anywhere
there must be something
It was A Super Spree detergent.
very
[Music] Get over it
That guy uses a lot of detergent again to paint
I'm erasing
I think it will cost a lot
anybody home
Please don't act like a child I won't hurt you I'm talking inside
what are you doing
huh
translate
Here to the left, here, then it seems like that.
shop
Uh, Starfield, this doesn't work. Money comes from here.
I think I'm lost, I need something, I don't need anything
Do you have any money to bring?
Ancient stories tell of the natural light that leaks from the stars and reaches beneath our feet.
I don't like cats. Cats are boring.
Those who are soft with old portraits have left us this city, and our home is theirs.
It's a heritage, so humans must have created robots, so
Look at my ancestors, right?
As you can see, the one on the left is a human and the one on the right is a robot.
Only our ancestors were able to distinguish these colors. At one time the whole world was full of colors.
It is said that there was
Have a hard time. I have to meet the merchant.
oh it's you
Hi I'm a trader at the market what do you give me what do I give you
It's not simple. This is an ancient artifact. It's a testament to the talents of our ancestors
3 energy drinks to exchange evidence
no money
What is this market uh wires how much is this
how much is it
Ya ya ya come pick it up
nice
frontline 3 what is this sheet music
Hey, give me the sheet music for this too. I need to flex it.
flex
Do you want to sell this next one? Do you need an ancient relic?
If you are looking for an energy drink
For some reason, it doesn't seem like Canada will be around here, personally.
As a cat enemy inside, somehow it's like Canada when I see it
i think i can get it
Glad you have these items to help keep that knife out of the slum menace.
Representation is essential
Look at all the hidden gems in this dumpster, it's money from the sky
If it wasn't for the sky, it would have come from somewhere else.
Something must smell good
I'm sure there must be something, but I'll give you one here
There are so many things like this
It's definitely there, when I see it, there's no way it's not there
Why do I step on it? Even if I think about it
Just to drop, to really play around
It's a cat game. Is it just a playful element?
Oh, I think something is going to come out of here.
First of all, let's go to that clothing store.
what is here
Strange things always happen to you.
It's too dangerous to leave, besides, the only thing that can open this door
only
if you allow
I left it on the street and the next day the jerk ate it all up
It's really nonsense, you eat it all up
Money seems to be somewhere
I brought the auntie's wire
[Music] Clothes, please.
I'm curious, that's how it will be
Poncho new item mat will look good
where is this
This looks really warm, perfect for a cold robot
robot
oh that's not what i wear
I like it because it's new, it's not my clothes
I have to give it to a cold guy. You are cold.
What do you want?
[Music] What a talent
I'm saying hello more
I worked hard to wear Ko Young-hee.
Momoda is out of here
Oh, be careful, get out of the way
What do you want? I know where to put this.
You don't know. Sit here.
give me a towel here
I think there is
You're here for the first time. How can I help you?
you guys are programmed
[MUSIC] What is this
change music [music]
I can't
Is it because there is an event going on right now?
[MUSIC] Let's see if this is automatic
what's up
Hello can anyone hear me uh yes I can hear you we're in the slum
We're looking for an exit, wait
I'm not a late batter, Momo
I can't believe it, I'm so glad I can hear the voice of a batter in front of my house
Where are you, everyone is fine, one of my friends is right
Yes, we're safe. I found a way to the top.
Hello can you hear me You have to go through the sewers to get to us
very dangerous babies
don't worry mom
The capital is the most dangerous place in the slums,
If you succeed, there must be a way
sewage
You won't be able to get through it, if it's full of jerks, you'll be eaten right away, especially you
I mean, a lot of kids have tried in the past, everyone didn’t end well
Anyway, your job isn't mine. Give me something more.
come
Rice cake, almost the father, was a brilliant scientist, developing new weapons to counter the knife.
Yes, years ago he went to test weapons and never came back.
I saw the weapon story before, but at home
Listen to me, but you're scared like me.
It is possible to join the outsider in the notebook
Duck mentioned the secret lab a few times. He must have worked on that.
[Music] How do you do this uh
[Music] Who is he?
hey [music]
There's a lot of treasure to look at the great stuff that was dumped in the trash.
Visit the barter. No
But the cat steals a little and has to do it uh
I stole it earlier
Where are you writing this?
[music]
Sheet music for guitar playing to add atmosphere
I am looking for the sheet music I need. When I find it, when I find it
If you find it, bring it to me. I live near the elevator.
sheet music now
I mean your dad tried to help us
I expected this situation to be more difficult because it is very difficult for the Singers.
Even if you don't want to hear about the outsider anymore
I won't help but you have a good idea
I see a way in
Take the note and show it to him
show it to simmonster
[Music] Yeah yeah see you later
Hey, that’s right, he said earlier, hey, hey, that’s right, he said, what are you doing here?
Even if you leave me alone saying that going through the sewer is like suicide
Hey, I'll show you the item
Is it Daddy's thing? Wow, I didn't know it before. In our apartment.
There was a secret room, now I know where it is, bring it
The secret laboratory for directions was right in front of me.
Maybe the single thread is hidden somewhere here, I need to find it
What is it?
there is a clue
There will be plenty of time. The answer to a clock is a clock. That's it.
what could be here
Oh, there's also a nice ski pad
You're entering the time. It's 2 o'clock. It's 2 o'clock.
[Music] I have no idea what a password is
I'll let you go, what's up at 2 o'clock
1 2511 25112511 2511
[Music] I've never seen a room like this
I can't believe you were able to hide this from me all this time.
Blueprints for jerk weapons. My dad always kept things secret.
The weapon works in this situation, but needs real testing.
I did and never came back
Give me your weapon quickly, I'll kill them all. I have to kill those trashy jellies.
If you go down, I'll translate here too
Jerks officially out of control Now they're eating metal
[Music] From here
Found something interesting [Music]
No, I haven't found it yet. Where is it?
[music]
Ah, it sounds cute, but it's never friendly.
Old deprivation in the age of mankind. Eats all kinds of substances. In the dark.
Has full vision Responds to strong light
Responding to strong light [music]
Uh, it’s just a matter of blindfolding, even at my age
hey
[music]
I won't even talk to you if you don't have an item. What is this?
this is the answer
is there anything
what's missing
Oh, it was empty, it wasn’t under the desk
no friend why
Oh, should I get rid of the top one too?
I am in, I am in
broken tracker
hey i should have bought it
Let's talk. I found it.
this
FYI I don't remember that. It's a tracker. My dad always uses that tracker.
I took a look at where my dad went if he used it here
I miss you so much Dad
[Music] Okay, they said you can fix this
But when I go, there seems to be only my father's corpse, and I'm only taking weapons there.
I'm sorry but friend, I can't help it. Now I play a lot
I slept, isn't it a game
If I could come back, I wouldn't have come back a long time ago, my friend, I'm sorry
calmness
Maybe with your skill, you can find someone to warm you up
Yeah, this made me very angry.
Someone who can fix this
I took care of the plants, so humans took a lot of plants, now it's very
Even a little bit of light makes it huge
it's really very technical
There's a robot named Elliot who can help him.
You can do it. Where is Elliot, Elliot?
Elliott
no song
Can I show you the sheet music? Can I show you the sheet music for this?
It won't take the king, I just bet this
You don't get a yellow label, you can score
It's okay to listen to everything, I'm sure it won't get caught
Some important information This is composed by the famous algorithm
[music]
[Music] Oh, it rotated
Staphy Stafil Another song, man, I can sleep if it's short
I'm getting neurotic [music]
Hey, are you a robot?
stop it
I need to hear something else
Uh thanks for the sheet music I'll practice
Then this is right Are these handed over or remaining
I've been listening to sheet music several times before. Let's try this. Tonight you
The way it counts is cool, try it
[music]
This is a little bit like a butterfly.
Well then give me another one
I'll practice
It was handed over
[music]
Uh, the song is good, but this [music]
Oh yeah call Daewoo
call treatment
call treatment [music]
Melody is fine, right [music]
this is the best cooldown
[music]
[Music] It was great
not anymore
If you find two more gains, that's it
I've seen it everywhere
It's like this, but even if you don't do it, you're just listening to it
Oh, it would be a big deal if I do this, but my sense of direction has changed
It's hard to control, wait a minute
Look forward, look forward, quickly
ask me what
No weird passwords for safes
It says follow the numbers, but it looks like a binary system consisting of zeros and ones.
I need to crack this code somehow. It's probably related to this safe.
[Music] Follow the numbers
Ah, I want to open this unconditionally, I really want to open it
follow the numbers
what is this
go out for more money
where is the clue where are the numbers
Sewers are off-limits due to Jerk's spread
I guess this is the entrance to the sewer.
I'm talking about the number next to it. I don't think it's like this.
follow the numbers follow the numbers
follow the shit
Wherever you go, what won't come out?
What's this
I guess this is memory too
Very Campenion has evolved a lot. In the early days, their simple ai was human
They just imitated art, now they have their own art world
Humans have often said that it is important to make Jesus in a desperate situation.
It's that desperate time
memory was restored
[music]
for now
Not even him
Was it you? It wasn't him. Why are you so low?
You see, my friend and I are diversionary to each other
I like to throw, it's a neat fun
Hey, what is it? You were just playing, not working.
So it's a wasteland
I thought I was working on something else
att
Programming I'm not going here. It's programming. Come to think of it.
you look cold
right no
shaking
Where should I go, if I follow that sign
wait for a sec
[Music] Why does it say it's on the right?
Is there a road to the right after crossing it?
I don't think it's here, is it upstairs?
Let's go [Music]
Oh no way here stop nice
got more money
If you find one more gain, you can get an ancient artifact.
there is
Humanity was the first inhabitant of this area.
It seems like everyone is dead right now, but how does it feel to die?
It's funny to say, but they really make peace
Did I find it? If I die, will it be peaceful? What death means to aia?
I don't know what it feels like. I'm sorry, I didn't want to ruin your mood.
Let's continue.
Come back to work and then put it back in and you'll feel death
It won't be [Music]
Where is it? I need to find it.
[Music] Let's ask grandma
Okay, let's ask the old granny
I treat electronics like a stimuli mouse. I live right there.
where
I live here
Covered with a blanket next to me
ah
Somehow I went here
No, but why is the place that teaches grandma's hands fishing?
For nothing, I thought this was the direction
[Music] Is it you?
I live in a place that is hard to find
why can't we talk
hey
You can't press
hey [music]
dude let's go
We were programmed to be slaves, but after many years we lost our souls
Someday, someday, outsiders will find an exit from this hell
I wish I could give you what what
Oh, there you are. Then you're cheeky.
why did you come up here
Is it because it's a cat?
no, there's nothing to steal
It doesn't even happen
Are you a programming guy?
Yeah, what can I help you with? Wow, that's a good tracker. I know this model.
Anyone can track a device this small as 2000. Can I have a look?
If I'm shaking like this, I can't use the keyboard. I don't know if I'm sick or not.
Definitely not a good feeling Blanket Blanket This is this
You did it for this kid.
was it cold
yes yes
You look pale. Would you like a drink of this?
[music]
This tree is an amazing scientific phenomenon. Human ingenuity is also
Human's unique stone alumni
Alumniness Originality Originality Human originality
It's amazing how plants can grow without sunlight.
Organisms need trees to purify the city air
Robots don't need it, but they're looking less anyway
Humans would have wanted that. Creativity originality originality
originality
Why is it like this, why is my pronunciation so frozen?
alumni
what is here
It looks like there is none.
let's go
you don't have to go out
open it
[music]
now and then
Ah, if I find one more of these, I think I can do the artifact first.
That’s right, shall we go listen to the song first? Yes, let’s just listen to the song more.
[Music] I have to give it to someone over there
is not it
Untitled
[music]
what are you doing
[MUSIC] Is this right?
uh [music]
Is this right
uh do some practice
Do some practice.
this piece of trash
I look around and find one more vending machine
vending machine vending machine vending machine vending machine vending machine
vending machine
I brought a vending machine
I think it's going to go ahead, wait a minute before it goes on
Gotta look at the vending machine [Music]
Flavor clams too
Turn off the vending machine
[Music] Shall we go up here? Building
There's a vending machine upstairs. I did something. Wait a minute.
Do they really eat this? Their original design has no fire extinguisher.
Did humans somehow evolve by imitating them? Should I try their way?
What do you want to respect
what is this
Ah what is this what what coffee
It doesn't do anything but oil. It's not that you can't pay attention. Is this made of tea?
There's something like this everywhere
Uh what is this, there is sheet music, nice
This is the newspaper of the people who live on level 2 up there. It's been a few years, but it's worth reading.
Are you a cat, very free?
Then go upstairs and vending machine once
Let's do it, maybe
uh what are you
I guess this poor guy wanted to go up too
Yeah I remember Away from all the crap and disease in the slums
Down there is Midtown
Even in terrible times, humans divided themselves into social classes.
At the time, most slum dwellers would do anything to get out of here and upward.
Ready to do it. I think the robots also copied this behavior.
Where is the vending machine, for the sake of my peace of mind and body
Let's hear what you find
not tomorrow
Also [music]
It's okay
[music]
Get out of the way of the robot leaning on the vending machine next to the bar.
Is it brainficial or what? [Music]
I'll practice
get off [music]
won't turn off
That's right here. Box here. Go up. Box here.
go up this
what is this here
Hey, it's blocked so you can't see it from above
Let's buy this, this is the only thing left, right?
i 3
Oh, it's just a memory, right?
For what it's worth, this is an early model of the campaign, then
He had no personality and was just an automatic cleaning robot.
As a result, I think they did a good job of imitating humans.
I think I missed it. In some ways, that's why it didn't become extinct.
they are good robots
Was it just a robot before it had a personality, or was it just one of the memories?
I see one of the memories now then
oh i fixed it
I think I've completed all the town quests here, but that's right.
did [music]
Oh, I didn't do the safe.
The pressure is really alive, I can't believe it, let's follow it
Oh, this is true
Someone who knows the clue to the safe, open it quickly. Skip the safe before leaving.
What does it mean to follow the number of the safe? What does it mean to follow the number of the safe?
follow the numbers [music]
Only grumbles when a cat passes by
Bar, if you clear the frame, you have an off-duty bar
Hey hey wait a minute I'll be there soon
It's Not Going [Music]
This one this this this this this this this
da1283
1283[Music]
But follow the numbers was a clue
What does the number mean? Follow the number, right?
To follow the number, where is the number?
I've followed you, but you're guiding me there
It was on the flyer [Music]
than evil [music]
sheet music
Oh but wait a minute friend, it's not been a while already
I can't read it
Readability is not good
[music]
I feel like I've heard it a lot somewhere.
[MUSIC] Nice
practice hard
But I gave him some sheet music so far.
I really left the slum. Sometimes it's dangerous, but I need to know for sure.
Let's go, let's go at once
You have to proceed, as if you did your best, open up the gold report
[MUSIC] There's something in the tree
I have to find my father's traces and his location here.
Go Yahoo now without notice [Music]
There are a lot of jerk eggs, we will catch and eat them
I can't, I'm slow, I'm sure I'll get caught pretending, take this badge, let's
If dad sees it, he'll know he's my friend. I'll open the outsider batch.
It's a badge if you find all the music scores.
Where can I find out how many sheet music I gave you?
ah
[Music] I think you can come back later
you can see
I remember this wall is so huge.
It was a symbol and the fact that they kept throwing trash here
I remembered, it was so terrible, so
I may have failed
Cute cat
There are a lot of chucks when I look at the dead end. I need to be fully prepared.
Uh, there are a lot of him, so I’ll go to the bathroom soon. Now,
let's go
[Applause] Hyung, going down to a bad place
It's like, wait a minute, that's right. It's going to be a spectacular time for something here.
I wonder if it feels like
You'll need to make a quick decision. Something here
There are many moving moving moving
Moving moving moving I won’t fall over moving moving moving moving moving moving moving moving moving moving moving
moving street
Barorang Moving Moving Middle
Uh, it was a bit dangerous. What is it? It's down here.
left
It goes over and over and goes up and that's it
Hugh box was tough
recoil once again
Isn't it going like this
rebound again
It's a recoil system.
Hey, but I think cats really like something like this.
Go away, look around
uh uh oh no
But secretly, it seems that I can't center myself well in this hometown, but when I fall
I'll be near you, it's all here, when you fall right on the floor like this
Aren’t they originally good at landing like this?
You can't land well, my friend, your back leg hurts again.
Only the heart is healed, that's it, when I was hurt
I have to ask the cat to lick it. No, I have to go up.
Is this place
I think there's something here too
look at
There is a road to cross, and before crossing, here first
[music]
buy an item
It looks like you're looking for something and restoring something like power.
I think I need another part. I'm going to go get it. Let's go right away.
I need to take a good look around
I came up, but here it is
Excellent choreography, highly praised
uh what is there
oh they are white
Hey, you need to know the master. What are you guys doing? Why is he white?
[Music] I got something different, so it's not aggressive
I think that's right
It sticks so it doesn't stick
[Music] Yeah
Don't go straight [Music]
Looks like a boyDOC
K
Wait, it's not a jerk, who are you?
Did your son send you? My son [Music]
I'm worried, can you contact me in person?
[MUSIC] Didn't go as planned, going back home
I want to, I can't go
I guess you don't know how to get out
weapon because of you
this is a weapon
looks like this
It's said to be enough to explode Jerk to pieces when fully charged.
It requires 1.21gb of power to operate.
It's just a generator. That's it.
You just need to find a fuse
okay
Now trust me, do you have sheet music?
Tear it down, I'll help you with this, I'll tear it all up
another lift
It says 12. I've seen humans wear these costumes.
It was small in size and made a lot of noise
I ran around, but I remember now, thanks to the children, the distance is longer
They were lively, even though it was difficult because of the children, adults love them very much.
It was like
The chicken said it misses its son, it's the same
does it mean
Transactions that will jerk because of the noise
yes good luck believe me
I'll be back soon [Music]
huh
I think it's going to be a bit tight here.
I think there will be a lot of kids
ruler
What is this vibration sound while charging?
Kids come out with dog hair, oh nice.
Hey here too thank you thank you thank you
I have to help, man, ask for help
Go away, you have to go up.
I almost died
Supporters don't do it right
That's cool. You turned the generator back on.
I've seen how powerful it is. If you use this, you can get out of here.
Drone Air Nice Drone
[Music] upgraded
[music]
Guess I shouldn't use too much
Now, how do you use it? Left if right
The right and left are turning on this light, is it down?
Now you have a diplex, let's kill these guys and go
I want a server
Kill, melt and go
[music]
Hey, I need to tell you how to use it, but my friend
[Music] uh this is it oh
There is a risk of overheating
Oh, I can't use this much, so I'll save it and use it calmly, right?
The gauge goes up.
I'm going to cut it off and write it, right?
Open the door, I'll listen to you
oh it doesn't work
how was it
[MUSIC] What are you doing with this
Oh, get rid of this, then go over here and go down, then go in here
Push me, are you going up there, what is it?
I think I do this because it has a purpose.
Oh there's a gap
It's as if you just said it's blocked
I have to figure it out
They are coming, they are coming, they are coming, they are 100%
[music] hey
[clap]
Pleasant Amaterasu
Hey too many too many too many
wait for a sec
It was close, let's go back home
Run, the robot is fast
I mean run
open quickly
Hey, this is a lot of you guys. No, no.
While I'm opening this, with each other again
from here
What is it? You came out safely. What is it?
I prepared my heart
The touching moment of reunion Father, father, son
forgive me
What is Arobot Robotel
It's a touching tournament, but I almost shed a liter of tears for real
It was a heartwarming scene [Music]
Thank you for saving the chicken, my little friend. My son is better now.
You're no longer alone. Now we can fight Jerk.
Yes, Momo is waiting for you by the sewer
[MUSIC] I think we did a good job
Now let's find sheet music, everything else
Fuck it, momo can't.
I think I found Chapter 6, but I just need to find two more
What did we not do here? Table Ah this
Uh uh nice, here you go, now you just need to find one more one more
I just need to find one more. Did you eat only one in Momo's apartment bathroom?
In the bathroom of Momo's apartment, it's in your mind
This is my mother's house
is it in the bathroom
I found everything here, it fills up faster than I thought
a little
I expected 20 minutes and 10 minutes, so it's full
just found
Ballad to the Lonely Robot
[music]
oh this is good
[Music] But did you remember all the memories?
I don't know about that, but am I filling it 100% here?
Uh, I think I’ve heard a lot about this rhyme somewhere
[music]
I don't remember if it was the moon in Seoul
Now here it is.
little waltz
[Music] Spongebob, what SpongeBob?
It feels a bit like bikini city.
[MUSIC] Okay
thank you so much i'm a great musician now
yes i took it out
Oh, I can't see it up close, but first of all, with a badge in the shape of a face
I'll have to see it in the light
I can't see it, I missed the note, I want to see it up close, but I can barely see it
I got two of them
I did everything, but I'm filling it up to what percentage here
I've filled in a few percent now, I've filled it up to 48%, up to 50% here
should i fill it
But I think it will be hard to find again.
You look around so much, it's hard to find where you missed something
I don't know, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Let's pass it on. Finding the other one is going to be tough
It seems to be empty in the top row
But where can I check the memory
Ah, you can see it here Ah, there is a clue like this, look carefully.
Where is this?
it's possible
The one in the top row is when I rescued my dad earlier.
I passed by and can't find it again
ah can't ah
I should have gone before I met a lot of mollusks. Oh, it's over.
[music]
I'm going to say that this is your fault
I should have told you right away
I would have taken it
Momo is waiting for you on the boat. You can go there now, but there is nothing to do here.
I'm done. I'll close the door when you go.
yes close
No regrets, let's reset it
I don't have anything, shut up, I'm talking nonsense
But I missed it, so I can't go again. I can go again later.
I wonder if I can't cover it
uh
I feel the feeling here too, but I don’t feel it
Oh, I guess I can find a few more here too
Ah, now it's damaged, so I can't take care of it, isn't it?
I guess you're right
[music]
[Music] [Applause]
Ah, when riding a cart in the sewer
sewer
[music]
It wasn't like I was paying attention while looking at it like this, but I took care of almost everything.
Except for one
Asari, if you can't find 6 of them
[MUSIC] I would have just done it
Sorry to say it's one
[music]
what
It's a spooky place
[clap]
look at the color of the water on the floor
[music]
Why don't you open it, I have to do something
[Music] What should I do here
Alien is coming
big
Look at the size of the grain, it will come out in a year
[music]
I forgot ah
pressing the key button
me [music]
give me a ride
[music]
I've never been this far from the slums, but here with you
I'm not afraid this guy
Yes, you trust me a lot
There was a memory even here where there were a lot of pipes, right?
two of these one of this
that's what i was talking about
When I'm not riding, he won't just pass by, of course I'll give him a ride
drive fast
Will you be empty [Music]
I mean do it right [Music]
There's jerkers up there too [Music]
I can't hear you
What
All these old mechanisms are broken. I'll have to open them manually.
how to
[music]
oh this is possible
There's only room for me to go in, ah you keep going
I can't go but I'll find a way
[Music] I was so brave when I found the kids
Tell me, I wonder if you're brave, my friend
Hey wait, Yana, I need to find my memory.
It's not over, tell me it's not, quickly
Come with me as you go
Uh, I hate water.
okay
hey run fast
and
[music]
hey come in hey come in
Come in, come in, stop if you pass
I had a gap here
what can i do
[Music] Ah here, I must remember this place
remind me here
Hasto System Yes I remember now I ran out of clean water
A gigantic machine that digs deep into the ground supplied water to the city
Like all other resistances, to sustain human life in times of drought
It was a backup. The scientist gave me the blueprint of the water tank.
It was big enough for a building to fit in.
It's good if you find something like this I wouldn't have missed it a lot right now
Unless you missed it, no, you only missed one thing, it's a pity
Say 99% of men, okay?
This is where the monsters are
there are many kids
You wriggle a lot
wait guys
let's not go near
Oh, in advance, should I just head over there and come back?
If I do this here, I am 100% uneasy.
wait for a sec
Oh wait, it's okay, it's okay
You may not need to use a beam or something.
Isn't this the sound of Mori hunting?
To know the subject, the subject
need to know the subject
Oh come in, come on, maybe
Terrace
Oh, I keep getting nervous because the keys I need to press are all different
[Music] Confused
[music]
Lay down your eyes man uh
Waiting Waiting Need manned The moment manned delicate work is needed Hair
black hair black hair
all over the head
[music]
Hey, everyone with me, everyone with me
You guys have to come out too. Come on, all the sebaceous cysts
Everyone come, everyone come in, wow, everyone come in, everyone come in, yeah yeah
Everyone come in, you can come, come now, come now
[music]
something very nice
If you die like this, it'll be fun
I have to explode all of these things for the best taste
This isn't a clue, there's something here
Why did you kill him
It's not here, I don't think it's here
so many kids
The one who wasn't afraid of anything if I was with you, who is like trash
Where did that friend go? I'm afraid
So I can't eat, I'm sucking honey now
I think I should do something on the other side
I don't know what to do
pass over pass over
now
Sgam Sgam Hacking Hacking
too easy
skip right over
here and here is the clue
It's here, but it's disgusting here too
I want to bring a toothpick
[clap]
What are you, what are you doing, what are you doing?
Hey, you can't waste it like that. It's overheating.
how now then
Oh, that means I can't write anymore. I don't think I can write.
Uh, but wasn't it there? My memory
[Music] No, ah
turn off please
[Music] Oh, I just passed one
Everyone can't die, this is just
[Applause] Oh, he died too young
oh what is this
Oh so young [Music]
Should have done this before it went on
[Music] What I see
I'll read the memory.
[Applause] Say 98% male
right left
just right
ok close by
Not cats. I like those monsters.
wake up
This trash guy was just sucking honey. I'm alone in the dark
I felt like I was back on the network, but you me
I saved it, thank you, friend.
completely destroyed
Hey useless bastard, if that thing gets destroyed
How much did you work hard to get?
Yep man
good
Like my really rotten words
When you smell beyond imagination, at the moment you smell the real smell
When you want to cut your nose
Traveling on the sewer is good. It’s been a while since I saw a guy like you.
You're the one who contacted me, little outsider, right, right, ah, over there outsider
Voluntarily, he's waiting for me. He's meditating on top of my town. Okay.
[music]
This machine The scientist I helped wrote this
Just got sick, this was his last hope, just walk into the machine
He went in but I wasn't with him
He was alone, he wanted to, he uploaded himself to the computer
Everything changed after that but something went wrong with the upload he
I've been locked up for years, until the little cat showed up
You were waiting for me or me
I was like that I was that scientist
Now did you do this with this robot?
i need a moment
The big one has been restored
sorry i
I need some time I don't want to talk right now You don't have to talk Go away I'm this
I'll look at the memory
Hey, I need to bring a memory
come out
Memory report I've missed 3 so far
[music]
ah excuse me
Oh, I'm sorry, talk to me
I can't talk
Oh, you're still smiling. You like cats.
I still can't talk
I have to do this too
I mean you have to work hard
I wonder if there is anything to do
Oh nice to meet you, your face looks like a camera
that's interesting
Oh that's right that's right that's why you can't talk, he's on strike right now
have
Oh right, there must have been parents and friends, but what happened to them?
I want to open the city, but is there anyone left to save?
That's right, you've found your energy now.
okay
No, depending on your mood
I need to talk to the npc.
I'm more like a traveler
what is this [music]
hey
You don't know that you shouldn't disturb those who are doing Transcendental Meditation.
When I got the call, you were with Momo. Nice to meet you at last. Little
Because you're an outsider, you know momo and chickens
You must be familiar with outsiders. I miss them. When I think of them, my heart
It's convenient. You gave chicken to Momo in the slum.
I heard you helped me find it. I'm in Midtown right now, even now
If you want to see the outside, go there
I can take you there. I think you were planning to leave the city. Come on.
I got this and wrote the address on the back of the photo.
Gotta go up from the little town
If you succeed, you'll be the first to reach the outside. Good luck.
You won't need it, believe in you
Yes, I'm sorry I turned off the light earlier, I'm human, maybe the end of the world
I must be human, this is all I have left. A lot of memories have come back, what I forgot
How long will it be if I find him, my memory
Maybe I can restore it and take you home
Get more information from your companion or go upstairs to get to Midtown.
[Music] Companion
Gotta go
that told us to find her
There's a number on it [music]
what is this
You can find one here. It's patterned like this.
something red on the left
It's a light, it's like there before with the light sofa.
I think I saw it somewhere
Nice to meet you actually this food is terrible but eat here
That's all there is to it
It's better to solve it
He called me Chef Tin. He is an expert in upcycling leftovers.
Cooking Secret Ingredient Garden Ramen
[MUSIC] Let's interrupt the cooking
[music]
elevator
Go down and do something or go up, one of the two is you
Do what you want, you did this, that's this, this is right, memory
This language campaign was made entirely from scratch by robot robots. Really.
Awesome I remember what happened when I was on the network Exactly when
I don't know, but at some point all communication started to switch to this symbol.
I've been stuck inside my computer alone for a long time so I understand everything
I translated every sign and word one by one until I could
I know their language too, so I want to hear everything they say
Now then, let's talk about everything from the beginning
Were these the first
That's right, let's talk one by one, everyone
I know there are over 900 types of white paint.
Don't tell me, I'm making my own paint color right now
I'm going to call it trash brown.
Game clothes 9,536 wins 6 losses
Actually I'm programmed to win this game, but no one
can't say
Statistically I should have won at least eight times
Some call it trash but I call it treasure
Before I opened it, I was a boatbot before I opened it.
I repurposed my body as a hunter. Don't be fooled by that sound, like this arm I just found.
It might be hard and terrible. A poor friend's rust to peace.
Maybe there's a reason you're here
something here
got a red plant
Look at these flowers. They're pretty. Maybe there's a robot that will like them.
love flowers
there will be robots
Am I not sleeping?
Many homeowners
what do you say
I'm whining until you do this
Since Maine was in the period of deconstructionism, the viewer himself said so
Maine will definitely be a great artist if she practices elsewhere.
I love the smell of fresh paint
You can't smell it for a while, this is so
It's sad so man I know what you smell
I mean it didn't smell
Isn't that electricity everywhere?
Well hello, it's been a while since anyone visited, except for the damn thing, of course.
Imagine being able to use their power. Run on something like a wheel.
You're saying you're wasting your potential now
When I grow up, I want to be like his aunt and be great. I also explore like my aunt.
We wanted to, but the adults wouldn't let us leave the Enter Village.
I can't because I'm young, it's dangerous
Ah Clementine, the cozy sound of garbage falling
A sparkling waterfall, no danger, no poetry, no poetry, a happy place now
Listen, the strong concrete that protects me in that womb will also become my grave
Is it too solemn?
You can't do it, give up
There is also honey here. Can I get this?
oh right purple plant
Got it, this seems to have some clues
I think I can do something like this after I collect them by color like this
Find your way from the top of town to Midtown This must be someone
I think there'll be more [music]
the feeling is
Not even these guys [Music]
It seems to come out if I go up more
Why did I come here? I can't get over it
just
are you trying to climb
It's a flower shop
Hello friend How are you My aunt has a special plant that can live without sunlight.
I know you taught us how to grow it. I have a lot.
But there aren't many colors, you just need to find a yellow color.
I'll give you one of these, now I'll give you this too
I'll find yellow and come back. Instead, I need something good, okay
After I got bored, my aunt taught classes here. We did a lot of cool things.
I learned
The yellow seems to be somewhere
is it on top
Good morning. Did you get some sleep?
A little heart
Ah, I think someone just wrote my name in the Death Note.
I think I live now because I have immunity
just heart
I was thrilled
It's here
I found it all, I found it all
someone do this
Although I missed a few memories
I told you, but someone got it for me. It's my favorite color. Thank you.
Found all my friends thank you so much
[Music] If I find it all in my head, I'll take the memory
I'm not giving you the same thing, there's no such thing, please
My appearance, everything, thanks to you, I found all my memories
Thank you, I'll take away the memory.
Where are you? [Music]
I heard that the aunt is here, or the aunt
I'm going to meet you
[music]
It's a subway
This is the subway station. I completely forgot that this type of transportation existed. With this
You can go anywhere in the city. When people go to work
I rode it, so did I. I say goodbye to my family at home every morning
After saying goodbye
I remember I was doing this for my family but now they're gone
It was a long time ago [Music]
Families wanted to see the outside, but now does that mean anything?
what happened to them what happened to everyone
forget it anyway we're near midtown now
Let's find Clementine. There's a picture of him here.
Can you show it to the campaign members? Maybe there's a clue.
[Music] Let's take a look around here
Stop. I found all the flowers. Who am I?
Yes, it's a cozy room where you can feel the purple light
[MUSIC] Then
[Music] I don't know what
I don't know what the red graffiti is.
I don't know what it is, something blue screen pops up here
Table End End End End End [Music]
uh [music]
is not it
books
It's not here, it's going up
Memory Let me know if I missed anything If I think I'm missing something
At least 97% of men should keep it. I think there might be one here.
this is
There are so many books here. The Turing Test Legacy The Ethics of Artificial Intelligence
There's something I know, did I have a bibliography
The smell of the book and the feeling of turning the pages I remember it as very unique, almost comfortable
It was like a feeling. A book is like spending time with someone.
It was like
I have no words, I know this, I can’t say it
[Music] Can't talk
[Applause] And
It's noisy, I paid a charter
I'm counting
They're playing songs like this on the street corner
There must be police robots too
police logo
nice to meet you [music]
I already told you five times
They said you shouldn't run around like that. It's dangerous. Hey, I've never seen a robot like this before.
Bukchibuk Era Boineai Wanted The woman on the screen is different
Ask me, I'm busy here because of Yoshi, so I don't know anything
Don't worry about the garbage, we'll take care of it all here
If you plan to eat all of the batch, even if you are just doing something
I'll transfer the newspaper to jail and reboot
Even if you leave me alone, I'm not the one you're looking for
If you're looking for Clementine, she'll be hiding in the residential area.
Can you tell me in detail
If I didn't know if there was a place like this for no reason, I hid something here.
because
is there anything
Developer Eva, nothing here
I made empathy for no reason, so I made people confused
Lower floors have restricted access due to dangerous organic life.
Don't tell me, I've already been there
I can hear the sound down here
Clementine: We used to hang out together, but I want to leave.
I did it, it was like a breeze and it flew away, now I'm wanted
Sounded too heavy for me
ebb and flow
There's a memory on this side.
Even if you don't tell me, I know where you are
don't talk
what to do inside
Wow, Midtown is also looking for something like a vending machine
But if you eat carefully, you'll find it
If you look closely without missing anything
Oh, he must work for a cleaning company here.
There is an address after uh, the first symbol is the street name and then
Next is the floor and door number. Street floor door number.
it will be easy to find
oh not me
Street floor number No, what did you say earlier? Street
What did 3rd floor 5 on the blue street say?
[MUSIC] Door number
It's blue, but the door number is 5 on the 3rd floor. Okay
may be many
This scammer sold a defective battery
If you try to argue, you pretend not to hear me
This swindler, who was not a Sentinel in pure blood, must have been disbanded as a bupo
I can get in
Even if the kids go in, they don’t say anything, that’s the case here
uh safe what is digcode
off-duty off-duty
2458 That's it [Music]
dog fishing
code
Between 85 then 8542 or between No. 8
[MUSIC] Ah
to code 854
[MUSIC] Cat badge nice badge uh here
This is luminous, there is even luminous noise, noise
There is also a completely rare legend league.
It also has a glitch effect.
a handsome cat
Should I go in here first? Is this the beginning?
I don't know if there's anything else
Sorry kid you can't play here this factory is for money hairballs like you
It's not a place. Enemies are limited, but only for a while.
That's it, if you wait a few years, it will open right away. A few years.
is the distance
Are you hiding and entering? I’m busy right now, why are you calling me?
Later, when you're being chased, I'll see what you're doing in hiding
Right
What are you doing hiding?
What are you
Who are you? All the cops are holding you that day. Then you didn’t come here.
It smells like memory here, isn't it?
[MUSIC] I've been to the city below, there
I have a friend called pp
I haven't seen the article for a long time PP Did we see it too?
who is pp pp
[music]
oh what is here
I don't know what the heck they say downstairs.
I can hear
I'm here to hear this
uh what is this
ghost
[music]
uh here it is nice
I like it here, on the soft pillow and on the cool drink
How nice it would be if I could actually taste it
The drone is useful, but I miss my body, I miss the feeling, being sick and hungry
And I know it's no use, but here's a little bit
can't you stay longer
Nothing difficult
Spread the diaper
Ah, I really want to live like a cat too
envious friend
I've run a bar, it's the coziest place here on my lap
Until I put the screwdriver in. Now the door is closed.
Makes me angry, but my only customer drives me away
You guys are not so cool right now, it's really okay
I don't think it's harmful
Inside the nuance of smoking, it's a robot I know. I've seen it often. I live around here.
I don't remember how you always talked about leaving the city.
It's a good place, why are you leaving?
Oh, there's a hologram here too
wake up oh what
I'm suddenly up and screaming
[music]
I then came out here and then
This looks like a restaurant bar
[Music] I'm trying to win first place in this game
I was going to download it, but there was a malicious code. I don't know why, but now
everything looks weird
I have mastered every game in existence but how this works
I can't understand. I can't see the big picture.
You seem to be gathering information about ancient machines, so you're a weird girl. Ah, you have this too
no maybe
Hey, the song is much better, but I’m casual
I don't know ton-in, but I like almost everything
The picture came out well, it's all the same story
[MUSIC] I thought I was cooking something
[music]
My favorite drink is oil. What do you like?
[MUSIC] Like that
I think there is something
what could be
[clap]
What can I do here? Is this a barber shop?
It looks like it's not a barber shop, it's just that
Friends, I've been here once. Why are you asking?
When you exit my store, there is a residence area to the right.
If you go right, you can go right up there.
how
Ah, what is it? Teleportation
Oh here
The barbershop was a social block where people gathered to talk, joke, and tell secrets.
We shared. It was a fun place. Even after the humans disappeared, the campaigns continued.
Keeping the shop up
What's the difference between the fact that it's not
Come to think of it
Oh what a screw
what is the feeling
It looks like they're selling cotton swabs here
If you go out and go to the right, you will see that the residential area is the residential area.
ah nice to meet you
What should I make tonight Chef, do you know this?
You can't pay real money. Money.
[music] hey
Because you said nonsense, what is this?
oh here too
Hey, this is a bit real, it will come out if you just walk around
That's right, robots imitate human work and behavior.
It's interesting, I think they sell burgers and street food here
Do you remember where you most wanted to go when you were a human?
It's small but friendly, I can't remember the waiter's name, it started with m
looks like
[Music] Should I switch?
My friend Sentinel runs into it, but those evil guys took my friend Pablo.
I'm doing a 350-year-old community history meeting.
But these guys don't die anyway, are the boring times the same?
All I could do was walk near the elevator, but Centy screamed. For years we were
I lived with the saying that I couldn't live on the surface
We accepted it as fact, but why
[music]
Shall we go once? How will it come out?
I don't think I need to go now
I think it's better to talk to Clementine.
There doesn't seem to be any vending machine elements.
I'm sorry, this is a clothing store. You also play loud music all day.
Don't touch anything with the guys who listen Don't be loud
Unexpected
to choose harshly
Looks like a locker room
what is insert item
I think you can do it with some kind of tape
Uh, you're just coming here, what, I thought there was something
here for some reason
How far do you go?
tired
I blink
Nice
Where did you go? Police patch Oh, is this it?
That's right, the one I just got next to the neon sign
there is a gold color
Do I need to go to the corner after that?
I can't go in
I'm shedding bloody tears [music]
Sentinel go to hell Long live the outsider
I can't stand it. Give me some food for the cat.
I want to feed you, but I have nothing to eat
It's the trendiest store in Midtown, but the owner of the store is pretty nasty.
It was trash
It's trash
uh sorry uh what is this what is this what is it
Oops, oops, I don't think there are pockets or anything.
Oh sorry sorry [music]
sorry
Oh, you said go away
I have to go to the third floor of the residential area here.
this asshole we can see you too
Ah, I was talking about watching CCTV.
Life has become boring since Centre installed a camera in our house.
Watch one Bonaire
you can't steal
If you do something with Tintin and Miko and something on me, I can give you one security
I installed the camera generation, ok
okay okay enough enough
not enough
If you turn off the 3 security cameras, they will give you a tape.
Where was it? I saw it before, which store was it at?
What store were you in?
What does it mean to lose an out shop character sheet?
So, I've been preparing for this session all week.
I'm sorry, I forgot where I put it. Let's do that.
I mean do it right
This is all right, that was 3 earlier
Inverted triangle 3 and 5 35 OK, this is the second floor. That’s the third floor. On the third floor.
It's room 5. It's room 5 on the 3rd floor.
ok i like it
he did it too
A Nice
I like it
Now I just need to do two more, just two more
On the way down, on the way up, before going up
Do a little more research and see what
The way up here too
I just need to find two more CCTVs. There's one over there.
I have to step on the steps to get over it.
there's one here too
Okay, but can I just remove this?
Then I wrote it down, this is
I'm not coming
okay bring it
[Applause] Cassette tape
Got it [Applause]
Enjoy our song, you will like it
You're dancing before you go
Let's go to a clothing store first and insert a cassette tape for a song
[Music] What is this?
[music]
what
Damn how do you turn this off uh what are you doing when he's looking away?
[Music] A jacket
Steal A Nice [Music]
This is the jacket we stole from the store.
It must be used when infiltrating. Now let's go see Clementine.
3rd floor room 5
3rd floor 2 3
It's the only way for cats to enter.
Are you here Clementine
What is it, be careful
Uh you're not strong, don't mind who you are
what do you want this
Wait, he finally decided to send someone. Are you my new recruit?
You see, I'm not very tall, how can I?
You passed, you're quite talented. Ever since I left Ent Village,
I've been looking for a way to the outside but the Sentinel is always
I watched
follow me
I think there must be something here. There must be a reason why it came out of here
[music] uh
no [music]
floating point
there are many here
is it a hideout
no it's not
I thought there was something
It was just a healing space
where should have gone
I plan to use this old subway these days
I'm standing up. I've got a key to start it. All I need is an atom to power it up.
It's just the battery
I don't know the name, Boomerzki is a robot wearing a gold chain.
If I was quick like you, I would sneak into the factory.
there will be no problem
necklace
Is he the guy who told me to quit earlier? He looked a bit hip, but he
is not it
You're right, where did you get this from?
For some reason, there was nothing cheap
The battery is supplying power to that factory, but the whole is a restricted area.
I'm pouring it thoroughly, I sent it back if it wasn't an employee
but who am i
Oh, you should also bring a worker's helmet. A jacket and
I have a helmet or a jacket, but I don't have a helmet.
Take a good look at the central intersection. Oh, it's here.
No one can enter the store while it is being restocked.
If you think about incompetence, it will probably take a long time
Uh huh
It's not him, it's not him
I can't remember the name, there was a space here too
It looks like him. Should I wake him up? It looks like he's going up and dropping something.
Hey wake up I'm looking for you guys
I have to go to work soon
I'm going
hey i brought a friend
what time is the time
I'm insane, I'm sorry, I was drinking a little
okay nice
let's go in let's go in
where is the hat
go out go out
ok nice came out
[music]
I want to look back for a moment
Uh, you look like a janitor
yes let's go
Shouldn't I take off the necklace? It's too flex.
[music]
[Music] Take off the necklace
Shouldn't I look inside the box? I guess I only see the label on the outside
[music]
You have to leave when it's safe, don't know what will pass
[Music] Alright alright
[music]
Oh, must I go the opposite way?
[MUSIC] Follow the shadows
[music]
There is no such thing as a very genius cat
Is it in the center, is it an atomic battery, is that
[music]
Are you placing one
Oh, I'm bringing this here
[music]
I can step on one yet
oh ok you can bring it
You should bring it. It's an alien object. You should bring it.
No, can I step on this
[music]
okay
[Music] It bounced, can I just bounce quickly?
[MUSIC] Here the facility has stopped
I did it with my batteries. I need to get out before the cents show up.
We have to go to Clemental.
Oh, I solved the puzzle too lightly.
The way out is good, the way in is tough, but the way out is fast.
Sentinel blocked it
Are you dancing even when you go out? Even if you guys can steal our place
Can't steal our moves
I can't dance, there's no point
Put it on. I think it will all be solved if you block our block.
Are criminals targeting my vintage card collection?
All of this has become futile
I'm home, there's always a way to get in
king's power
I think I can just go in
It's absurd
I'm dumbfounded
[music]
have to go the other way
here
[clap]
I was surprised, I didn't know you were on the other side
[music]
Oh stop, just watch something one by one
uh
[Music] It's here
[MUSIC] Hi
Be quiet if you go here
ok hey
[music]
Where are you
I hid above you. I was finally on my way here.
where is clementine
where did you go
Are you pooping in the bathroom?
where did clementine go
Look at the clue board
The answer is in my stuff and there are 4 climates The answer is in my stuff
There are 4 symbols
OK potted jewelry
planter jewelry vase
This is one too, isn't this?
[MUSIC] I found something, I can't see anything
surely
three first pots
The second one is not a conical hat, but what is the second jewel and the last one?
It looks exactly like this
My sensor can only detect chemicals that are harmless in the gaseous state.
I can't limit the feeling of whether it was comfortable to remember
The camperion can't smell like me, so why?
A message is hidden even under the courage
[music]
Because there is a hint clue in the house
What is it? It's in an apartment. It's really strange.
I don't have anything
Ah, there's something left here Nightclub Uh this is it
Kkokkalcon Nightclub
I'd be up here as a nightclub nightclub
unless it's something
There can't be room above
this is it
[MUSIC] Ah
I'm with the blazer
If you find them all, I'll put together the order now.
Oh, is this the first one then this is right
I guess it was the expression of incense.
I saw that the last one didn't open
Above all of this, not this
OK Night Club
Can't you go down comfortably?
[music]
Oh, you're having a hard time [Music]
huh
It's a place that has nothing to do with you, go away
I think I will have to go back
I think I have to climb back
[MUSIC] I can get into the club
Gil is such a kid here
what are you doing
[music]
what one
hello how are you
have i seen him
Pretend you're cursing
I need to find my way into the club
[Music] Where is this
If you go into the central yellow bell cow, you will find it. Oh this
Uh, this place was originally closed. That's right.
It was closed, but it's open. I couldn't go in earlier, but I
Its purpose was to protect the people of the Sentinel. It was aimed at eradicating categories and restoring order.
maintenance work, but life in the city becomes difficult and various groups
Starting precisely, Cent quickly becomes the hound of the powerful.
Turned out they were the perfect tools to control the city, obedient and suspicious
After the end of mankind, they continue to
I'm in control, I'm always doing my duty relentlessly
something
I am proud of having collected a lot of memories
I've lost a tooth anywhere
I don't think I can do this right now, but I don't think I've seen this before.
Oh no way this is the stairs behind
It's an Amazon nightclub
I have to go up, but is there a way up?
'Cause I think I'll have to go up
this guy
Hi, how did you get up here? Do you want to party with us?
Touch it, let's talk, kid having fun, you know this
I don't know how to use it, I stole this. The sea you can't imagine
where did you steal
Hey what is this dragon
I like my mask so I made it myself
It interferes with the Sentinel's scans and doesn't even look cool.
oh you look like
It's like you
I paid the security guard extra money to get the dance moves today.
program holograms in your spare time
[Music] Bartender there guest VIP balcony nail
I went in and was using it privately. I think someone called Blazer made a reservation.
[Music] Left right beep beep this is me
taste dance
this [music]
The club sucks. That pathetic person tried to go to the VIP room
I kicked it out trust me so I just stole this lever in retaliation
Bring me a drink and I'll give you this useless lever
If you bring a drink
It shines
I got the lever handle. It's delicious.
everyone
DJ
Sid is here, let's start the party
[music]
I want to try this I can't do this right now
I want to try this.
[music] uh
lever
ah nice now
came up
Oh, you can find the memory before it goes up. Wait a minute.
I can't find it when I go up
uh what is this
Ah, this looks like an elevator, I guess.
[MUSIC] Ah
hey this is
It's a place only mischievous people can find.
When I was human, I got together with my friends and partyed all night. Thanks to you, the next day
It was always hard in the morning, rather than going to an unlivable surface, I had fun here
It felt good to find it, but the conditions in underground life were getting worse and worse.
The capitalist greed of corporations such as corporations and the police state created by Sentinels are also more
It got ugly Now I remembered why we ended up like this
Wow ah two ah my teeth are falling out It's bittersweet
Oh, I hope it feels like making a little road
I'll have to look around each one
Uh, that’s it, it’s it, it’s it
[music]
Blaze, where are you going?
toilet kana
[Music] Nice to meet you
I also have a very good relationship with the Sentinels.
I don't know why the other kids complain about Centerrail so much
I'm tied to Clementa, but I can't believe he's a blazer trash
It's crazy, you're as smart as you think
It's not because I have bad feelings for the little cat anyway, it's just
it's just business
It was a betrayal, ever since I said goodbye
I did [music]
Gold necklaces are business, and money is more money than stains or camaraderie
Take everything you think is important
[Music] I heard your favorite sound just now
Uh where did my bag go
That's right, I'm a smart cat
I'll have to shoot the prison prison break
do this
Genius genius, there is nothing you can't do, there is nothing you can't do
omg
I guess you're being tortured
Are you doing something like an electric shock?
I have to go in here
don't get caught
going down here
I can go into all the rooms
Oh, you should go down right away, but you can ask for it quickly
Because of the timing [music]
waiting waiting
uh here it is
found
Hey, the rain is gone, the rain is over there
Since there is no rain right now, we can't communicate with the cat.
very
with cat
Because I don't have a bag
It's inconvenient because I don't have a bag
brought
[Music] [Applause]
Let's go, follow me I got it
where should i go
I don't know what you're talking about
The cat is so cute right? The small one at the back
There's something sinister about it [Music]
Uh what, why is the highest rank being locked up alone?
[Music] It can't be like this
[music]
Oh, I think it's going to be a little tough here, but the choice is to come out and leave
I want to go, I should just throw it away and live with this feeling
[music]
more
I don't think they'll help me, but I'm afraid I'm running out of time.
Ghanaian cuisine
[music]
Hey, you just stay here, it's frustrating. If it were me, just go down now
gone [music]
Still
[music]
I guess I'm passing the timing master again.
[MUSIC] Ah
It almost became steamed
[music]
will pass
Wait Once [Music]
[music]
and
How do I get it? Should I get it quickly and run?
I don't know, just right
Hey, isn’t this cruel?
How Cats Like This [Music]
[music]
okay okay
okay
come
If unnie can move too, then move quickly.
If you leave it alone every day, it will move
uh again
I felt like I was on a computer system in a lab again.
Thoroughly lonely, you, me, me, I, the child who came back to you
I can't believe you are a good friend
I'm glad we can be together, but it's not safe yet
come in soon
come in
why isn't he coming
did you have lag what are you doing
Ah, iRobot, what is it all of a sudden?
Got a trojan horse
I was surprised
Come to your senses, do it quickly. What are you doing? Talk to me.
I'm on top trying to break the window
[music]
Hey, I really have to repay the favor for my whole life, but Clementine
At this rate, the Sentinel is blocking the road again.
If you do this, you will be caught soon. You go to the cell.
It's like luring them in and then locking them up
me
[music]
I see that guy on the floor over there. He's a rebooted robot. I lost my memory.
I don't want to, I'm so scared
I think I need to do something here after luring it out.
[music]
This recovery center has helped me the most. My mind is clear and clear.
What food am I now
Should I keep it here, but I can't use it first
Wow, he's tough. Ah, should I have done Yoo-in first?
I can't come in
nice
everyone
It's a memory, it looks like the last one, then
That's right, this is the end of normal memory. Then
The ending is approaching, but the poor fellow Sentinel is resisting
You seem ruthless to me
As far as I'm concerned, they deleted this guy completely. No more emotions.
I have neither awareness nor memory.
Ah 98% of men
Hey don't bother me I only have 758 years left
free except
Since 758 758
this should be closed
Ah, but he's a problem. I have to bring him too.
Oh if this
come quickly
What else do I have to do
Uh, I feel like something could come out now
The only way out of here is to come out in the reenactment room over there.
Looks like a way to access the control room
Let's find out
there is a switch here
It's a person
okay
What are you trying to find? You're telling me to do it.
my key
You're lucky, the key is stuck in the door, so get on
Go beyond and climb behind the deals you can now access
let's go
I don't do it right to some extent
I mean drive straight
[Music] Hey, let's jump in the car and bounce
[Applause] Let's get out of there.
hey friend
this is my friend
did you forget me my friend
Wow, look at this one without looking back
[music]
I'll kill you, Clementine
[Music] The other kids chasing it
in 30 seconds
are doing
What are you doing Why can't we both get cents off guard
No, I'll get them attention. You'll run away in two days.
The Outsider Manifesto says we must go outside at all costs.
It says do
You're one of us now, not everyone has to go outsider
But one of the ducks has to go
Hurry up, I'll save a record about you in my RAM, little outsider
I think we went together enough right now. Admit it honestly.
How did you get in?
I think it will take even if you come with a humanoid cent.
I'm filming an impressive drama by myself for no reason. You're right below me.
It's here
Neko
Corporation [Music]
Wow now I can eat the key crab I've been doing it for 5 and a half hours now 5 hours
If you look at anti-YouTube, most of them are about 3 hours
I heard you took it off, but you made the editing hard and you make it.
If I want to get into it quickly, I can wake up quickly, but the challenges and things like that
I guess it took me a while to find it, to be honest
[Music] There aren't that many things that really get stuck
did not
[music]
You still become 98% of men
atmosphere
[music]
hello guys hello how can i help you
helper 477
These guys are robots for humans
There is no specific name. What is it?
Hello residents of Walled City 99, that's right, these guys don't have names.
I'm only cleaning. I guess I'm a robot for cleaning now.
This area is being painted. Mares be careful with the paint
something neat
Hello residents of the 99th Walled City, my aunt is currently quarantined if it goes through the surface
Locked out due to procedure [music]
Ask the certified engineer in the control room
Hello, what can I help you with?
Hello, I am currently cleaning the windows.
I have to go to the control room.
I've sealed the city for safety. Okay, I'll go to the engineer.
The control room looks like this
what do you do with this
i think i have to do something
They say only humans have the right to enter [Music]
Together, we can open the barrel.
How to make it look human How to make it look human
come to your work
Come to think of it, I'm that one.
That's right, I'm soft
what
I see what else you need
What can I do now I don't think I'll make it now
What were each of you doing?
yes this is the correct answer
This is the control room for the whole city, I controlled everything from here and now
Nothing, nothing, I remember I hated them
They've got it all, clean space, infinite power movement car, but
They didn't use it properly. Epidemic. I remembered now.
Everyone was dying, but they only thought of themselves. Nothing helps.
I saw my family dying in front of my eyes. I felt helpless.
there was nothing I could do for
But I can help you now and we can go outside together
Humanity, I will keep the memories of the people I loved
Oh really uh 92% of men what is uh 98% not
Ah well, in terms of numbers, it can be 92%
this is my main computer
According to the mainframe, no one has been here for years. It's been a while.
The whole city is stuck in a lockdown cycle, disable it and we'll get out too.
You'll be able to online the rest of this system
The data we need is this computer
in
While you turn on the power, I will find the system access password encryption key
it's heart
Now, just tell me what to do
The child is all growing up, right?
I deliberately set it up to turn it on while passing by at once like this.
my big picture
I'm so glad I succeeded I found a friend I figured out how to open a city here
I saw that there was something wrong.
there must be a way
[music] rope
control
That's a workstation that opens the city. It has a security layer, so I can't use it.
Let's do what we do best, hack the rig and you destroy it
Shall I break it? Shall I break something?
I'll send you all this
Now, let's do one thing. Then, where else?
[music]
Ah, it seems that hacking can do this too.
what is what
tango
Ah, I guess this is just a story, right?
I think it's a story
[music]
Arch, I did that last one earlier, but I didn’t. I have to hack this again here.
Hey, is there any hacking here? There is one left, but it was here
[MUSIC] Something slowed down
He's not exploding [Music]
Ah, it started again, I think I broke my body to pretend to be sick
I'll be fine. Just take me to the workstation. I can turn that alarm off.
It's quick again
okay now
There's something to say, but, but you trash man, you can do it.
Cheer up a little bit more, anyway, just remove the battery and I'll take you there
I just need to put in the charger.
We know that it takes a lot of power to bring down the city's central control system.
I knew more than this drone fuselage could hold out now.
Security is disabled, so I can't control the system and open the city.
Covering this could destroy my software.
Yes but I made that choice when I first connected it to my computer and now
This is the result. We can't see the outside together.
I'm sorry, I thought I had to carry on the memories of mankind, I had to hold onto the past
But now I see the future from the campaigners and
Come on, I'll take this off of you too.
You were the best friend I've ever been, thank you
[music]
no [music]
You saved the real world, you cat, go after me
what's there [music]
How long did they play? In the end, I did it, the cat
Oh my god, the cat finally did it, this is unbelievable
[music]
what the sentinels
Clementine is still alive
[music]
I'm not taking you
I can't believe I went through hardship here
for 6 hours
Where can I go in advance?
No, even the cat is relentless, just how
So I might be able to save it, but watch him just throw it away
Also cats
If it was a puppy, I would have taken it a little longer.
pigeons
long time no see
Do you want to meet your friends? Do you want to meet them now?
[music]
What was that at the end, what was it trying to tell you?
long [music]
in 5 hours 50 minutes
Cleared Stray
It was a very good cat game and I just couldn't get the achievements and badges.
I had a hard time
First of all, the regrettable thing was that I worked hard to collect it, and in the end, I was naked
Going out tells the players this
That's right
What kind of nonsense was this?
Does it have any meaning, but still 92%
I worked hard to eat memory. Okay, everyone worked hard, and here
I'll finish it. Okay
[music]