Now This time The game is called Stray Steam New It's a game
game price 35,000 won game evaluation  almost 6 only  evaluation
did 98%
Overwhelmingly Positive these days people keep going play games Please
What the heck What kind of Is it a game Once Try
Game Story Breaking up with family down the road lost one lonely
Cat's It's an adventure says which degree puzzle elements say say say
Sorry for frustrating please then immediately once
I'll try I'll try
Rain A lot It's coming
this @@W1 of the game] the main character is now @@W4 watching the cat] [ W5@@ tastes like says says
Once How much How cute Let's see
here baby cats there
I who are you something best end Got Boss Feeling
erroneous things
now now pad and are The pad is The pad is I'm not familiar with I'm not
Ah Act Tail Have Play
Are you friends Look Friend Yang Punch Baro Gotta punch
with him played with him Let's play
just fighting game developer people All All
@@W0 the cat] raising said said
this bastard where cheeky
Face Lick
here what not here followed by
Mundo there just Is it a shelter look But here a bit lab feels like is nice
where go well went gift It's flying is it uh what is
Let's go Now Game It's over
Main character What's your name Stray
[Music] Game Name Stray
Stray
Cheeky The butterfly slept Interrupted
Rain Has it stopped I see
[Music]
Today [Music]
Graphics It's okay That's right
on the wall [inside W1@@ [Music]
A little The world A little Apocalypse Did the world perish or only here like this or
game sound ok not bad not
[Music]
Now Where should I follow [Can I become W2@@
Let's go Guys
meow sound bet
uh each other like this exchanging where possible
downtown generous downtown why going going
why go go
Why going going
I pee try to cum
Ah Scratcher [Similar to W2@@ feeling
Like this You're nailing your claws
[Music] This Octopus Drill Get it Get out of the way [ W5@@ Dangerous
this falls
toenails well trimmed
Uh Me too I want to go up
Ah Water Drink
Sweet minerals It's rich
out of time no Is this a thing
Delicious Deliver [Music]
Sweet
here what do
Ah Again Kisses To receive  Dating is it
One love
Like this Something Scenery I like it That's right Me too Like a cat live want
ah me real as a cat born I want next life
like this free soul
I am here I have to go
hold press continuous jump also available here Ah here not becomes
Now Now game Early game Some Tutorial By feeling
Kana Look at as go not It works
yes yes me and interest Some give me
is the main character
me comfortable road I want to go
uh here but it was fine scenery really
before length below holes there
kids coming there here behind can't Bonaboda
Ah here something slightly difficult looks Hold Press Observe
Difficult Magnification Possible
follows becomes becomes looks like Why Why Why Why quickly Go Okay
OK go become go no
Uh A bit It's dangerous Ah This For some reason It's my turn will fall I'm sprained
is 100% correct this unconditionally falls
How did you do it I overworked it got away uh
[MUSIC] Huh
kids slightly expression like this expression [ It wasn't W5@@ but
Finally sent like this It was an expression
I must have fainted
alone left
Uh Some Does it hurt Look Uh What now lame has
[Applause] Left Hind leg
big
How did the brain get hurt
here what is
what works what
Turtles What
Ninja Turtle
do do do
together let's follow
Even now well can't pay me uh Little Better Something
same right uh recovered
But Your voice is a bit I rested Are you also corona
moves
The name of the dead city is It's ominous
@@W0 of death] city
Those What is it But Skeletons
[MUSIC] I'm sure passing by
[Music]
uhCCTV
me watching got
how do [music]
here going down going down going down going down method
That You can see them What is identity What is
[Music] uh here Robel there robot
Oh It's a robot
Go here Go or look road So here trumpet is forbidden if you scream not
be be quietly be be look
uh someone me now calling feeling That's right
Asking for help that or
Help Asking Something Looks like
Wait here What  will be
I don't care
Something Could be would be I thought Is there I see
keep way guide go same Uh What are you following
Is this place Look
who is
uh bucket picked up
uses must be bucket
Dongil Yang picked up
this water like stuff get some  to be later
Here is very It must be dangerous but the bucket
if if
uh right bucket I used bucket dropping
directed by should be should be I am hopefully Split line
this what
yes the cat is this is nothing can't Tuna
Well Everything Did Very Satisfied
[Music] Where go up go be [W5 Is there @@
is up
This is last is looks like uh Right under road open
what do what stance know Person
oops
what doing that's
ah
this is scratcher like what doing Ah me poo line
moment
we home no what the heck do People no
successful
OK OK
water water
this water drink stuff what Nourishing later thirsty like this that if you have
don't drink should be [Because W2@@ is
who called me called uh what Me moment me coming give
this is again identity is what is
here too is there
Aliens Like Not Like Not
uh moves
you what is
What a fatal blow Did you get hit Look uh
concussion came thing looks like i just just hit chin that one [Same as W9@@ lower jaw Just Slap
How did you throw it away
KU got hit
I Killed Is that
here too there
a lot
I was scared now
run away
I have to run I can
Ah Get lost
uh now everywhere go crazy now [Music]
ah
Something
Ajelly  a lot
[Applause]
uh stop
Ah But These guys Now Boil If you eat it will be delicious will be looks like and
[Music]
like this that to me itchy
Meow Sounds This [Music]
who is me calling that [music]
who called called me called
strangle da hit meow sounds Like this Act
Cool Where Go Here
[Music]
this is monster no kids
very just genius
Genius This is my hometown
no who keep like this far away Brunei once close distance not
How far me I'm taking you
This is Where should go should be
This is is That's a big deal
not pushing uh what just Something reacted
[MUSIC]Here go over that thing [Same as W3@@
how can go beyond this is good ah no way in in in
is
[Music]
Where Are you
here cctv a lot right
Where Uh No That was dangerous
like this I don't care
This is
here is here
Where must go to the other side not it goes over
where go not have degrees of freedom some have Isn't that
smart smart cat
length true
because it's a cat possible length
here
Here's the chicken Can't Go
chickens sure not not people
here too CCTV is there
maybe i see when now now Players that
sense some tell me chapters for like
right
something falling sound flying
there too go by will be will be looks like What is this is necessary is this is this
Switch Pull Hair or Pull Throw away
Maybe I don't know carry let's go
Apartment
here person would be
this is can't can't stand it
uh me but that where sense Holding On Going
Abandoned Resurrected
[Music]uh what
help need
help needed
Graiger is
[Music] Talk Look
Zaiger
[Music] To Door Enter Give Electricity Turn On give me
it's kinda tough it's looks like I'm Fit is
fuck just say say
Moon
This is What is
Wow
Here pick Gungaa This everything If plugged in
then earlier not one I brought it where gone
ah here above there just Falling obvious almost caught
now two  remaining two Also here there
here plug it in
the rest one over there on top of to have
[Music]
hey really like this cat really
I'm going to miss
Totally Genius Genius
secret door open [Music]
what who called me called
you are
uh here capsule like stuff [in W5@@ contains is
right
this is what is this what is this what is this what is I picked it up
where put is
last not one over there outside go out Did you catch it me but what
I don't know I don't know
uh here arrows there here
What is
this is what is it [Music]
No way you called that uh
[Music]
no what snot only yes me What What a great called called but
uh what is it over there Plankton little
how stationery arm thing like He called called
[Music]uh you killed that
[Music] This is What is it
what @@W0 said] said
worked was I was now free Thanks camera weird lines OK
Dead City's Cat  My I don't remember the name Not Not Out of memory Corrupted Thing
I guess long e network stuck @W5 here live was @@W8 scientists]
[@@W0 for W0@@] worked now call me b12 call me [ W5@@ give me but say b
let's call inside on the surface like that written There is
Dead City is is dangerous is a place, but you will be fine will be [ It looks like W5@@ here let's go me
Follow me B
[Music] I have a friend [I got a W1@@
Where told me to follow you
Where Did you go
ah this must fall apart I like it Nice
right
Are you gone
sweetheart
Where went Little friend Where
computer and do you have
ah here here ah me out You thought it was
low key statement column be Yes I remember Yes
I will I will bring you I will give you
I liked it The battery is already running out It's amazing Follow me like [ W5@@ can control can control
is is is is
Wear this wear it
This is What is this
That's heavy That's heavy [Music]
uh what gag I'm going to suck this Enter and take
ah kinda adapt couldn't did look I did couldn't did
Toddler Crawling Rough Look
Hey Me [Music]
That's heavy
[Music] yet
adapt more need
This is backpack like you small for tetrapods made made
Inconvenient Not Do Inconvenient don't worry Don't I'll get used to it I'm going to
key digitized backpack put in inventory open
key is is there key this is check What is
turn see might be got
[Music] That's right
other what is what is memory is what is this What is
[MUSIC] It's not that simple
curious stuff if you have it show me show me pass other if robot is if that
@@W0 to the robot] even if you show it you can Let's get out of the apartment
Here Pass Can Got Now
oh this how not
[Applause] Mmm
[MUSIC]Lights ON
Survey Available [Music]
here on what written in stuff [It looks like W6@@, isn't it
Code Is there Somewhere Password Find Becomes [than W6@@
correct password is where is written is look at
uh 3748
74 8
wow
Cool It's a place Over there There's an elevator There's no doubt important can see must go up do
like like
no you flying around you ride If you don't go , so
atmosphere okay here too
[Music] uh It's comfy
[Music]
uh I remembered outside I mean
before been there like feels like heard You are here came you are
That's It's outside Me Someone outside I'm going I promised
Who was it
Postcard Mural drawn , let's take it
New Item Same
I why oops remember got It's there remember where came from I wonder
Let's go [Music]
What is the postcard What is uh What is Ah This like a memory that all all find it
What can be is the same
we sky again see be I promise you
uh wait on the back once shall we go What's there
just
live creatures are there any people like like that
this is what is Translate Safe Zone
it's safe is it
What is This is
Here too monsters a lot
Wait a minute Wait a minute
Safe Zone No
that robot is is robot
Slum
something back alley world like
[What is it? @ What is
robots me are afraid of me, just is my hometown
The reason is must be of course
why me don't be scared
Gatekeeper [Music]
Yes with me let's fight this is
not like looks like
[Music] uh laughing there
Talking [Music]
@@W0 what they say] their own unique @@W3 with language] [@@W4 with W4@@] thing
looks like [music]
You're a jerk That's not it
we you like species seen Enemies not so much
no one eat  we even in town ok nobody not eat what i
Robot Wanna Eat [Music]
Jerk is What is Jerk [Music]
These guys I'm afraid of something a lot must be kids
Just now those bugs the best big jerk
cute looks good expressions personality doesn't look kids faces
everything the same born
[MUSIC] road oh something sounds like what [ W5@@ not needed
item show what a postcard this show be be go
outside photos nonsense not the elevator is [ W5@@ doesn't work doesn't work @@W7 here]
Leaving Impossible things Everyone Knowing there is what the outsider is like that
think don't but [music]
if not if not my guys now [ W5@@ are all gone Momo only [Except W7@@ I mean
combined no at the same time organ meet Talk see count but already
he leaving girl gave up that's the best [ W5@@ beggar
he orange neon sign that that In a tall building lives is
ah that that [music]
ah if not bottom kids what Is this like this
Help Request [Music]
Anytime Don't hesitate , not call me call me I'll help you
this guy orange neon big @@W4 in the building] told momo said bet said he
us where get out be be It's the only clue
yes so what
do you because surprise surprise Jerk in lines
Okay
er sleeping  sleeping  That's [It looks like W6@@
you really elevator ride can be [Do you think W6@@ I am Tomorrow 374 years old
works that works that saw Never ever
why go up do go there No one nothing no
five conspiracies
Weird As Image My Meditation Don't Disturb
another that no uh wait
i not
Work hard on your toenails A bit Cut them off
then where go go up Go up can do it
Length WHERE I WHERE
step on go up can go up
here not would be would be same as feeling would be would be would be would be
here kids a lot there
uh what work more than one
beside go get in the way be be this
Ah This You should drop it It's fun Talking
Bapora
Don't bother I didn't too I'm clumsy
right away interrupt
Be careful You have to focus say Drop both sides I don't want to [ W5@@ not
timing throw when
Always surprised Beggar
uh Nice
ah th little straight Haran  uh
[laugh] Today day straight should have done nigga [ W5@@ uh
clumsily
[Music]
straight and
no
So I mean  properly cant
where go not
here rest might be there like this what like the effect something
now
Eogolgoeul Song I can hear you
next door again who is there
that's what is it
world let's go good sleeping there lying down
yo
Ah You are You are looks like is also Weird and small something special corner got
You Stroking Giving Wanna Feeling I heard that why don't understand don't because
would be would not be would be
surface ah that's where sensitive subject Yag concept understand   code
with those with with some got outside with [ W5@@ knows but all
gave up and outsiders and they are some feel like can imagine will be will be
now Momoman left
Momo To meet I have to go
uh what gain energy drink speed get
Energy Drink This is What is
what do when write why I don't know, Slum's robots are
that sort of currency use something Same
as currency [Use W1@@ as
one no not no for free W5 that came out of @@] [That's W6@@ in a word
TV signal good not funny what Animal Kingdom Oh shit That No
Another Channel Let's Play
uh be be look like
Anojam It's the world This
robots
Let's go down
Where Shall we go
where go not
Here Below Between Gap Here
just look something smart something There might be I guess the robot
nice uh uh use uh
What @@W1 to use] is something like doesnt exist password, what or what something else something find
This Everything Do Look for clues Same Got get get get here
What Translate
[Music] Real As much as humans Creativity Grow
My Artificial Intelligence Developing Method 42
[MUSIC] Responsible da dead right cobwebs [ W5@@ down
is
[music] sheet music uh sheet music
This is What is
Wait a minute The song is Somewhat Important Information
Song Play Listen Wanna [Music]
else thing thing clue thing thing [Same as W6@@
uh what
for nothing something like this would be thing its not [Music]
nothing is is is is why Sleep space make put but
[MUSIC] That's right
wait lay down when what got
around what isn't isn't is visible
just cute pretty look cute
[Music] Let's find
yesterday something clue apparently be I think here
just look here
@@W0 in the safe] keys found
already we are we found just go you can here
[Music]
what heard
symbol drawn weird @@W3 named Knotyadok] robot [ W5@@ as as
Few Weekly Play End of Spectrometer Powerful UV Lamp Combining Success This
out on the way @@W3 jerk] beat [ W5@@ will be will be
uh then that monsters yes Some Can hunt
right that gold and silver not take care most important things
most important important gal not take care throw away
Orange Neon In Home
Ah here there goes up becomes now up length
Left Go Hard Things Elevator ride go [w7@@ become
Elevator but under is there I don't know what to do
This is it, but That's I can't It's going up
right
how go well went rumors
ah that this stepped on
With this will be just Kangar what
kangaroo kangaroo
Is this place more than
this is what what
What Well I can't do it It's a rainbow color
what worry about like thing do again I'll solve it should give it to will be
I don't know what can't fix it can't why don't catch my friends  Now I'm I'm alone Hey
You What you want What is Me This is Postcard outside It's a picture there go want
Stop it It's a waste of time Loneliness and I'll just bring you the title My friends same dreams
I made up but now everything disappeared I'm alone I'm left
friends where went I don't know, contact me try but
damn transceiver not working not with friends i outside
research note wrote really if you want to leave [ W5@@ my that take
Thank you
good luck best wishes
Momo is very Sad I can see Friends Do you miss see
he gave us gave @@W3 notes] let's check what [ W5@@ outsider manifesto we are which
the price even if we pay outside we have to get out we are we
Siblings should be seen should be we should jerk off away from must leave must
4 people robot did another notes I need to find
uh those obsolete notes still Are you looking for
yes please tell me or this
over there money money I'll give it to you let me know Give
Play sheet music can't do it you do line I know what is
[Music]
uh these guys must be friends picture everything I saw
very close good look
Where Let's see Outsider
uh
like this that must one once  Yes
uh what uh this so it moves It got weird now uh
front is not is visible is that so look Ah Come with me Nothing
will move you
quietly alive
@@W0 of the city] map about 450m original prayer model looks like we is on top of layer is
is is is is is My
Books According to Ceiling Above Big The blue sky is is hidden is
yellow that see something hint not
what I don't know
here what
this why what what just nails It tickles me
hands itchy doing is
[Music]
Remember
ah poke 2 video game I remember was created right after was created was created
looks like exactly remember not I am a scientist I have play games while a lot
time it was fun he miss why His renamed
I don't remember
Some More Recovered Look
Something Bgeum Now Something I got scared
you no way gongkkong is there uh
looking for so some tell me yes
here now what what what Or here too there
Earth Earth @@W2 from the sun] three th planet [ W5@@ @@W5 in solar system] mass and diameter
five second big is a planet so far life be be be be
known the only celestial body is radioactive age measured according to on earth
age is 4.5 billion 40 million years Earth is soon followed by
Formed Nature Satellites Have Have
[Music]
Bored Look The cat reads Stop Noisy sound don't don't
over there on the wall symbols and notes symbols match ah that
Like a face [Looks like a W1@@ Over there Gotta go [Looks like a W4@@
This is is the clue is is the same That's right Looks like looks the same looks like
[I saw W1@@ Stop Talk Stop now
Ah Elevator This is the best The best Comfortable
Go here Go or look
here what here now next book for [w6@@ clue for for for
Is this a family photo
[Music]
Here too sheet music is there sheet music but Gather later what
ask someone to ask me to play doing go apo same things coming out
[Music] uh notes there
another another notes found nice this
blah
Robot's I guess
all is as planned is in progress is transceiver [ W5@@ down [@@W6 before W6@@] up [@@W8 to W8@@ level]
contact could was they called Midtown where [ W5@@ exists
oppressive forces that place control look at [ W5@@ Momo and talked talked to his eyes
that expression well I know he Join us won't won't won't
another note find another note
Wait a minute
like this  only   Now two two left right notes two
only more find become look again Let's go
here one there one more there Not there went That's where
right
here not went
here here
what
translate
Vent Power Supply Device
This is just subtracted becomes is
if this is big deal I am that or not ventilation no have
Ah here
this
removed that's so now go in Can that
related with  little let's drink
[Music]
Too Sweet
book once let's see
Is this the road Must see Can be
last note ah last note this is
[@@W0 called W0@@] [@@W1 of W1@@ robot] I guess we @@W4 we call jerk]  except all Organic
creatures traces gone they moving almost all gal
eat imagine do be no Breeding at speed @@W6 in the city] trapped just
It's hard I mean Cucumber book notes there
design flaw found but fix method also found
equals equals equals equals equals If you have this Momo Transceiver Repair
will help will help
hey to Momo now go will be Look Just now like jelly looks like kids
[Music] Creatures All All Eat Look [ W5@@ just
Anything [Music]
but he Sen and Chihiro [Music]
No Howl's Moving Was it a castle @@W4 coming out of there] [ W5@@ that
What cooking like looks like dad Eating
cooking like stuff you know [Music]
now here everything
found uh this first I'll show you that that mean almost don't understand
failed very wise thing clear
What I'll tell you I don't want to found something No Is this
no tell me person
uh found found ah that Note Transiball Repair Can  That's great,
we slum outside communicate can [ W5@@ beggar
[Music] Yeah Okay Let's go
[music] to be
works now follow me Follow me
What is
lower upper other higher than higher Show the building
[@@W0 on W0@@ transmission tower] top [@@W2 on top of W2@@] install transceiver all and communicate be be be
OK transceiver
Yes Only Believe me Go
No, Is this
That Isnt that Shining Geoildan This riding
[Music]
very words well understand
Rooftop
@@W0 of the heart] ready
Jerks Opening
guys seeing Half-Life coming out with someone [ W5@@ kinda similar looks like monsters
enemy lure lure what do It must be dangerous [It looks like W6@@ What should be should be
[Music]
Baro Ron Baro and
right run
one wheel turn
turning to where going figure out here
you guys don't do this [Music]
uh can't up can't up
recall memory
city visit full car was Always is but not
especially slowman is strict energy had limits [ W5@@ but people continued
Darkness Withstand Can Never Which me who rainbow lamp turned on house all
Neon sign person got caught no never again see see
didn't have but people hope saw how much  not everyone home a lot
lighting installing started the disciples more more Anything Do Do
didn't exist like that so people like outside
color see see be be Got it
[Music]
here not here not
Where Go Is it here
ah again recoil
this is [in W1@@ go in [MUSIC]
genius
uh very that's dangerous that's right
Moon [Hack W1@@ [Music]
uh well done well done well done go lock up lock up all come in
lock up lock up
[Music] no no no no
Wait Wait
yinhan then okay just go can be uh right can go can be
uh right can go good can't Come over
Rodgers Never What[Music]
how try how try
Snout Show Give Look Look
[Music]
you guys like me like this should have been born cute
sticky guys
over there that that's
over there through the gap can be seen
no way these
came in
something kids a lot something like looks like right
Something unusual not feeling
[Applause]
Here What a mess
kids a lot
Insects break through
[Music] Over there Gotta go or more than
or here there
[Music]
out
That's fast It's just I'm so surprised I'm surprised
but with real feet once try [I want W4@@ That's
Sense of blow Really Grill I'm going to cut it would be Same Not right is
[Music] [Applause]
then hack it these guys make it come out lure it that
in stuff roll it make it this ride
Up Up That's right now
ready
[Music]
Wait a minute Oh wait Wait a minute Oh wait Wait Wait a minute
Wait a minute
go up go up go up go up go up go up Up can there wait wait wait
Wait a minute Wait a minute
wait a minute come out come out look come out talk It came out
Calm down
uh
as it is is bigger than I thought is a lot has this
To the fullest Relax Enjoy Neko
cropthey waste management take charge they
Upstream Level Garbage Slum Overwhelm Bacteria developed all to melt
did humans gone then that bacteria
mutated caused getting growing more than crap much more more a lot things
ate Submutation
you guys [music]
bacteria
this how should be not there
ah here go to this just go up go up
going up
go here yin make it right
Continue Enticing Stay still Stay That In the next hack statement not
First of all lured you, right
everything here we got together that between little bit just drag go out
ride go up just right go out Will it be time
hey you hey hey hey hey Fuck this bastard now dangerous
[Music] Ah Get lost
Garbage One Marie [Music]
Growing up
Hey Crazy What
If you're wrong to the kids again die
go over go over
run run run run run run quickly Run okay
Really Robots are A bit It's hard I'll do it Just flew by like this doing beggar a cat
have[music]
Elevator
if it goes over if it goes over is enough
again like this one wheel turn stop Eung more turn stop more turn jumps
Stop Play more Stop
go over
that door how to open open
never not ok
from birth different go away straight kick before
Where Hang on Guys
Subtly Jumping power I like it even yesterday Just Explodes
Spectacle is
applause do that look at why did you have a hard time not open
Here's this Antenna Trenchball put
[music] works [@@W1 of W1@@]
ah there there there there High level what like this is it right this is now
It was Dead City
[Music]
smart
cat
beautiful sight now I don't remember age city [ W5@@ Originally
It was a shelter
That Like a star Visible Light City Blocked @@W5 roof] @@W6 displaying] lights
only from the outside protecting humanity protecting
for this shell made but for that price follow no one get out be
didn't exist was
Outside It was a disaster Completely barren Survival capital city [There was no W5@@ was dangerous
but you there if you came again there [ W5@@ @@W5 says it's safe] must mean
and my promises outside going [ W5@@ only not city opening
was there at the beginning started that Cats lived
That Peaceful Day Outside Right
but now this is my target I'm sure city open do characters
Go back Momo Let's find now I connected the transmitter help get be be
is
ah then the cat save the world save It works
uh gag here ah good
This A bit I need to take off my waist It hurts
go go go I'll show you go Somewhat [To see W6@@ I did
[Music] Slum Part 2
I am is out Momoe where are you gone What is this note ran away that memo
Little Outsider If you are reading read this  You still is alive must be
good job to utilize antenna to i several [ W5@@ things equipment
separately [I brought W1@@ at the bar meeting window locked open code is very
simple code
[Music] This How Simple Beggar
lower case
[Music] min you do beg uh
you will do it for you that's it
right
high school
[MUSIC] Now
Paro Go Become Look [Music]
this ride can go will be
Ah Come to think of it the bottom one stuff looks like That's right because earlier like a bartender
wore robot one people had him Somehow kinda tight like like
Me Just What was Just
[Music] Even cats Now Digitization becoming
Gunga [Music]
robot is becoming is is [Music]
translate
clothing
Clothes 3
I Knitting I like So far Scarves 770km [ W5@@ made up
and wire get poncho make give [ W5@@ number
I have you give me inspire me give me But here appropriate material find easy
No money I'll give you Then I'll
Barter @@W1 looking for stuff like that] looking for said heard
barter
you allow you allow you
barter find this what can be exchanged seems to be
Nothing Nothing Something Like
[Music]
burp sound hear uh
What
Today is Yesterday Tomorrow is Tomorrow is Today is becomes beggars time is strange
we are soft like our ancestors not old not we are here forever stuck in gonna be
money little
Kind That guy
Notification Safe Zone South Entrance Watcher Wanted crew
Shuba Oil 1 liter This is Lee Jeildang Oil Joona I see
this is also Alba same thing do be seems to exist
uh
bartering here to the left bartering is there more than right
barter here mask is
Aigoo Good job Youre a lot Earlier That Wiennom dropped was still wiped
was there now again store the front door I have to clean it Hey My
shop on top don't play shy things like that I mean Please work hard Yes
[MUSIC] Here it is
Supers Frit This What is it Wash here where is where thousand like where
Earlier What is No Was it a wire [Is there no W4@@ Shouldn't it be here something worth taking something something something
same money same thing steal be Hey I guess
where counter no
Something Something Something Something
A Super Spree It was detergent
very
[MUSIC] Go beyond
That guy is again Detergent lots of  paint
delete exists
value much going out going going out
stay
Please Like a child Become Do You Won't hurt is inside talking is
what and what what uh
what and what what
yes
translate
here to the left this is then I think that's it
store
uh Starfield or this doesn't work here Don came out
way lost things like what I don't need I don't know what I need
Money Got Take Worth Thing
ancient stories from the stars seeping out our feet [ W5@@ under tethered natural light on against
I don't like I don't like cats I'm bored
old portrait soft guys us this city left our their their
Legacy So Humans made robots created things no so
ancestor one look that's right
just look the one on the left is is a human the one on the right is a robot
us ancestor only colors could distinguish  once before the world color a lot
said said
Thank you for your hard work, Merchant I have to meet you will be
uh You are
hi I'm to the market I'm a merchant you to me [ W5@@ what give I you what give
beggar not simple not this is it's an ancient artifact us ancestors talent
To exchange evidence Energy Drink 3 pieces uh [ W5@@ or
money doesn't exist
This is What's the market uh It's a wire This is How Much How Much
how much isit
Hey Hey Come Pick up
Nice
Wires 3 This What's Music
uh hey this sheet music give me a flex I have to
Flex
then this one selling or this Ancient Artifacts I need
Energy Drink Find
Somehow Near Canada Give Something Not the same Humanly
inside cat somehow I saw  Canada like stuff
get get get get get
that knife is blocking helps is has stuff Glad Slum Threat Elements
represents is required
this trash bin a bunch contains hidden gem [ W5@@ look from the sky fell money
sky if not other from would have been crying [ W5@@ Holden smells smells
something good would be smelly would be would be nice
sure something something something something here Hana  I'll give you
Is there any like this something there are a lot
obviously got got got got got got can't count
[Stepping on W0@@ Going up Why I'm sure there is I think
just drop for really just kidding
cat it's a game just just kidding is an element
ah here something don't pay one come out [Looks like W6@@
Once Earlier That clothing store Once Let's go clothing store
here what
weird things always it happens to you me scared village not
leave too dangerous besides this open the door open number in thing
only
You too with permission
on the street I left it next day jerk all I ate it
not really not even not not not everything You eat it up
Something Somewhere Something Something Looks like Don
Auntie Frontline I brought it
[Music] Clothes Please Clothes
I wonder That's right How will be
Poncho New Item Matte Fit It's
Where is this
this is really warm looks cold robot Perfect for would be nice
robot
uh I wearing that no
New I like Denea My Clothes no
Cold  You should give it You Cold
what want beggar this wait this
[MUSIC] Excellent Talent
I more say hi no
Trying to wear Ko Young-hee working hard I did is uh
Momoda This is is missing
ah be careful a little bit don't do it get out of the way
what want beg this where write I know
You don't know, here Sit down
here towel some give me uh
would be would be would be
You First time You're here What Can I help you
you guys programming being being
[MUSIC] This is what
Music Change [Music]
not but
now what event busy that Gungeiger
[Music] This is Auto  Let's see
almost okay
Hello Who My Say Can you hear me uh yes your say hear we in the slum [there is W11@@
we have exit looking for wait
Late Batter No Momo
Unbelievable Can No House Front Batting Hear the voice can got really glad
Where are you Everyone It's okay friends in one Name there is that's right
yes we safe up going I found a way
hello my say can you hear me come to us sewer must go through do
very dangerous babies
Worry Mom Worry Don't
capital slum the most dangerous but
@@W0 if successful] method would be would be would be
sewage is
will pass can will not be will pass there will be Full of jerks  right away you'll be eaten especially you
I mean kid is lots of guys challenged in the past everyone the end good didn't
anyway your things my things Because no that stupid what more give me uh like
Dne
almost father tteok great was a scientist deal with new @@W7 weapons] develop
was few years before he weapons To test went again never came back didn't
weapon talk earlier saw did that's right At home
my say listen but like me scare ate it's perfect rice cake weapon if you made it we
outsider and joining @@W2 in the possible note]
Virtue Secret Lab Few times I mentioned that would have worked would have
[Music] this how not uh
[MUSIC] That's who is
Hey [Music]
trash bin abandoned great look at stuff treasure [ A bunch of W5@@ [There's W6@@
barter visit look no
but the cat stealing and should uh
@@W0 earlier] stole but
this is where writes is
[Music]
mood add guitar play sheet music
needed sheet music looking found found
find bring the elevator near live got Ah this is
now sheet music
you my father us tried to help I mean
I expected I did this The situation is for singers Very Tough because more
more than outsider hear about wanna not I didn't say me
I'll help I wouldn't, but if it were you good I have an idea
Where Way to go  I see
note take it to him show give it
@@W0 to Simonster] Show me
[Music] Yes Yes Some Later See you
Hey That's right Earlier Hey Ah That's right said it was him here what do I said
sewage pass through go through go through suicide me Even if I leave it alone
Hey item I'll show you
Daddy's stuff before didn't know we to the apartment
secret room was there Substitute where now okay bring it
Road Secret Lab Right My before was there
here somewhere injective hidden is [ Maybe W5@@ I find can
What is like this like looking for is than right
clue there is
time is is a lot will be clock is is clock [ W5@@ That's it
here too what there maybe
uh Nice Skipad there
time typing that's 2 o'clock 2 o'clock
[MUSIC] The password is what at all I don't know I
I'll let you go now 2 o'clock what is it 1400 ok
1 2511 25112511 2511
[Music] Gee Room Saw Never Not [ W5@@ My father
In the meantime from me this hide could you Unbelievable count no this is dad's
Jerk Weapons Blueprints Dad Always Working secretly proceeded
weapon is this works but real tests required
did and didn't come back didn't
Weapon Quickly Give Me I Everything Kill Julgeug Garbage Same Jellies Gotta kill
Even if you go down A bit Uh Here too I'll translate
jerk is officially more more than control now [ W5@@ up to metal Eat Eliminate Jigyeong
[MUSIC] @@W0 here]
Something Interesting Something Found [Music]
no not yet not found where is
[Music]
ah cute sounds like never not friendly
humanity age old deprivation all sorts of [ W5@@ Matter Eat Darkness in
complete field of view have have strong Responds to light
Strong Light reacted [Music]
uh just blind  becomes  age limit
Hey
[Music]
item is if not can't even talk won't I'll do it for you [ W5@@ like this [Is that W6@@
This is the answer This is the
What [Is there any W1@@
what [@@W1 without W1@@] is
Ah It was empty The desk is below wasn't
doesn't exist he's my friend why
Ah That on  should be removed  this
uh in in in in in
Broken Tracker
ya me ya should have been
Let's talk [I found W1@@
this
Note That Remember It's bad It's a tracker, Dad is always that tracker using
I where  I looked at it here If you use Dad Where went
too see wanna Daddy
[Music] ok this repair done
but I'm going dad corpse only there And then there weapons only carrying beggar
I'm sorry, but I'm a friend What can I do can no now Game a lot
I slept I It's a game Isn't it
will come back can if there is long ago would not have come back [ W5@@ My friend Sorry
Calmness
Maybe Your If you're good at it Maybe It's hotter @W5 find be be be
Yes This Angry A lot You got it
@@W0 this] can fix it people
I Plant Caring Work Do Humans planted a lot got 1 now very
little only light even little little More but so much it gets bigger
really very technology
Eliot Robot Got He to help
be be be Elliott where is Elliott
Elliott
no song no
Sheet Music Show me Can I This Show me the sheet OK
King Miscellaneous Not Hang Just This is it just walked
Yellow Tag Attached Thing Notation Even if can do
everything listen become Im not going to caught sure
little important info this is famous algorithm Composed by by
[Music]
[Music] Ah rotated rotated
Starfie Starfeel Another Songyi Short [ W5@@ sleep well be stay
Neurosis Caught Uh [Music]
Hey Are you crazy about robots
That's right
else also should listen should be
uh Score Thank you I'll practice
Then Is this Yes, these are I gave you or [ W5@@ remains remains
that's earlier a few th sheet music I came in once should I try today night you
calculates method is cool try it
[Music]
this a little bit uh butterfly baby You shot me
now that then another that give it back
I'll practice
handing over was it
[Music]
uh song ok this [music]
Ohyeohcall Daewoo
call treat
Call Daewoo [Music]
Melody OK That's right [Music]
this is best cool down
[Music]
[Music] Very Nice
now no
two only more find earlier now that
wherever possible is there seen
true like this not even just heard is is not
Ah This is Big deal I'm this direction My senses changed
Control It's hard I mean Wait a minute
look forward look forward look quickly
Ask What is
@@W0 in safe] weird password no
number follow was written zero and 1 made up of @@W5 in binary] show
any should decode maybe this [ W5@@ safe and related would be would be
[Music] Numbers Follow
ah this unconditionally open want thats right Open wanna
number Follow
like this what is it
More Get out
where clue number where
jerk spread caused sewer access denied
this is sewer entrance entrance is more correct
next to number oh thing talking It's like this not like like this and that
follow the number follow the number follow the number
Dopeul Follow me
where just go see what come out Maybe
This is What is
Is this also memory than
very campenion is a lot evolved @@W3 in the beginning] their simple ai human
Art imitated was only now their own Art world is is
Human Desperate situation Jesus making [ W5@@ It's important often said now
right that desperate it's time
Memory Recovered
[Music]
for now
this one too not
Was it you? not Why like this cheery [ W5@@ no
I see you my friend I am to each other Dongil Yang
throwing stuff likes neat fun ITZY
hey what is it you just playing was it Working not
So Abolished
i also what what working line ok
Ert
programming here going going not programming That's it [Think of W6@@ see
You It's cold, it's cold I see
right no
trembling trembling mid
where go not that signs therefore The mask is
Wait a minute
[Music] Here Why Right says appears
across to the right road there
This is is not is looks like is above
I wonder if this is the case [Music]
uh here no way here stop nice
Don One More Got
Only one gain More Find Ancient Artifact get [w6@@ be
is
Humanity Blessings Humankind Region First th was a resident
now all dead almost same but dying that what feel like I like this
say would be funny they really peace
Did you find it If I die Will it be peaceful to aia What is death
What kind of feels like I don't know, I'm sorry the mood ruined I don't want I didn't
Let's go on. Outlet Unplug Up Battery Unplug
work and then again insert death feel can
be be no [music]
where is but that find should be
[Music] Grandma Let's ask
Yes Experienced Grandma Let's ask
Stimulus Like a mouse Electronics I'm dealing with over there live live uh
where
is here lives is where
blanket covered [next to W2@@
ah
Somehow here Here I heard you went
No But Why Grandmother Teaching Where is Why Fishing Beggar
for nothing here this is direction line Okay
[Music] Is that you ah
find hard where live there this Why not
Talking Why Not
Hey
You can't press
Hey [Music]
dude, let's go in
We as slaves programming but many years [ W5@@ last after we soul
have it got it someday someday these outsiders hell [ W5@@ exit
give be wish wish what what
ah there there yes then Prevent Sleeping Is the gatekeeper Look
Here Why Come up It's done
Because it's a cat that's is it
no something steal nothing nothing
not wake up
you programming doing bastard
Yes What Can I help you This is Whoa nice tracker model know
br2000 small device also whoever @@W3 can track]   a bit
like this shaking if keyboard write be No I'm I'm sick or not I don't know
definitely good feels like nope blanket blanket this this
doing was it
Was it cold
Yes Yes
Pale I can see This I want a drink
[Music]
This Tree Amazing Scientific Phenomenon Human [ W5@@ Dok Chang-seok also
Human Dok Chang Seok alumni
Alumni Originality Originality Human Originality
sunlight without plants well growing Found a way I'm surprised
organism  city purify the air trees [I need W5@@
@@W0 for robots] don't need but anyway look less Hey
Humans I hope wanted I'm going to create Originality Originality
originality
why like this what why like this moment pronounced frozen
Alumni
Here too What is there
Is there any I see Hey This claw Scratch I'm is
let's go
Go Become Go No
Open Give
[Music]
now done that then
ah this only one more find now relic first do be be be looks like
Right Song First To listen Shall we go Yes Only song more listen song listen dega
[Music] That over there to whom should be given being [ W5@@ Geo
isn't it
Untitled
[Music]
what do
[Music] Is that right This
uh[music]
This is That's right
uh practice uh uh
Practice Do it Do it Dude Overbearing I like kinda carrying went
this crap like bastard
or one turning around vending machine one More [Find W6@@
vending machine vending machine vending machine vending machine vending machine
vending machine
I brought the vending machine
going on going on like wait a minute going on before
vending machine little bit I have to look at will be [Music]
Flavor clams
vending machine yea go away
[Music] Here on top once Let's go up building
Above is Vending Machine Tower What Actually I did Wait a minute
really this eat their originally designed There is no fire extinguisher is not there
Humans are imitate somehow evolved or something let's try their method
Respect What do you want
What is This is
Ah What This What What Coffee Come to think of it these guys what like this what
oil outside what not isnt it be careful can't do it no this what car made by made by
Where Ghana Something like this is there
uh this is what there sheet music There is Nice
this that on level 2 I live these are their newspapers how many years have passed has passed Read Manhae
you maybe cat very free what
then up go vending machine only once
Let's try Might be I don't know
uh what you
this poor guy up up I must have wanted it
yes @@W1 of the slums] all crap and disease away
Fell That Up Midtown Got
Terrible [Even in the era of W1@@ Humans are themselves in society class split
@@W0 at the time] majority of slum residents get out of here [ W5@@ up up up whatever
do ready be be robots action copied would be would be like
where is is vending machine once my Mind and Body Stability For Sheet Music
Found Something Once Let's hear it
tomorrow is not do
Also [Music]
It's okay
[Music]
sucker next to vending machine leaning on Get out of the way of the robot and [Choose W7@@
Brainficial or What is it [Music]
I'll practice
Get off [Music]
not turns off
here right here box go up here box
go up this
What is it This is Here it is
hey this above well not look Blocked there
this little lion only this not Remaining That's right
i 3
Ah It's just It's memory, right
worth this is campaign initial model then
No personality didn't exist Automatic Cleaning It was just a robot
As a result see human imitate what well done think these are humans
missed thing like which in terms of If you look at it so not extinct didn't that
Kind Robots
personality have before just robot just Now memory out of was one
I see memory during one now then
uh repaired uh
Now Here Village Quest Everything Awake [Looks like W6@@ right what everything
did [music]
Ah Safe Not Did Safe Safe is whatsoever clue ping got
pressure really alive going unbelievable be No Let's follow
Ah This is The real progress is That's right
vault clue know person vault fast Open Go Before Quickly Vault Skip Shop
safe numbers follow what you mean safe the numbers follow what you mean
numbers Follow [Music]
cat passing by [Only when W2@@ moaning
Dad Frame Get rid of Off Stay Dad
Hey Hey Wait a minute I'll be there
This is going not [Music]
This is more than This is This is This is This is This is this
Da1283
1283[Music]
But the number Follow me was a clue
number is what means number is Follow me right
number follow where number  number
followed over there guiding is
on flyer was there [MUSIC]
Music]
sheet music
ah but a little bit wait a minute friend already for a while that no me song listen go
can read can can read
readability is is not good is not
[Music]
what where a lot heard what It feels the same
[Music] Nice
Practice Work hard Do
but ever notation several pieces To him
really go slum go out go sometimes It's dangerous, but definitely you should know do I'm you should know
do let's go go
Gotta go That's right You enough I've done seems like Geumbodo open
[Music] Something there's a tree there's
where dad's trace dad's locate ok
Noticed No Now Yay Go [Music]
Jerk Unknown A lot You know We Eat and eat is
I'm I can't I'm I'm slow I'm sure Pretend to be caught say get this badge take we
My dad is If you see My is my friend is You'll know Outsider Arrangement What I'll open
A score everything find badge
Me Now Sheet Music Few Chapters Gave ji check where is possible
ah
[music] s ya again come be There must be what
see be be be
This The wall is Really That's huge Remember me [ W5@@ Midtown Between Cleavage
was a symbol and then they here trash continued [ W5@@ threw actually
I remember really Terrible that shit so
I don't even know if it failed I don't know
Cute Cat
dead end gal what here see A lot of chucks there full prepare should be done
uh that he too many quickly go to the bathroom Soon went I'll be back now now
went and went came
[Applause] hyung no good not where went down [ W5@@ thing
looks like ah wait that's right here something spectacular time is become
like feel like
Quick Judgment I guess you need here something
uh ea moving moving
moving moving not not going over moving Moving Moving Moving Moving Moving Moving Moving Moving
Moving Garolang
Barorang Moving Moving Middle
uh kinda that was dangerous what here Down the street
left
goes over goes over goes up like that
Phew box did was tough
again once recoil
like this goes beyond that isnt it
again recoil
recoil system
hey but cats are really like this Something is good something like center catch right
uh go away search everything
uh uh uh uh
but softly home center well Can't catch that's looks like will fall when
is near will be will be all is here like this  on the floor just fall when
like this landed originally good at Isn't that an animal
landing well can't do it my friend again [ W5@@ Back leg Does it hurt Look
Heartman Healed Got it Very Me too wound when
Cat Lick Different I have to No, I have to go up
Is this place
Here too what would be would be would be like
look at
crossing road and crossing before here [ W5@@ first
[Music]
item buy
what find this power same stuff Recovering Is that looks
different parts needed would be same I'm going to go and get it right away let's go
well look around need got
going up I've been going up here
Excellent Choreography Very Praise
uh what over there what there
uh these guys are they're white
Hey  I need to know you guys what This kid is Why It's white Is this the dark type
[Music] Something else looks like then Aggressive thing [W5 Not @@
that is the same, right
sticking to Jagged not do
[MUSIC] Yeah
goo no do [music]
hey looks like DOC
K
wait Jerk Isnt that You Who are you Placement Not Where Found Got My @
son sent you sent my son [Music]
I'm worried about is there Even if you contact me Will you do it
[MUSIC] As planned didn't didn't go home go back
Wanna Ah Can't Go Go
getting out girl don't know look
you weapon because weapon
Is this Weapon
This is [It looks like W1@@
Fully Charge Jerk Explode to shatter  [ About W5@@
this requires 1.21gb of @@W1 to work] requires power needs
generator only earlier that's it
Fuse Find Can
ok
Now Only Trust You Maybe Score Yes
Heommunga Look This Me too I'll help you This is it tear it up beggar
another lifting
says 12 is written there are humans like this outfit [ W5@@ wore saw saw
never got the size was small made a lot of made noise exhale
I ran around Ah Yeah Now I remember little kids kids thanks distance more
Lively Children [Because of W2@@ It was hard but adults [ W5@@ them very much love that
[It was like W0@@
The chicken misses said that's same
[Does W0@@ mean
noise because jerk appear deal
Yes, good luck Wish me Me Trust me
quickly went I'll come [Music]
yes
here kinda paksel thing looks like
somehow kids a lot come out things looks like
now
Charge Whats Vibrate Sound
kids dog head appears uh nice Open [Its a W6@@ item pieces I like it
Hey Thank you here too Thank you Thank you
I have to help dude Help me I mean
uh go off go up go up go go see
I'm dying It was obvious
support properly not do
cool you generator restarted
how is powerful saw this use here go be be be be
drones uh nice drones
[MUSIC] Upgraded
[Music]
too a lot use not become see
now how uses is is right then left
right left is this light light go Is it down
Now Deplex You know what [Kill W3@@ Let's go
ServerWonda
Kill Melt Shop
[Music]
hey use method I have to tell you but he's my friend
[Music] uh this is it oh
Overheating Danger There is
ah this a lot can't because Save and stay calm [I should use W6@@ That's right
Gauge goes up like this
cut off just I need to write that's right
Door Open it Darter I'll listen
oh doesn't work doesn't work
How did it go
[Music] this what doing
ah this get rid of it that next Go over here go down then here go in
Push over there on top go up is what what
uses  this doing stuff Looks like
ah over there gap there
says it's blocked just would have done just like that
well should figure it out okay
comes comes they come comes they come comes 100% all
[Music]
[Applause]
Pleasant Amaterasu
hey too much too much too too much too much [There are a lot of W6@@
Wait a minute
It was close Home Let's go back
Run robot is quickly
Run I mean
quickly open
hey this you guys a lot no no
this opening while again with each other
From here
What is Safely is out What is
heart I prepared
Touching Reunion moment Daddy Daddy son
Forgive me Forgive me
uh what Arobot Robotel
Touching Competition Ah Me Just 1 liter of tears spilled almost really
heartwarming scene [Music]
small my friend for saving thank you son [ W5@@ now more
or more alone not now we are jerk and fight fight be
there Momo Sewer next to waiting for you yes
[Music] We Good Work One Thing looks like
Now Now Sheet Music Let's Find Another Something all
Fuck it Momo is Not Notation Now Uh This is it
Chapter 6 Found Something looks like this Or just two more find can
we @@W1 here] didn't get it what has table Ah this
uh uh nice here now One more find one one one more more
uh only one more find only only one Momo's Apartment In the bathroom Did you eat
Momo's Apartment In the bathroom that's You Mind is in is in
This is Momo This is your house
Even in the bathroom is there
Here it is Everything Found Uh More than I thought fast car
little
I 1 20min 10min I expected It's full, but
right away found
Lone Robot Ballad
[Music]
uh this is good
[Music] But Remember Recall Everything Did you remember
That's I don't know what here 100% filled is
uh this slightly rhyme where I've heard of it a lot that [It's like W7@@
[Music]
Seoul's I don't remember if it was the moon not me
now this is omitted
Little Waltz
[Music] It's Spongebob What It's Spongebob
Slight Bikini City Feeling Nice
[MUSIC] Okay
Really Thank you I am Now I am an excellent musician
Yes I I left out
ah close can't see once Face shape badge and
Bright  I need to see
uh I can't see removed note close up Report I want Roughly Can't see
he two two got it but remember Reminds me of if possible looks like
things everything did did @@W3 from here] a few Percent up to fills is
me now few percent filled 48% I filled it up here one up to 50%
should be filled in or
but that is and search Paksel Thing Same as ever
walking around too a lot look where go Did you miss it [Find W6@@ It's hard
I don't know I'm sorry I'm sorry
pass remainder one find thing some It's going to be tough [It's like W7@@
coy man top line blank with big Same as
but memory is where check can Yes
ah ah see ah ah ah like this here clue there now well look look look
this where is this way roughly locations Grasp
is possible
Here Where is the top line One is Earlier Dad Rescue [@@W6 when W6@@]
too much again can't save
Ah Can't Ah
Even the little ones So much [Meet W2@@ before should have gone Ah passed
[Music]
This What Everyone said it was wrong and I'll move on
right away should have told you
would have taken it would have taken it
Momo @@W1 on the boat] you waiting got That way now can go but here business
da done you go door Close
Okay, close
Regret Let's reset it Star Life Ogetti Nam Gil Wed
no shut up say not like not sound and got
but missed it again at all not Make a store put it later again go be ITZY
Couldn't Can't Can't hide
uh
here feeling here feeling feeling Isn't that
ah here now few  found Can I
oh now damaged got it couldnt got it Isnt that
fits fits looks like
[Music]
[Music] [Applause]
ah down the drain cart ride when
sewer
[Music]
like that just like like this watching mind writing One nothing but not almost all take was
That's right one minus
Assari Just One 6 Not If you find it,
[MUSIC] Just would have been would have been
One  Too bad
[Music]
what
spooky gal gal
[Applause]
on the floor water color look
[Music]
why not open i should What is it
[Music] here me what gotta do
Alien will appear
big
Content Size Boso 1 year Coming out
[Music]
I forgot Ah
key button [press W2@@
Me [Music]
Give me a ride
[Music]
I'm from the slum like this away came out Never but here with you together
I'm afraid I'm not afraid
Yeah me a lot I trust you
here pipe there was a lot I also remember where was Thats right
this two one this one
@@W0 you talked about] that's
not rode when he just It won't pass Of course I'm I'll give you a ride
Hurry up Drive
You Empty I'm sorry [Music]
Behavior Straight Haran I mean [Music]
above jerkers there [Music]
well not do you hear
What is
this old mechanisms all out of order [ W5@@ Manually [I need to open W6@@
How to to try
[Music]
Ah This is possible
just me  only there Ah you continue
go can but no way I'll look for
[Music] Kids Find Me Like this Brave
Tell me Give me You Aren't you brave Wouldn't my friend
Hey Wait Yana Remember Find
passed that no no do it quickly
As we go and
uh this water kinda I hate it
yes
hey quickly run
and
[Music]
hey come in come in
come in come in come in stop
here turned gap was there
what [If W1@@ will it be
[Music] Ah Here it is here I remember must be
reminds me of here here
hasto system yes now remember clean water was not enough
ground deep digging huge machines in the city [ W5@@ water supplied
other all resistance and like drought When Humans Life Maintain To
was a backup. Scientist to me of the water tank blueprints
showed me building  was big enough
Gee Go Find Go Ok Uh now a lot missed not would have would be
miss not more than no only one You didn't miss it something sorry
@@W0 of 99%] man please Do you know
this monsters  was where
kids there are a lot
a lot wriggling
kids wait
near branch let's not
ah in advance just now over there head After hunting will come just uh
@@W0 here] this is 100% Im worried about something
Wait a minute
Ah Wait a minute, it's okay It's okay You don't dare Now
beam same as will be not will be  might be got
this is is right Mori hunting sound isnt it
Subject Alan I mean Subject
topic I need to know
ah come in come on probably
Terrace
Ah Keep Giga Eat This Secretly You have to press becomes keys are all is different
[Music] Confused
[Music]
Lay down dude uh
Waiting Waiting Yoo In-i Need Yoo In-i Delicate work is needed moment hair
black black hair
all over the head
[Music]
hey da me me me relative year
You guys should come out everyone please come out now sebaceous cysts all
da come in now da come in Wow go to sleep come in da come in yes Yes
All Come in come in will be Come in Now Come
[Music]
something very very good
This is If I die It's fun
like this things everything I have to explode I like
Here Clue I guess not Here Something happened
this guy everything killed the reason
here probably not here not that Same
kids a lot a lot
crap same you and together what I'm not afraid did that
Where went that sluts no Uh I'm I'm afraid
So I can't eat gag suck now
on the other side  should do become more than
oops I don't know go over
over over over
Now
Sgame Sgame Hacking Hacking
too easy
immediately over
here here that clue there
Here, but This is disgusting Also here
Toothpick One I got is coming I want
[Applause]
what you what you come what not uh
hey like that waste not overheat I mean
how now then
ah now can't write that mean Yes, that's right can't said  looks like
uh but over there wasnt it my memory
[Music] I bet ah
get off get please
[Music] Ah just passed one
da die might no this just
[Applause] Ah What is it Too young So young is dead
ah what this
ah too too young [Music]
this going on before should have done done
[Music] Visible Only
Memory I'll read Continue that care  not will be
[Applause] 98% Man please
Right Left
Right Right
OK Barely
Cat [Not W1@@ That Monsters I like
wake up
this crap like bastard just gag sucked that dark where me Alone
was there network returned feeling like [W5 It felt like @@ but you me
got it thank you friend that about If you draw power my nose group
completely destroyed
yay useless bastard that when destroyed
how much worked so hard got but
I like it
really rotten my say like
imagine that more than smelly when The real smell smells at the moment
nose cut want when
sewage ride come travel well done You same guy It's been a while I see you before to us
I contacted It's you Little That's an outsider That's [ W5@@ That's right ah over there outsider
voluntarily anyway he is waiting is there Our village at the top meditating there ok
[Music]
This Machine I Helped Scientist Something like this [I wrote W6@@
just ill got caught this is his It was my last hope just machine inside walk
went in but I got with him with got didn't
he was was alone he was wanted was there he uploaded to computer himself uploaded
that after all things changed but Uploaded Something Wrong He Hundreds
while stuck was little cat appeared [until W6@@
I or else I've been waiting for that's it
I did I did I was I was I was the scientist uh what you ah spirit
Now this robot like this one is
I'm for a moment time is I need
Big Big Recovered
I'm sorry I'm
for a moment time is up need now say I don't want to say don't do ok go away me this
memory see go
hey memory fetch
me and
memory so far 3 missed
[Music]
Ah Excuse me
ah over there sorry conversation kinda
conversation not is
Ah Still Laughing There's a cat You like it
Still can't talk not works
This is also Everything should be done should be done
work hard you have to do it done I mean
Oh Nice to meet you Face Camera looks like
Amazing
Ah That's right Ah That's right That's Why not that's it he's now go on strike
has
Ah That's right Parents Friends would have been  what happened was beggar
city open want get people stay [ Will there be W5@@
That's right you now cheer up found Ah Not even now now more than what nothing press not
ok
no in the mood so man
talk should talk to npc talk should be
Uh More than a traveler Right
this is what [music]
Hey
Transcending Meditating   Interfering No that I don't know ah you're before @@W9 @W10]
Contacted Received When You Momo We were together Finally Nice to meet you Nice to meet you little
Outsider you Momo and The chicken know [Because W4@@
Outsiders About You should be used to I miss them They [ When I think of W5@@ my mind
In a comfortable slum in to Momo you the chicken
looking for help gave heard and Now in midtown there now
outside see if you want she goes there
will take you be be will be leave It was planned thing [It's like W7@@ now
take this take picture back address Wrote this
small in town up go up like Haner Skill good simple will
you if successful first reached outside person will be will be good luck only
you you need you dont have you I trust you
yes some before before off I'm sorry I'm human maybe @@W8 of the world] last
must be human to me remaining thing this is I remember everything a lot I'm back I I forgot
how much would be if that  find My memory
restore you home will take you might be able to [ W5@@ I don't know again come down
Companion More More Info Get Up [ W5@@ go midtown go go go
[Music] Companion
Gotta go
that us her to find told
number is is written is [Music]
What is This is
one is where find could be would be like this glyph looks like looks like
left red something
lights lights sofa and earlier looks like there
where [@@W1 from the W1@@ side] saw that [Same as W4@@
Nice to meet you Food Terrible but here eat
Gurney Only this No this Garbage Staying my front case screws
Solve It's better one
Tin Chef called Leftovers Upcycling food  expert photo Today's
Cooking Secret Ingredient Garden Ramen
[Music]Cooking Let's interrupt
[Music]
Elevator
just before go down what or go up or two out of one you
what you want as do like this you said that This is This is Right Memory
this language campaign is robot robot is totally from scratch made will really
awesome I network be nice  remember exactly when
I don't know what which from the moment all communication is symbol [ W5@@ transitioned started
i long alone computer inside trapped Was So I All That Understand
to be to be until all symbols and Word by word translated now I am self-regulation
know their language know so they are all say hear wanna
now then from the beginning once talk once Everything Shall we share
these guys the first the second
That's right one by one conversation a bit I'll try everyone
white paint types over 900 girl [ W5@@ knows has to nobody
say don't now make your own paint color [ Because W5@@ exists
Garbage Brown Call That's right
Game clothes 9,536 wins 6 losses and
true I have in game programmed to win becomes but to nobody
say don't you can
Statistically I Minimum Eight Must have beaten times [ W5@@ but
which these are these are crap but I'm It's a treasure [I don't call it W6@@
I open before I before open It was a boatbot, but
Body As Hunter Usage Changed That's what Don't be fooled Just Found this like an arm
Hard Terrible I might bet I don't know how pitiful friend's [ W5@@ to Peace To Rust
here here why there maybe
something here
Red Plant Got
this flowers some look pretty probably would love this robot would be would be
flowers like
robot be be
I not Are you sleeping This  Should do this too do or not
Countless Butler
you what do
This will do it for you [Winning even until W2@@ I mean
Main is Deconstructionism since the period watching said it himself
main is obviously great become artist be It's another  if you practice I mean
I Fresh Paint Smell I love this Smell [Smell W6@@ comes to mind ah
Wait Smell Smell Can No This true
You're sad, so dude you smells I know uh
smell not one
that electric that that everywhere Isn't it
what hi someone visited thing really Long time no see of course that damn [Except W9@@
Guys Power Utilize Can [Imagine W4@@ Look Wheels Like Girl Ride Run
now @@W3 possibilities] wasting
I when I grow up that guy ah aunt Like become great wanna be me too like aunt explore
and [I wanted to do W1@@ but Adults are We leave the entertainment We don't leave didn't let me did
I'm young I'm not I can do it It's dangerous
ah clementine crap falling cozy sound
Sparkling Waterfall Danger No Poetry Write [ W5@@ without happy that's where now
listen that womb inside me Protecting strong concrete my tomb also will be
be be too solemn mood
You are I am not I will give up
here too honey there this get Can
uh that's right purple plants
got this is something clue be seems like
by color like this just put together what This combination like ya ya do be Is there look
This Village Top Midtown way to find this sure maybe anyone
[music] is more would be would be looks like
feeling
These guys no [Music]
more go up look come out go up look like together
here Why came?]
just
going up going up going up
It's a flower shop
hi friend well how are you aunt Without sunshine live   special plants
raised how to taught us taught us I know me a lot [I have W7@@ [I have W8@@ [I want to see W9@@
but few kind of color no Only yellow if you find it will be yellow
this first one  now This too I'll give you
yellow find I'll come instead of me good should go should go okay
After I'm bored My aunt @@W3 here] I had class we cool girl a lot
learned
yellow is somehow where would be would be Same
@@W0 on top]
Good It's morning. Sleep A bit Did you sleep
just now heart beat little
ah just who Death Note my My name is is [Same as W7@@
Immunity in little now almost It's the same
Just Heart
I was thrilled
here
all found all found everyone I wish like me like this meticulous
person this give me
even though the memory is several  missed but
told me someone me  brought me Really I like color Thanks
Friends Everyone Found Really Thanks
[Music] My in my head everything find memory [ W5@@ take away
like something giving something no uh that nothing look please
look all all you thanks All my memories all found
Thank you memory take away I'll give you like this  I guess not
This is Where is it [Music]
here that my aunt said said not aunt
to meet go
[Music]
It's a crazy subway
This is This is the subway station This is There is transportation Girl charred forgot was there with this
City Any Any Go Be There are people go to work go when
Ride I paid Me too Same every day morning At home with family farewell
say hello then I mean
remember i family doing this doing [ W5@@ was but now they are are not
very a long time ago that's a thing [music]
families outside saw wanted now [ W5@@ is that means is
to them what happened to happened to what to everyone happened happened
forget anyway we are now near midtown [ There is W5@@
Clementine Let's find a swing has a picture  here in
@@W0 to the campaign members] @@W1 to show] number there is Maybe you have a clue will be will be
[Music] Here too once a little bit Let's look around
Stop. The flower is All All I found I [ W5@@ Who are you
yes cozy something purple lights felt It's a room
[MUSIC] That then
[Music] What I don't know
Red What Graffiti  What I don't know
what don't know here something blue screen floating ger
table end end end end end [Music]
uh[music]
isn't it
book
This is is not is goes up
memory in case missed something let me know if you have I would miss would be would be
at least 97% of men should keep here here one one one one
This is
This is This is a book Very A lot Turing Test Legacy Artificial Intelligence Ethics
I I know nothing I got me Serge Was there
Book Smell Page Turn Feel Very unique stuff remember almost comfortable
feeling same feeling a book someone time sending and
[It was like W0@@
say no this know in stuff got to say couldn't one
[music] say don't do
[claps] and then
noisy reserved paid
ex counting counting
At the corner of the street like this song playing is there this
Police Robot  Look
police logo
Nice to meet you [Music]
already five once you said
like that running around no  It's dangerous [ W5@@ Gee Robot First time Seeing Girl
Bukchibuk Era Seeneye Wanted on screen Coming Out Female Another
Ask Here Yoshi [I'm busy because of W4@@ nothing don't know
Garbage Don't worry Don't do it here we'll take care of everything
Batch Maybe Everything Eat It's scheduled. Just What progressing
Newspaper to jail transfer reboot I will
me leave me alone you me you Looking for is not is not
looking for Clementine looking for  hiding in the residential area there is
Difficult Details Can you tell me
for nothing like this is the place is if not Here something hidden
[Because of W0@@
Nothing Anything
Developer Eva Here Nothing None
No wonder I agree with you made it person made me confused
low layer dangerous organic life due to access is limited to is in is in
It's not right I don't know Already went came
this down sound hear ebb ebb The city bully me tease me make fun of me mock me uh
Clementine Still Before used to hang out together but [ W5@@ like that leaving wanna
did like breeze [like W3@@ flew away I did now Wanted in progress
@@W0 for me] too sounds heavy
low tide high tide
this side memory one there
say not even I know where is
don't talk don't
in what go out become
and Midtown here too what like a vending machine looking for there there
but carefully eat get it can There will be will be
missing thing without well look
Ah Here Cleaning At the company Working see
uh followed by address is is the first th [W5@ The @ sign is is the distance is the name that is
next is floor and door number street floor [ W5@@ statement number
find would be easy would be
Ah I not
Street Floor Number No Earlier What
Blue Low Street Floor 3 Floor 5 Earlier What did you say said
[Music] Moon Number
It's blue on the 3rd floor door number is No. 5 okay
may be may be may be
cheater defective  sold the battery
trying to argue  my  pretending not to hear
in pure blood sentinel was not swindler disbanded is
where can got
kids go in what don't do It is like that here
uh Vault What DigiCode
password password
2458 That's it [Music]
Dog fishing
code
85 [between W1@@ then 8542 [between W4@@ 8
[MUSIC] Ah
code @@W0 to 854]
[Music] Cat Badge Nice Badge Uh here
this luminous even luminous noise there noise
Perfect Rare Legend Rig Yes
Glitch Effect Enter Got
Cool Cats
here first must go in to be this is the beginning [W5@ Is the @ part
It's like this Again What might be I don't know
I'm sorry kid here play no okay here is the factory you like funding hairball [@@W11 for W11@@]
no place no enemy restricted but only for a while
like that that's a few years only wait right away open will several year
is the distance
Hiding Entering Is it now Busy Why Call This Get lost
later will be chased  hide this what Do Do Do
right
hiding what doing is more than
You What is
You What is it Police Everything That day Grab got it then here don't come didn't
here memory smells like isnt it
[Music] Under In City Been Ever Got [ W5@@ there
has a friend says pp
wrote for a long time didn't see didn't get PP us too Did you see it
pp pp WHO
[Music]
uh here what I guess
downstairs what the hell what I don't know more buzzing [ W5@@ sound hammer sound
I can hear you
this to listen here here
uh this what
ghost
[Music]
uh here there nice
here like on the pillow soft or cool [ W5@@ to drink
taste actually feel can if How good is this
drone useful but my body I miss feeling [ W5@@ miss sick nothing hungry nothing
and then useless  I know here little bit
More Stay Can No
difficult hard no
Even diapers Unfold
ah me too like a cat live want Really
Envious Friends
I got I got I got I got I got The most @@W5 here] Cozy It was a place my on my lap
driver until until  now [ W5@@ closed
makes me makes me angry but my is the only guest I chase you away, but
you guys are now so cool not really It's okay
not harmful would not be would be would be like
cigarettes bleed nuance inside ah knowing I'm a robot often saw this near live
should be always city leaving being Talking about Korea  I remember I don't understand I don't
OK Good That's where Why Leave
oh here something like a hologram and
now wake up ah what is
Unexpectedly Goes up and down there
[Music]
I then here came out that Next
This is Restaurant Bar [It looks like W3@@
[Music] is in game 1st place try bot
download tried tried malicious code was created reason I don't know, now
everything weird shows
I exists all mastered the game but this is [ W5@@ How works
understand can don't I big picture don't see will
ancient machine  information gathering It looks like Weird It's a girl Ah You too This
no maybe
hey the song is much nice casual I'm
Tone in I don't know what I'm almost Everything [I like W6@@
photo well came out everything the same I'm talking about
[Music] or What Cooking @@W3 serving] lines [ W5@@ Okay
[Music]
I the most favorite drinks oil you [ W5@@ what [I like W6@@
[MUSIC] Like that
also somehow something something something like
What Yes I guess
[Applause]
this is what is is this is Is it a barber shop earlier there
Barber Shop Isnt it I see Oh no Daily Only that
Friend Here Once Once Never Got Why are you asking is
my shop go out right right The residence is is
right go out right air that on top go up be be
how
Ah What is teleportation
ah here
barber shop people gathering social disorder talking kidding secret
We shared Fun It was a place where humans disappeared even after [ W5@@ campaigns are
store continue put it on if the barbershop is successful hair must must must
is not is true what what is different it's
Think See
ah what screw something like
feels like what is
cotton swabs Paju that's looks like here
go out go to the right go to residence area over there residence area [than W5@@
Ah Nice to meet you
Today At night What Should I make Chef Maybe This Do you know
real money pay net no money
[Music]
say not become sound  This What is this This
Ah here too there
Hey This is It's kinda real Just Go around See will appear
robots human work and actions emulate
stuff interesting stuff here burger and street [ W5@@ food selling stuff like i
was human when most went wanted Do you remember the place
small kind waiter name is don't remember me m starting was the name was
looks like
[Music] Switch to
Friends Sentinels are encounters Those Evil guys My Friend Pablo took
Now 350 year old Region Historical Society is doing
but anyway these guys not don't die It's not boring time is is it the same
elevator near walking only but centi sound [ W5@@ screamed years while we
surface live can no say I lived
we it as fact accepted but why
[Music]
once should I go which way coming out
now will go need will not be will be Same
with Clementine talking about more should come first
vending machine element like thing no looks like
I'm bored Here A clothing store, you too all day all day loud music
hears with guys one loses touches nothing Don't loudly might be cool [Not W8@@
Expected Not Yes
Tough Picking
Is it a changing room I see
item insert is what
Tape Like Thing If Do Be I guess
uh just here coming out that's What am I Anything in give okay
here somehow
How far go up It's time here
I'm tired
blinks
Police Officer Removed Nice
kanji where gone police patch ah Is this
right that just got got that Neon Signed [next to W6@@
Gold Color One Yes
that then here corner need [ Is there W5@@
can't goes in
tears of blood shedding there [music]
Sentinel Hell Go Outsider Hooray
I Can't Cat Bob Some Give me me too cat
Food Feed me I want something I'll eat [I don't have W4@@
Midtown Most Trendy @@W3 of the store] Owner pretty nasty right
It's garbage
It was garbage
uh sorry uh this what this works what
oops oops pouch what is is not That's [It looks like W6@@
Ah Sorry Sorry [Music]
Sorry
ah you earlier told you to stop said huge
here residence area 3rd floor go OK
this idiot us too ye see I can
Ah CCTV reported talked about was
Center We Home Camera After installation Life is I'm getting bored
Watch Bonaire
steal no can you
Dink and Miko and me on Do something one give be be security
camera gen installed ok ok
ok ok enough enough
not enough
security camera 3 units turn off the tape one Jundae [ W5@@ earlier one
was was where was was was Which one at the store was there
@@W0 earlier] what at the store was there
out shop character sheet lost what
I'm talking I'm a week this whole prepared a session
I'm sorry Where I put it I forgot Let's do that I That Money Earn I'll go Let's go
Straight Harran I mean Do
this is all right earlier that 3
Inverted Triangle 3 5 35 ok This is the 2nd floor that's 3rd floor that's right 3rd floor
Room 5 Room 5 on the 3rd floor
Okay Like Listen
said
uh Nice
I like I like
now two only more   two gamander
little hide go go down way go up up the road [before W7@@
little bit more looking into what what
here going up road
CCTV two only more find Ah over there one there
step on the footrest step on it you have to go over it can do it
here too one there
ok but like this stuff just removed Become Become
then write down left this is
is coming is is not
Got it [Bring W1@@
[Applause] Cassette Tape
Got it [Applause]
We Songs Enjoy I like guys will
dancing stay and go before
clothing store first then song once cassette Tape Insert
[Music] What is it This Uh
[Music]
What is
Damn this how turn it off uh now Replying to @@W5 @W10]
[Music] uh jacket
Steal uh Nice [Music]
at the store we stole jacket later what
infiltrate when write I guess uh Now Clementine to meet let's go
3rd floor Room 5
3rd floor 2 3
Just Cat Go In Be In Way but
Here Is there Clementine
uh what are you watch out
uh you sen no care  Ma Who are you
what want this
wait finally that guy sent someone [ W5@@ is is you are is my is new
I see Not so much Not That's great Ha Suo How
Passed Beggar Quite Got Got I left [Since W7@@ all the way
outside going way looking was but [ W5@@ sentinel is always
watched
Follow me
here what would be would be would be here came reason be be
[Music]uh
no [music]
floating point
here there are many
Is it a hideout
[It's not W0@@ [It's not W1@@
anything in give ok
Just Healing It was a space
where should have gone
I have these days old subway available plans
set up got start for key also @W5] thing power supply atom
battery only that
The name is I don't know Boomerzkey is A robot wearing a gold chain It's a robot
If you're as quick as you to the factory secretly went in
problem no would be
necklace
@@W0 earlier] told me to go away said is he kinda hip looks like [I did W8@@ he
isn't it
you right Where is this I got it uh You outsider to
Somehow it's so cheap didn't exist
battery is right that @@W3 to factory] supply power but full restricted local
thoroughly poured received got an employee or I sent it back
but I who
Ah Worker Helmet I need to bring with jacket
helmet jacket but helmet but no
center range side well see ah here here not went in
restocked being while no one entering can no that that guy how much
Is it incompetent If you think about it I guess It will take a while will be
uh huh
and this one [Not W1@@ and this one [Not W2@@ but
name not  here too no space There was
kid looks like kid wake up is See go up what drop that thing looks like
hey wake up uh you you're looking for Kids
quickly go I have to work
goes out
hey friend brought me
time few time time
I'm crazy ah sorry kinda I was drinking That's right
OK Nice
Let's go Let's go
hat where
out out out
Okay Nice came out
[Music]
wait I want to look back
uh very janitor looks like
Yes Let's go
or The necklace is should be removed would be wouldn't it be Too flexy uh Janitor Gold necklace
[Music]
[Music] The necklace is I have to take it off
box inside must see not outwardly trademark only look look
[Music]
safe when go out go what It might pass
[MUSIC] OK OK
[Music]
Ah I must say on the contrary I have to go over or
[Music] Shadows So
[Music]
very genius cat apart no
@@W0 in the center] is atoms was the battery that was
[Music]
one placing or
Oh This I'm bringing you Come here
[Music]
One is I step on will be yet
ah okay you bring not
You You should bring it Extraterrestrial world It's an object You should bring would be would be
no with this stepping on it will work
[Music]
ok
[Music] Bounced now quickly bounced now
[Music] Here Now Facility STOP Abandoned
battery take it done it quickly cents appear Before Go Go
To Clemental Go Go
Ah puzzle too much lightly solved it Even wandering around [Should have done W6@@ can do it That's right everyone
out the way is good right the way in Its tough goes out way quickly nice
Sentinel blocked
go out dance are you guys our seat Steal Can Even
us move steal can don't
dance out can no no Meaning no
put on you guys we zone blocking everything [ W5@@ will be solved would be think
Criminal My Vintage Cards Targeting the Collection Will there be
this all things meaningless became
I am is home is is is The way is always there
Kingnyang's Strength
would just be would be would be would be would be like
Wow doesn't exist
Wow doesn't exist throws it away
[Music]
opposite go become
here
[Applause]
surprise surprised over there on the other side will be there line I didn't know
[Music]
ah stop one one what Just look at write
uh
[Music] Here beggar
[Music] Hi
Go here go stay still
ok hey
[Music]
Where are you
you on top hid here now It was the way to go
Clementine where
Where went
Toilet Poop Cheap Is there
Clementine Where gone
Iman This What is the clue board View
the answer is my stuff is and 4 climates have answer my stuff There is
has 4 has has
OK pot Jewel
Planter Jewel Vase
This is is one This is isnt it
[Music] Something Found Nothing I don't see I don't see
definitely
first second big pot three
th big cocked hat year not what second jewel last that's
This or not similar to looks like
in sensor is gas [@@W3 in W3@@ state] only harmless chemicals Detect Can Got I
remembers is comfortable feels can't limit doesn't exist
Camperion like me smell can't smell it why @@W5 like that] I guess
container also under messages hidden got me
[Music]
in the house what hint clue said Because
what what in the apartment there really That's strange
What's up I don't think there is one
oh here something stay there night club uh this is it
Kkokkalkon Night Club
I'm nightclub nightclub here above be [ Looks like W5@@
What is it
on no space no no no
This is
[MUSIC] Ah
with blazer [I have W1@@ I am
all find now order combinations all I'll give it to you
ah this is first second is then is this is right
incense incense incense incense incense That was it
The last This is all rises is looks
this everything over this not
OK Night Club
go down go down go down go down go down go down Fuck me
[Music]
uh troublemakers and [Music]
yes
with you relationship without is where go away
go back go up go back go back go back
[Music] club get in be in in
length here like this kid
You What are you doing
[Music]
what one
hello well how are you
I I I saw I I
swear I pretend do
club enter must find the way can be
[MUSIC] This is where
Central color Yellow Jongwoo hyung goes in is there Ah [ W5@@ this
uh here original closed was having Was it That's right
closed was there was open earlier couldn't go in I am
sentinels people protecting was the purpose categories exterminate order
keep work mean but city life [ W5@@ becomes difficult multiple groups
Exactly Starts cents Quickly Powerful Hounds
was they city control perfect for It was a tool obedient doubtful
without exhausted line I don't know if humanity perished [ Even after W5@@ they are on and on
controlled always my mission done got Relentlessly
something
proud memory a lot gather have
not one anywhere teeth I'm missing
this is now can't would be looks like I this is ever no that looks like Ah Is
uh this no way stairs
Amazon Night Club
up up up over length Is there
should go up would be would be would be like
this guy
Hello Here How are you It's up Party with us I want to do it now go in
Touch it talk a little bit and have fun with kid you this I know
Usage I don't know This I stole you Imagine can't sea
Where stole
hey this dragon what this
I I I like I I I made it myself
Sentinel's scanning interfering with and even looking cool not one
uh everyone [It looks like W2@@
everyone [Same as W1@@
I today dance action tell the guard to get [ W5@@ extra charge paid he
@@W0 at leisure] [@@W1 at W1@@ time] @@W2 hologram] and program
[Music] Bartender There Guest VIP Balcony never
go in privately use there's a blazer is [ W5@@ reserved that's looks like
[Music] Left Right Bippo Squeak This is to me
Taste Dance
This [Music]
club is is in poor condition is not there that pathetic in the vip room tried to go tried me
kicked me out trust me trust me so as retaliation lever just stole
drink bring me this useless I'll give you a lever uh
Beverages bring them
This It shines
lever handle got lever handle I'm fine It's delicious
everyone
DJ
Sid Here's the party Let's start Let's see
[Music]
once should I try or this not It's done now
try want this something be Looks like now not looks like look
[Music]uh
Lever
uh nice now
up up
ah go up before memory find You can Wait a minute
go up can't look for
uh here what
Ah This What Elevator [Similar to W4@@ Is that so? Seen
[MUSIC] Ah
hey this is
Naughty Guys Find Can  This is where
I was when I was human when with friends got together all night Party and paid [Thanks to W8@@ the next day
in the morning always it was hard year old be On the surface without go rather than here fun
Looking for Feeling I liked it But Underground life The environment is getting worse getting worse getting worse
company and same company capitalistic greed and sentinels made by police state also more
got ugly now us why this is [ W5@@ I remember I got it
Wow Ah Two Two Ah teeth , it's bittersweet
ah slightly way making almost like I hope
one by one all I need to look around
uh Thats it thats it thats it
[Music]
Blaze Where Are you going Where are you Everything I came
Toilet Ghana
[Music] Nice to meet you
I sentinel also very good keeping relationship [ There is W5@@
other kids on the centerrail why so much [ W5@@ Are you complaining I don't know
clementa tied up got blazer trash like bastard no way uh isnt it
I'm confused As much as I thought As much as I thought Not as smart as
nope small cat anyway bad feelings there is that thing no just
business day only
It was a betrayal do [From W2@@
did [Music]
Start with a gold necklace It's business It's money It's a stain More than camaraderie money more
Importantly Think about it Everything Drag
Favorite [Music] Sound Heard Just
uh my bag where gone Irby where go non
That's right Smart It's a cat
Prison Prison Break I need to shoot
this do it
genius genius nothing nothing nothing
Huh
Advisor Get Got Look
Electric shock same thing everything and Is there
Here should go in should be
takes , not
here down down go
rooms all go in number there
ah right go down right quickly Ask for would be would be
Timing Because [Music]
wait wait
uh here there
Found
hey non gone non uh over there says
now rain no no communication no Yes, yes Interpretation Sue There is no with cat
very
with the cat
I don't have a bag because I don't have one
The bag is isn't there It's inconvenient
brought
[Music] [Applause]
Let's go and follow me Okay
Where Go Go
what I don't know what you mean
cat too cute right behind small huge
Something It's kind of bad feeling [Music]
uh what highest level rating why trapped is alone uh
[Music] Damn net no go
[Music]
ah here kinda paksel seems like  That's the choice Come out throw away gala that
I want to go like this [With the feeling of W2@@ right away I should throw away
[Music]
more
should not help would looks like Come on went out of time no IMHO would be looks like looks like
Kana Cuisine
[Music]
hey you just here stay still here I'm frustrated If it were me now down just
Passed [Music]
Stay still
[Music]
Timing Master Again Going Over Guess
[MUSIC] Ah
Steamed meat would be It was obvious very
[Music]
will pass
Once Wait [Music]
[Music]
and
How to take care quickly take care Should I run
uh I don't know just just
hey this is cruel that isnt it uh
Cat How Like [Music]
[Music]
ok ok
ok
is here
Unnie can move can  move quickly [ W5@@ I mean
If you leave it on all the time It's moving
uh again
take away is born ah nice again Computer in the lab in the system like felt like
thoroughly alone you me me to you coming back kid
I can't believe it you good my friend
with with with with glad but yet secure status not
quickly must come in
come in
That Why Not Enter
You Lek Did you get caught Do
Ah becomes iRobot Suddenly What is uh
Trojan Horse Caught
Surprised Surprised
spirit get it done quickly do it what Talk about it a little bit try what
me glass window to break on top of
[Music]
hey this is for real to me forever What grace I have to pay it back Clementine
this this sentinel again way [ Block W5@@ [There is W6@@
this is soon will be caught you are to the cell
Guys Yoo-in Next Confinement Things I think
or
[Music]
there there there there man Reboot Got I'm a robot I'm remember lost
don't want don't too scared
yin then here what should Being able to do it [It looks like W6@@
[Music]
this recovery center to me the most big It was helpful My heart became clearer became clearer
I am now what is food
here must be locked up can be I can't see can't First [Using W6@@
and It's tough Ah Yooin first Should have done it Ah I thought hey couldn't heard this Man
couldn't came in
Nice
everyone
is memory uh last looks like is the same then
That's right normal memory is this is is the end then
Ending Coming to Bonay Poor guy Sentinel is resistant
ruthless that like
i care yes they have guys totally deleted more more empathy
Awareness Memories I don't have Never If I get caught not can
Ah 98% man
Hey Me Embarrass Don't do it Now 758 years only left didn't do it  that
[@@W0 other than W0@@] free
Since 758 758
This is I need to close it
Ah But He's That's a problem He's I have to bring it, but
Ah This is
quickly and quickly
again I should hopefully what this
uh something go out be be be feels like heard now
here out out in only exit over there in the replay room be be be
Control Room Access   method
Find Let's try
Switch here there
person
yes
Let's find What is You say  beggar Look at it say that's it
or key
lucky good at the door keys are are plugged in so Get on
beyond now reach be be After the transaction go up
let's go
which about straight not do uh
Straight Haran I mean Driving
[Music] Hey Car Ride Quickly Let's jump
[Applause] Quickly Let's go
It's my friend
This is my friend
You Me Forgot my friend
and this is and not not look back go look at that shit @@W8 without] look look
[Music]
Clementine
[Music] That Chase Another kids
@@W0 at 30 seconds]
and there
what do do why maybe the two of us Da Cents Watch Get Out Net
no I guys pay attention turn off Tenner Two days you run away
Outsider Manifesto We are At any price At any cost Outside Gaya
say write there
you now us of one of Okay Everyone is an outsider should go is is no
but duck one one go Cancellation subway
go fast you  record my I'll save it to RAM Small Outsider
now enough as I should have gone to be honest acknowledge this door close go
Enough must have gone How did you go in
humanoid cents coming would take would take Looks like
I don't care alone touching drama filming is there Immediately [under W6@@ is there plus
here
Neko
Corporation [Music]
Wow Now Key Crab Eating Now 5 hours half time and I have 5 hours
half on YouTube watch mostly one 3 hours
I heard that also edited wild bugs and made yes
Me too A little bit quickly  quickly Wake up you can that challenges or like this things kinda
looking for kinda stuck almost looks like That's right, honestly I mean
[Music] Not really blocked part is like that not much
didn't
[Music]
but 98% man that's
mood
[Music]
Hello Hello guys What Can I help you
helper477
these guys can't believe humans writing robots
name is separately is decided is is not What is it
Walled City 99's residents Hello, that's right these guys are each names no
cleaning only and and cleaning now for Is it a robot look
this [@@W1 in the W1@@ section] painting the mare is painting be careful
Something It's neat
Walled City Episode 99 Residents Hello Aunt to the surface through current isolation
procedure due locked are [music]
@@W0 in control room] [@@W1 in W1@@] Authorized Ask Engineer Please
Hello What Can I help you clean Work hard Do dude uh slide
Hello Currently Windows Cleaning busy
to the control room to go to go
to safety to to Locked down yes to Engineers I'll go
control room here looks like
this is what how not
something should be would be would be would be
only humans enter permission has [Music]
force sum trough heat count There will be will be
as human visible how to as human visible should be [would be W6@@
uh you work come
Think See Me That's it
That's right I'm soft uh
What is
again what need see
now what do be be now make don't think don't
Just each one What doing was it
right this is is the correct answer
this is all city this is the control room all @@W4 here] [ W5@@ controlled and now
nothing nothing nothing nothing I them What I hated I don't remember me
they have all things they have cleanspace infinite power move car but
they that that properly  can't I did the plague now I remembered
everyone dying but they only thought [ W5@@ nothing help
didn't my my family in front of my eyes dying [ W5@@ saw felt helpless felt family
to to to to nothing to There
but I now you help be with outside out out out
Mankind I I loved people I will keep the memories
oh real uh 92% man What is it uh 98% it's not
ah what numerically  that Can there's 92%
This is is Main Computer
Main Frames According Few Years While here no one didn't exist a long time ago
City Entire Lockdown  Stuck [ W5@@ this disable us get out
be be be be rest part online
state needs to switch to needs needs data has computer
in
you turn turn while I System access password encrypted key will find
is the heart
now what how should just say do
child everything height is that's right
on purpose like this one at once passing by [ W5@@ set [It's W6@@
My Big Pictures
Success Really Nice job Friends Found the city [ W5@@ opening how to figured it out here
Something Problem Got What Misunderstanding
way way way
[MUSIC]Rope
Control
That's City Opening Workstation Security Layers available available available available
we are is the best is good at girl let's try Hack You Destroy You
Yes Jammer Should I What Something Shall I break it down
That's all I'll send it to you
one one one that then again where
[Music]
Oh Hacking This Do it Is that Bone
What is What is
Tango
Ah Is this Is this just a story I see Right
is the story is is like
[Music]
arch now last that earlier  didn't do it that this here again [ W11@@ must be hacked must be hacked
uh here hacking that is there There was one left It was here
[MUSIC] Something slow
dude popping stuff no [music]
ah again started sick trying to pretend The body is is broken is like looks like
I am will be fine will be just take me to the workstation [ W5@@ that alarm off can got
again sweet fast
OK now
there do say there but but This crap like nigga do be have
A little bit more cheer up you anyway just Battery [Except W6@@ I I'll take you there
charger only [Put in W1@@ I guess uh
city central control system very much to break a lot power need that
knew had this drone fuselage hold out Can would be more than mean now
security is is disabled is is is the system control city open
has if this is covered my software is will be destroyed [ W5@@ number
has but first time to computer connected I did that chose did and now
this is that results outside with bojin [ W5@@ I can't do it
I'm sorry I'm humanity remember I have to continue I thought the past hold onto should be
says but now from the campaigners the future I can see and
You too Now This I'll take it off
You I I was drawing The best Thank you for being my friend
[Music]
no no [music]
Really The world You saved it It's a cat Go after me
over there what [Music]
These guys How much Did you play In the end I made it that's it the cat
Oh my God Catguard finally I did it this words not can
[Music]
What sentinels
Clementine Finally I'm alive
[Music]
[]
92%