[W0@@ Now @@W0] [W1@@ This time @@W1] [W2@@ Welcome to the game @@W2] [W3@@ Two @@W3] [W4@@ Korun @@W4] [W5@ @Kowloon @@W5] [W6@@ Welcome to @@W6] [W7@@ that @@W7]
[W0@@ Welcome @@W0] [W1@@ Steam @@W1] [W2@@ New @@W2] [W3@@ Horror game @@W3] [W4@@ Game @@W4] [ W5@@ price is @@W5]
[W0@@ 7,800 won. Bunny's @@W0] [W1@@ Korean patch @@W1] [W2@@ receive @@W2] [W3@@ proceed @@W3]
[W0@@ @@W0] [W1@@ Game @@W1] [W2@@ Story @@W2] [W3@@ You're cheap @@W3] [W4@@ Housing @@W4] [W5@@ Find @@W5] [W6@@ @@W6] [W7@@ Kowloon @@W7]
[W0@@ @@W0 in the area] [W1@@ come @@W1] [W2@@ done @@W2] [W3@@ here @@W3] [W4@@ residents at first glance @@W4] [ W5@@ looks like @@W5] [W6@@ plain @@W6] [W7@@ like people @@W7]
[W0@@ looks like @@W0] [W1@@ more @@W1] [W2@@ depth @@W2] [W3@@ digging into @@W3] [W4@@ their real @@W4] [W5@ @ look @@W5] [W6@@ look @@W6] [W7@@ would be @@W7] [W8@@ would be @@W8]
[W0@@ says @@W0] [W1@@ then @@W1] [W2@@ right away @@W2] [W3@@ once @@W3] [W4@@ I'll try @@W4]
[W0@@ Kowloon @@W0] [W1@@ Walled City @@W1] [W2@@ Year 199 @@W2]
[W0@@ Foggy @@W0] [W1@@ Foggy @@W1] [W2@@ China @@W2] [W3@@ Khan @@W3] [W4@@ Under Population @@W4] [W5@@ most @@W5] [W6@@ many @@W6] [W7@@ city interest @@W7] [W8@@ poor and @@W8]
[W0@@ gang @@W0] [W1@@ violence @@W1] [W2@@ rampant @@W2] [W3@@ city @@W3] [W4@@ Kowloon and @@W4] [W5@@ is @@W5]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ but @@W0] [W1@@ yet @@W1] [W2@@ young @@W2] [W3@@ student @@W3] [W4@@ @@W4] [W5@@ Cheap room @@W5] [W6@@ get @@W6] [W7@@ get @@W7] [W8@@ best @@W8] [W9@@ prefer @@W9]
[W0@@ Urgent @@W0] [W1@@ It's a job @@W1]
[W0@@ but actually @@W0] [W1@@ is @@W1] [W2@@ is the place @@W2] [W3@@ look at @@W3]
[W0@@ atmosphere @@W0] [W1@@ good @@W1]
[W0@@ city @@W0] [W1@@ wall @@W1] [W2@@ inside @@W2] [W3@@ what @@W3] [W4@@ waiting for him @@W4] [W5@ @ Could it be @@W5]
[W0@@ Now @@W0] [W1@@ Now @@W1] [W2@@ Building @@W2] [W3@@ Came in @@W3] [W4@@ Quite @@W4] [W5@ @ Quality @@W5] [W6@@ I like it @@W6]
[W0@@ very @@W0] [W1@@ well @@W1] [I made W2@@ @@W2]
[W0@@ Once @@W0] [W1@@ Let's go @@W1]
[W0@@ my @@W0] [W1@@ home is @@W1] [W2@@ where is @@W2] [W3@@ but @@W3]
[W0@@ something @@W0] [W1@@ people @@W1] [W2@@ sound @@W2] [W3@@ hear @@W3]
[W0@@ what @@W0] [W1@@ party @@W1] [W2@@ are you doing @@W2]
[W0@@ Quality @@W0] [W1@@ Really @@W1] [W2@@ Nice @@W2]
[W0@@ [Music] This is @@W0] [W1@@ My @@W1] [W2@@ Is this my house @@W2]
[W0@@ here @@W0] [W1@@ not @@W1] [W2@@ that's @@W2] [W3@@ looks like @@W3]
[W0@@ Nothing @@W0] [W1@@ Anything @@W1]
[W0@@ Yeah @@W0] [W1@@ Somehow @@W1] [W2@@ Here @@W2] [W3@@ looks like @@W3] [W4@@ and here @@W4] [W5@@ Isn't that @@W5] [W6@@ I see @@W6]
[W0@@ where @@W0] [W1@@ song @@W1] [W2@@ sound @@W2] [W3@@ flows @@W3]
[W0@@ It's locked, but the key is @@W0] [Something like W1@@ @@W1] [W2@@ is needed @@W2]
[W0@@ Is this place @@W0] [W1@@ uh @@W1] [W2@@ open @@W2]
[W0@@ just @@W0] [W1@@ ghost @@W1] [W2@@ come out @@W2] [W3@@ thing @@W3] [W4@@ like @@W4]
[W0@@ This is @@W0] [W1@@ is @@W1] [W2@@ House price @@W2] [W3@@ How much is @@W3]
[W0@@ I am @@W0] [W1@@ How many @@W1] [W2@@ 10,000 won @@W2] [W3@@ One 4th floor @@W3] [W4@@ I must say @@W4] [W5@ @ 4th floor @@W5]
[W0@@ Something @@W0] [W1@@ It's ominous @@W1]
[W0@@ here @@W0] [W1@@ floor @@W1] [W2@@ what @@W2] [W3@@ guide @@W3] [W4@@ not @@W4] [W5@@ Can @@W5] [W6@@ in @@W6]
[W0@@ Something @@W0] [W1@@ But @@W1] [W2@@ Wait a minute @@W2] [W3@@ It's like this @@W3] [W4@@ Just @@W4] [W5@ @ Even if you go in @@W5] [W6@@ will be @@W6] [W7@@ will be @@W7]
[W0@@ small @@W0] [W1@@ pelvis @@W1] [W2@@ looks like @@W2] [W3@@ looks like @@W3]
[W0@@ The atmosphere is @@W0] [W1@@ It's creepy @@W1]
[W0@@ Next time @@W0] [W1@@ I need to look around @@W1]
[W0@@ Here @@W0] [W1@@ Wounded @@W1] [W2@@ blocked @@W2] [W3@@ is there @@W3]
[W0@@ where @@W0] [W1@@ dog @@W1] [W2@@ grow @@W2] [W3@@ look @@W3]
[W0@@ ah @@W0] [W1@@ somehow @@W1] [W2@@ ghost @@W2] [W3@@ come out @@W3] [W4@@ would be @@W4] [W5@@ looks like What @@W5] [W6@@ sounds like @@W6]
[W0@@ doorbell @@W0] [W1@@ sound @@W1] [W2@@ what @@W2]
[W0@@ The dog is here @@W0] [W1@@ What @@W1] [W2@@ Hani @@W2]
[W0@@ That's @@W0] [W1@@ I feel sorry for you @@W1] [W2@@ I'm hungry @@W2] [W3@@ shows @@W3]
[W0@@ I'll eat @@W0] [W1@@ I don't have one @@W1]
[W0@@ It's dark, it's locked @@W0]
[W0@@ This is @@W0] [W1@@ What is @@W1]
[W0@@ Like this @@W0] [W1@@ What's the smell @@W1] [W2@@ It's so bad @@W2]
[W0@@ Here @@W0] [W1@@ Garbage @@W1] [W2@@ Throw away @@W2] [W3@@ This is where @@W3]
[W0@@ is @@W0] [W1@@ is @@W1] [W2@@ is like this @@W2] [W3@@ crap is @@W3]
[W0@@ do well @@W0] [W1@@ do @@W1] [W2@@ ya hyung @@W2] [W3@@ eat @@W3] [W4@@ go @@W4] [W5@ @ Buy @@W5] [W6@@ I'll give you @@W6]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ why @@W0] [W1@@ like this @@W1] [W2@@ dark @@W2] [W3@@ that @@W3]
[W0@@ Here @@W0] [W1@@ Go @@W1] [W2@@ Be @@W2] [W3@@ Got @@W3]
[W0@@ here @@W0] [W1@@ power @@W1] [W2@@ like that @@W2] [W3@@ than @@W3] [W4@@ like @@W4]
[W0@@ It's okay @@W0]
[W0@@ This is @@W0] [W1@@ Why @@W1] [W2@@ like this @@W2] [W3@@ couldn't block it @@W3] [W4@@ let it go in @@W4]
[W0@@ Up @@W0] [W1@@ Going up @@W1]
[W0@@ Length @@W0] [W1@@ Blocked @@W1]
[W0@@ bug @@W0] [W1@@ sound @@W1]
[W0@@ how @@W0] [W1@@ not @@W1]
[W0@@ Is this place here @@W0]
[W0@@ this @@W0] [W1@@ open @@W1] [W2@@ immediately @@W2] [W3@@ again @@W3] [W4@@ home @@W4] [W5@@ Not @@W5] [W6@@ Tobogdo @@W6] [W7@@ format @@W7]
[W0@@ right @@W0]
[W0@@ What @@W0] [W1@@ That's what @@W1]
[W0@@ Wrong @@W0] [W1@@ Did you hear @@W1]
[W0@@ Who @@W0] [W1@@ Crying @@W1]
[W0@@ Who are you @@W0]
[W0@@ cries @@W0] [W1@@ disappeared @@W1]
[W0@@ Is this place @@W0] [W1@@ went out @@W1] [W2@@ Ohma @@W2] [W3@@ The key is @@W3] [W4@@ I left it at the store @@W4] [ W5@@ entrance @@W5] [W6@@ outside @@W6] [W7@@ be @@W7] [W8@@ be @@W8]
[W0@@ What @@W0] [W1@@ It's hard to hear @@W1] [W2@@ came up @@W2] [W3@@ uh @@W3]
[W0@@ wearing @@W0] [W1@@ outside @@W1] [W2@@ entrance @@W2] [W3@@ talking @@W3] [W4@@ going @@W4] [W5@@ Probably not @@W5] [W6@@ No way @@W6]
[W0@@ Building @@W0] [W1@@ Wearing @@W1] [W2@@ Talking @@W2] [W3@@ Is it @@W3] [W4@@ Leave it to the store @@W4] [W5 @@ I put @@W5] [W6@@ outside @@W6] [W7@@ there @@W7] [W8@@ there @@W8]
[W0@@ Somehow @@W0] [W1@@ while running @@W1]
[W0@@ again @@W0] [W1@@ sound @@W1] [W2@@ heard @@W2] [W3@@ coming @@W3] [W4@@ sound @@W4]
[W0@@ For now @@W0] [W1@@ Let's go down @@W1]
[W0@@ uh @@W0] [W1@@ why @@W1] [W2@@ energy @@W2] [W3@@ got it @@W3] [W4@@ suddenly @@W4] [W5@@ honor @@W5] [W6@@ I'm hungry @@W6] [W7@@ again @@W7]
[W0@@ I am @@W0] [W1@@ no @@W1] [W2@@ uh @@W2]
[W0@@ right @@W0]
[W0@@ like that @@W0] [W1@@ think @@W1] [W2@@ not @@W2] [W3@@ can @@W3]
[W0@@ What just @@W0] [I saw W1@@ @@W1]
[W0@@ here @@W0] [W1@@ earlier @@W1]
[W0@@ something @@W0] [W1@@ was there @@W1]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ no @@W0] [W1@@ earlier @@W1] [W2@@ here @@W2] [W3@@ like this @@W3] [W4@@ person @@W4] [W5@@ Arm like this @@W5] [W6@@ out @@W6] [W7@@ then @@W7] [W8@@ like this @@W8] [W9@@ sprout @@W9] [W10@@ disappeared @@ W10]
[W0@@ is this @@W0] [W1@@ what is it @@W1]
[W0@@ You @@W0] [W1@@ Let's go @@W1]
[W0@@ is out @@W0]
[W0@@ @@W0 more than before] [W1@@ a bit @@W1] [W2@@ louder @@W2] [W3@@ more like @@W3] [W4@@ looks like @@W4] [W5@ @ and @@W5]
[W0@@ Stay [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ landlord @@W0] [W1@@ wrote @@W1] [W2@@ wrote @@W2] [W3@@ wrote @@W3] [W4@@ shop owner @@W4] [W5 @@ Looks like @@W5]
[W0@@ key is @@W0] [W1@@ here @@W1] [W2@@ somewhere @@W2] [W3@@ should be @@W3] [W4@@ should be @@W4] [W5@@ Uh @@W5] [W6@@ dog food @@W6]
[W0@@ uh @@W0] [W1@@ feed @@W1] [W2@@ take care @@W2] [W3@@ be @@W3] [W4@@ be @@W4] [W5@@ uh @@W5] [W6@@ I @@W6] [W7@@ can give @@W7] [W8@@ @@W8] [W9@@ look @@W9]
[W0@@ but @@W0] [W1@@ like this @@W1] [W2@@ steal @@W2] [W3@@ becomes @@W3] [W4@@ get the key @@W4] [ W5@@ Once @@W5] [Let's find W6@@ @@W6]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ Ah @@W0] [W1@@ This @@W1] [W2@@ Detail @@W2] [W3@@ It's okay @@W3] [W4@@ Game @@W4] [W5@@ Hey That's @@W5] [W6@@ key @@W6]
[W0@@ I got it @@W0]
[W0@@ Let's go @@W0]
[W0@@ stay like this @@W0] [W1@@ go out @@W1] [W2@@ will be @@W2]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ what @@W0] [W1@@ ah @@W1] [W2@@ surprised @@W2] [W3@@ surprised no @@W3] [W4@@ suddenly @@W4] [W5@@ The song is @@W5]
[W0@@ Cut off @@W0] [W1@@ Noise @@W1] [W2@@ Sound @@W2] [W3@@ I heard it too @@W3] [W4@@ Immersed @@W4] [ Was there W5@@ @@W5] [W6@@ uh @@W6] [W7@@ Samchi @@W7] [W8@@ was @@W8]
[W0@@ What did you just do @@W0]
[W0@@ now @@W0] [W1@@ again @@W1] [W2@@ came in and got the key @@W2] [W3@@ got it @@W3] [W4@@ we @@W4]
[W0@@ Puppy @@W0] [W1@@ Give @@W1] [W2@@ Food @@W2] [W3@@ I got it @@W3] [W4@@ Really @@W4] [W5 @@ not @@W5] [W6@@ do @@W6] [W7@@ ah @@W7]
[W0@@ Surprise @@W0] [W1@@ I was surprised @@W1] [W2@@ What is it @@W2]
[W0@@ What is @@W0]
[W0@@ This building is @@W0] [W1@@ It's old @@W1]
[W0@@ Just @@W0] [W1@@ Ringtone @@W1] [W2@@ Doorbell @@W2]
[W0@@ waited @@W0]
[W0@@ now @@W0]
[W0@@ no @@W0] [W1@@ Eat [Music] @@W1]
[W0@@ maybe @@W0] [W1@@ don't know @@W1] [W2@@ one @@W2] [W3@@ once @@W3] [W4@@ more @@W4] [W5@@ look around Let's see @@W5]
[W0@@ Gee @@W0] [W1@@ Place @@W1] [W2@@ Original @@W2]
[W0@@ uh @@W0] [W1@@ uh @@W1] [W2@@ i @@W2] [W3@@ like this @@W3] [W4@@ statements @@W4] [W5@@ Column @@W5] [was the number of W6@@ @@W6]
[W0@@ @@W0 earlier] [W1@@ didn't @@W1] [W2@@ did you see @@W2] [W3@@ yet @@W3]
[W0@@ Here @@W0] [W1@@ goes in @@W1] [W2@@ becomes @@W2]
[W0@@ ah @@W0] [W1@@ go @@W1] [W2@@ or not @@W2]
[W0@@ something @@W0] [W1@@ close @@W1] [W2@@ go @@W2] [W3@@ sound @@W3] [W4@@ well @@W4] [W5@@ see @@W5]
[W0@@ something @@W0] [W1@@ first time @@W1] [W2@@ goes beyond @@W2] [W3@@ something @@W3] [W4@@ but @@W4]
[W0@@ people @@W0] [W1@@ sounds @@W1] [W2@@ can hear it, no matter what @@W2] [W3@@ wouldn't @@W3]
[W0@@ [Music] How @@W0] [W1@@ not @@W1]
[W0@@ One number curious @@W0]
[W0@@ [Music] No @@W0] [W1@@ No @@W1] [W2@@ No @@W2] [W3@@ No @@W3] [W4@@ No @@W4]
[W0@@ No @@W0] [W1@@ No @@W1] [W2@@ This is @@W2] [W3@@ is not @@W3] [W4@@ is @@W4] [W5@@ is the same Not @@W5] [W6@@ like @@W6] [W7@@ like @@W7]
[W0@@ what no @@W0] [W1@@ in the first place @@W1] [W2@@ going up @@W2] [W3@@ length @@W3] [W4@@ blocked @@W4] [W5@ @uh @@W5]
[W0@@ Just now @@W0] [W1@@ like this @@W1] [W2@@ I didn’t know @@W2] [W3@@ So @@W3] [W4@@ go here @@W4] [W5@ @ Go @@W5] [W6@@ say @@W6] [W7@@ that's @@W7]
[W0@@ Mood [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ now @@W0] [W1@@ well @@W1] [W2@@ came out @@W2] [W3@@ now @@W3] [W4@@ here @@W4] [W5@@ my house Is it @@W5]
[W0@@ House @@W0] [W1@@ Easyline over there @@W1]
[W0@@ Isn't It [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ That's right @@W0] [W1@@ came out @@W1] [W2@@ that's @@W2] [W3@@ that's right @@W3]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ just before @@W0] [W1@@ couldn't @@W1] [W2@@ entered @@W2] [W3@@ door @@W3] [W4@@ opened @@W4] [W5@ @ Go here @@W5] [If you go to W6@@ @@W6] [W7@@ you can @@W7]
[W0@@ [Music] now @@W0] [W1@@ home @@W1] [W2@@ here @@W2]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ The house is @@W0] [W1@@ a lot @@W1] [W2@@ How is it dark @@W2]
[W0@@ bathroom @@W0]
[W0@@ hey @@W0] [W1@@ toilet @@W1] [W2@@ this @@W2] [W3@@ on @@W3] [W4@@ in @@W4] [W5@@ stuff @@W5] [W6@@ Look @@W6]
[W0@@ Nice view @@W0] [W1@@ Nice @@W1]
[W0@@ This is the warehouse @@W0] [W1@@ Warehouse @@W1]
[W0@@ uh @@W0] [W1@@ better than I thought @@W1] [W2@@ but @@W2] [W3@@ here @@W3] [W4@@ me @@W4] [W5@@ Living alone @@W5] [W6@@ Day @@W6] [W7@@ Is that right @@W7] [W8@@ isn't it @@W8] [W9@@ with people @@W9]
[W0@@ as @@W0] [W1@@ as @@W1]
[W0@@ ah @@W0] [W1@@ landlord @@W1] [W2@@ room @@W2] [W3@@ joint @@W3] [W4@@ that @@W4] [W5@@ Maybe @@W5] [W6@@ is more correct @@W6]
[W0@@ This is @@W0] [W1@@ Now my @@W1] [W2@@ Homework @@W2] [W3@@ Capital @@W3] [W4@@ I have @@W4]
[W0@@ It's different @@W0] [W1@@ first @@W1] [W2@@ once @@W2] [W3@@ shall we go @@W3]
[W0@@ Here @@W0] [W1@@ This is the kitchen @@W1]
[W0@@ [Music] Very @@W0] [W1@@ Aged @@W1] [W2@@ Seriously @@W2]
[W0@@ Facility balcony @@W0] [W1@@ The door is @@W1] [W2@@ closed @@W2] [W3@@ says @@W3]
[W0@@ this @@W0] [W1@@ moths @@W1] [W2@@ what @@W2] [W3@@ what the hell @@W3]
[W0@@ This is @@W0] [W1@@ My @@W1] [W2@@ This is my room @@W2]
[W0@@ first @@W0] [W1@@ bed @@W1] [W2@@ on @@W2] [W3@@ load @@W3] [W4@@ put @@W4]
[W0@@ Once @@W0] [W1@@ Door @@W1] [W2@@ Let's close warm @@W2] [W3@@ Tea @@W3] [W4@@ A cup @@W4] [W5@ @ drink @@W5] [W6@@ wanna @@W6]
[W0@@ this @@W0] [W1@@ why @@W1] [W2@@ not @@W2] [W3@@ open @@W3]
[W0@@ crib @@W0] [W1@@ because @@W1] [W2@@ not @@W2] [W3@@ open @@W3] [W4@@ do @@W4]
[W0@@ blocked @@W0] [W1@@ stuff @@W1] [W2@@ looks like @@W2]
[W0@@ Once @@W0] [W1@@ Tea @@W1] [W2@@ One cup @@W2] [W3@@ Drink @@W3] [W4@@ Come @@W4]
[W0@@ here @@W0] [W1@@ go @@W1]
[W0@@ wait @@W0] [W1@@ will work @@W1]
[W0@@ Now @@W0] [W1@@ I'll eat @@W1] [W2@@ I'll give you @@W2] [W3@@ eat @@W3] [W4@@ if you want @@W4] [W5 @@ two @@W5] [W6@@ times @@W6] [W7@@ talking @@W7]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ just @@W0] [W1@@ something @@W1] [W2@@ sounds @@W2]
[W0@@ something @@W0] [W1@@ heard @@W1]
[W0@@ one shot @@W0] [W1@@ did @@W1]
[W0@@ my @@W0] [W1@@ into the room @@W1] [W2@@ let's go @@W2] [W3@@ like this @@W3] [W4@@ sound @@W4]
[W0@@ uh @@W0] [W1@@ here @@W1] [W2@@ original @@W2] [W3@@ like this @@W3] [W4@@ opened @@W4]
[W0@@ now @@W0] [W1@@ open @@W1]
[W0@@ What is it @@W0] [W1@@ I'm scared @@W1] [W2@@ Home @@W2] [W3@@ I'm going @@W3] [W4@@ I want to @@W4] [W5@ @ landlord @@W5]
[W0@@ Granny @@W0] [W1@@ Crazy @@W1] [W2@@ Like @@W2] [W3@@ Like @@W3] [W4@@ Long @@W4] [W5@@ Go outside @@W5] [W6@@ can't @@W6] [W7@@ there @@W7] [W8@@ I mean @@W8]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ here @@W0] [W1@@ what @@W1] [W2@@ are you talking about @@W2]
[W0@@ nonsense @@W0] [W1@@ not @@W1] [W2@@ ok @@W2] [W3@@ but @@W3] [W4@@ if @@W4] [W5@@ Prepare the front door @@W5] [W6@@ check @@W6] [W7@@ would @@W7] [W8@@ I wish @@W8]
[W0@@ [Music] How @@W0] [W1@@ check @@W1]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ What is @@W0]
[W0@@ here @@W0] [W1@@ impatient @@W1]
[W0@@ Hey @@W0] [W1@@ Really @@W1] [W2@@ Can't @@W2] [W3@@ Get out @@W3] [W4@@ I'm stuck @@W4]
[W0@@ [Music] How @@W0]
[W0@@ [Music] Hang @@W0] [W1@@ Lock @@W1]
[W0@@ Me @@W0] [W1@@ Here @@W1] [W2@@ Now @@W2] [W3@@ Like @@W3] [W4@@ Is [Music] @@W4]
[W0@@ how @@W0] [W1@@ not @@W1]
[W0@@ ruined @@W0] [W1@@ wrong @@W1] [W2@@ got caught @@W2]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ just saw @@W0] [W1@@ saw @@W1] [W2@@ people[music] @@W2]
[W0@@ Shh @@W0]
[W0@@ grandma @@W0] [W1@@ me @@W1] [W2@@ staring @@W2] [W3@@ was originally @@W3]
[W0@@ [MUSIC] Hey @@W0]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ at night @@W0] [W1@@ carelessly @@W1] [W2@@ outside @@W2] [W3@@ don't go out @@W3] [W4@@ stop @@W4]
[W0@@ Hey @@W0] [W1@@ I need to find the exit now @@W1] [W2@@ I need to find it @@W2] [W3@@ No @@W3] [W4@@ What is @@W4] [W5 @@ grandmother @@W5]
[W0@@ [Music] How @@W0] [W1@@ not @@W1]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ Why @@W0] [W1@@ This is @@W1] [W2@@ This is everywhere @@W2] [W3@@ Something @@W3] [W4@@ Strange @@W4] [W5@ @Now @@W5]
[W0@@ Why @@W0] [W1@@ Ask Yourself @@W1] [W2@@ Ask[Music] @@W2]
[W0@@ like this @@W0] [W1@@ door @@W1] [W2@@ opened @@W2] [W3@@ now @@W3] [W4@@ in the comic room @@W4] [W5@ @ sound @@W5] [W6@@ hear @@W6]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ stay @@W0]
[W0@@ Now @@W0] [W1@@ Taking a shower @@W1] [W2@@ Did you go in @@W2] [W3@@ Granny [Music] @@W3]
[W0@@ It's now @@W0] [W1@@ quickly @@W1] [W2@@ something @@W2] [W3@@ I need to find @@W3] [W4@@ ok @@W4]
[W0@@ I know @@W0] [W1@@ It's a big deal @@W1] [W2@@ This is here @@W2] [W3@@ Crazy @@W3]
[W0@@ Hurry up @@W0] [W1@@ Gotta get out @@W1] [W2@@ Go [Music] @@W2]
[W0@@ how @@W0] [W1@@ do [music] @@W1]
[W0@@ heart @@W0] [W1@@ ready, surprised @@W1] [W2@@ not @@W2]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ slowly slowly @@W0]
[W0@@ how @@W0] [W1@@ do [music] @@W1]
[W0@@ how @@W0]
[W0@@ Not [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ [Music] How @@W0] [W1@@ not @@W1]
[W0@@ Can't [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ Wait a minute @@W0]
[W0@@ [Music] What should I do @@W0]
[W0@@ big deal @@W0] [W1@@ happened @@W1]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ what @@W0] [W1@@ me @@W1] [W2@@ Caught @@W2] [W3@@ No way @@W3] [W4@@ Caught @@W4] [W5@@ That @@W5] [W6@@ no @@W6]
[W0@@ Aigoo @@W0]
[W0@@ Trouble @@W0]
[W0@@ What is @@W0]
[W0@@ Why @@W0] [W1@@ The door is @@W1] [W2@@ Only this @@W2] [W3@@ not @@W3] [W4@@ won't open @@W4]
[W0@@ this @@W0] [W1@@ look at @@W1] [W2@@ that's it @@W2]
[W0@@ ah @@W0] [W1@@ really @@W1]
[W0@@ how @@W0] [W1@@ this @@W1]
[W0@@ Flashlight @@W0] [W1@@ Same @@W1] [W2@@ Something @@W2] [W3@@ No @@W3] [W4@@ Too @@W4] [W5@@ Dark That's right @@W5]
[W0@@ Once @@W0] [W1@@ Around @@W1] [W2@@ Get @@W2] [W3@@ Investigate @@W3]
[W0@@ oops @@W0] [W1@@ open @@W1] [W2@@ that @@W2] [W3@@ key is @@W3] [W4@@ here @@W4] [W5@@ Is that @@W5] [W6@@ look at @@W6] [W7@@ got @@W7] [W8@@ that @@W8]
[W0@@ all @@W0] [W1@@ is here @@W1]
[W0@@ uh @@W0] [W1@@ here @@W1] [W2@@ where are you @@W2]
[W0@@ These days @@W0] [W1@@ village @@W1] [W2@@ situation @@W2] [W3@@ strange @@W3] [W4@@ like @@W4] [W5@ @ I'm in danger @@W5] [W6@@ in danger @@W6] [W7@@ that's @@W7] [W8@@ same @@W8] [W9@@ refurbishment @@W9]
[W0@@ When it's over @@W0] [W1@@ quickly @@W1] [W2@@ I'm moving @@W2] [W3@@ I have to go @@W3]
[W0@@ Who is @@W0]
[W0@@ Ah @@W0] [W1@@ Why @@W1]
[W0@@ what @@W0] [W1@@ sounds like @@W1]
[W0@@ stay @@W0]
[W0@@ What is @@W0]
[W0@@ What is @@W0] [W1@@ what the hell @@W1]
[W0@@ Refrigerator @@W0] [W1@@ Door @@W1] [W2@@ Why @@W2] [W3@@ keeps @@W3] [W4@@ open @@W4] [W5@@ closed that's @@W5]
[W0@@ It's dark @@W0] [W1@@ I can't @@W1] [W2@@ I can see @@W2]
[W0@@ here @@W0] [W1@@ now @@W1] [W2@@ go in @@W2]
[W0@@ be @@W0] [W1@@ be @@W1] [W2@@ key @@W2] [W3@@ key @@W3]
[W0@@ Ah @@W0] [W1@@ Turning back @@W1] [W2@@ too @@W2] [W3@@ I hate @@W3]
[W0@@ just saw @@W0] [W1@@ saw @@W1]
[W0@@ Kakao Talk @@W0] [W1@@ Bouncing @@W1] [W2@@ It wasn’t @@W2] [W3@@ Who @@W3] [W4@@ Everything @@W4] [W5@@ I made you look at it @@W5]
[W0@@ but @@W0] [W1@@ key @@W1] [W2@@ where @@W2] [W3@@ key @@W3]
[W0@@ It must be here @@W0]
[W0@@ lock, password @@W0] [W1@@ format @@W1] [W2@@ @@W2] [W3@@ same as @@W3]
[W0@@ Finish this @@W0]
[W0@@ now @@W0] [W1@@ we @@W1]
[W0@@ I don't know @@W0]
[W0@@ other @@W0] [W1@@ where @@W1] [W2@@ what @@W2] [W3@@ need to know @@W3] [W4@@ can be @@W4]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ Kakao Talk @@W0] [W1@@ Be careful first @@W1]
[W0@@ Ah @@W0] [W1@@ Surprise @@W1]
[W0@@ Middle @@W0] [W1@@ C Middle @@W1] [W2@@ C @@W2] [W3@@ Same @@W3] [W4@@ City @@W4]
[W0@@ this @@W0] [W1@@ behind @@W1] [W2@@ looking back @@W2] [W3@@ in the middle @@W3] [W4@@ and the rest @@W4] [ W5@@ where @@W5]
[W0@@ oxygen is @@W0] [W1@@ is @@W1] [W2@@ is @@W2]
[W0@@ ah @@W0] [W1@@ this too @@W1]
[W0@@ Just now @@W0] [W1@@ is here @@W1]
[W0@@ no @@W0] [W1@@ no @@W1]
[W0@@ yes @@W0] [W1@@ ah @@W1] [W2@@ pictures @@W2] [W3@@ single line @@W3]
[W0@@ Mr. Lee @@W0] [W1@@ Mr. Lee @@W1]
[W0@@ Hit-and-Go Pictures @@W0] [W1@@ Find @@W1] [W2@@ Can @@W2]
[W0@@ ah @@W0]
[W0@@ ding @@W0] [W1@@ CA ding @@W1] [W2@@ e @@W2] [W3@@ c @@W3] [W4@@ a @@W4]
[W0@@ Ding @@W0] [W1@@ Mr. Lee @@W1] [W2@@ a @@W2] [W3@@ yecay @@W3] [W4@@ then @@W4] [W5@@ first @@W5] [W6@@th @@W6] [W7@@ arrogant @@W7] [W8@@ find @@W8]
[W0@@ It's okay @@W0] [W1@@ remember @@W1] [W2@@ please @@W2]
[W0@@ ok @@W0] [W1@@ last @@W1] [W2@@ one @@W2]
[W0@@ here @@W0] [W1@@ one @@W1] [W2@@ maybe @@W2]
[W0@@ cover @@W0] [W1@@ one @@W1] [W2@@ where @@W2] [W3@@ is @@W3]
[W0@@ sound @@W0]
[W0@@ is @@W0] [W1@@ no @@W1] [W2@@ but @@W2] [W3@@ last @@W3] [W4@@ drawing @@W4] [W5@@ Find progress @@W5] [W6@@ can't @@W6] [W7@@ won't @@W7]
[W0@@ but @@W0] [W1@@ here @@W1] [W2@@ inside @@W2] [W3@@ I draw @@W3]
[W0@@ this is @@W0] [W1@@ earlier @@W1] [W2@@ lock @@W2] [W3@@ click @@W3] [W4@@ not @@W4] [W5 @@ That’s okay @@W5]
[W0@@ Clues @@W0] [W1@@ Everything @@W1] [W2@@ must be gathered @@W2]
[W0@@ go to @@W0] [W1@@ be @@W1] [W2@@ be @@W2] [W3@@ be @@W3]
[W0@@ bathroom @@W0] [W1@@ on the floor @@W1]
[W0@@ be @@W0] [W1@@ be @@W1] [W2@@ be @@W2]
[W0@@ This is @@W0] [W1@@ This is @@W1]
[W0@@ Substitute @@W0] [W1@@ ja @@W1] [W2@@ d @@W2]
[Let's solve W0@@ @@W0] [Let's solve W1@@ @@W1]
[W0@@ to @@W0] [W1@@ and @@W1]
[W0@@ is out @@W0] [W1@@ is out @@W1] [W2@@ is @@W2] [W3@@ is @@W3] [W4@@ is @@W4]
[W0@@ or @@W0] [W1@@ just right @@W1]
[W0@@ separately @@W0] [There is W1@@ @@W1]
[W0@@ child @@W0] [W1@@ corner @@W1] [W2@@ why @@W2] [W3@@ like this @@W3] [W4@@ scary @@W4]
[W0@@ now @@W0] [W1@@ only here @@W1] [W2@@ open @@W2] [W3@@ @@W3]
[W0@@ is here @@W0]
[W0@@ Finally, finally @@W0] [W1@@ is out @@W1]
[W0@@ now @@W0] [W1@@ get out @@W1] [W2@@ be @@W2] [W3@@ be @@W3]
[W0@@ Go @@W0] [W1@@ Go @@W1]
[W0@@ quickly @@W0] [W1@@ I have to run away @@W1] [W2@@ I can @@W2]
[W0@@ quickly @@W0]
[W0@@ Earlier @@W0] [W1@@ That @@W1] [W2@@ Puppy @@W2] [W3@@ Where @@W3] [W4@@ went @@W4] [W5@@ Eunhye @@W5] [W6@@ Pay me back @@W6] [W7@@ This @@W7] [W8@@ It's not @@W8]
[W0@@ Me @@W0] [W1@@ In crisis @@W1] [W2@@ Situation @@W2] [W3@@ Help @@W3] [W4@@ Even if the puppy survives @@W4] [W5@@ gave it to me @@W5] [W6@@ just @@W6] [W7@@ feel good @@W7] [W8@@ I like it @@W8]
[W0@@ @@W0] [W1@@ event @@W1]
[W0@@ Why @@W0] [W1@@ Why @@W1] [W2@@ Why @@W2] [W3@@ Why @@W3] [W4@@ Why @@W4] [W5@@ Why Running away @@W5] [W6@@ suddenly @@W6]
[W0@@ Suddenly @@W0] [W1@@ told me to run away @@W1] [W2@@ says @@W2] [W3@@ wait a minute @@W3] [W4@@ over @@W4] [W5@ @ uh @@W5] [W6@@ embarrassed @@W6] [W7@@ now @@W7]
[W0@@ Where @@W0] [W1@@ I have to run away @@W1] [W2@@ will be @@W2] [W3@@ I don't know @@W3] [W4@@ now @@W4] [W5@ @ @@W5] [W6@@ ran away @@W6]
[W0@@ well @@W0] [W1@@ ran away @@W1] [W2@@ go ok @@W2]
[W0@@ exit @@W0] [W1@@ way @@W1] [W2@@ no password @@W2] [W3@@ 5913 @@W3]
[W0@@ 513 @@W0]
[W0@@ Run @@W0] [W1@@ Run @@W1] [W2@@ Run @@W2]
[W0@@ uh @@W0] [W1@@ what @@W1] [W2@@ came out @@W2] [W3@@ that @@W3] [W4@@ no this @@W4] [W5@@ It's outside @@W5]
[W0@@ Weird @@W0]
[W0@@ Terrain @@W0] [W1@@ now @@W1] [W2@@ distance @@W2] [W3@@ is out @@W3] [W4@@ out of town @@W4] [W5@@ method @@W5] [W6@@ find @@W6]
[W0@@ Underground @@W0] [W1@@ Let's go here @@W1] [W2@@ not @@W2] [W3@@ @@W3] [Same as W4@@ @@W4]
[W0@@ This is @@W0] [W1@@ Hell @@W1] [It looks like W2@@ @@W2]
[W0@@ Here it is @@W0]
[W0@@ this is @@W0] [W1@@ here okay @@W1] [W2@@ please @@W2]
[W0@@ Go here @@W0] [W1@@ go in @@W1] [W2@@ just before @@W2] [W3@@ go there @@W3] [W4@@ or @@W4]
[W0@@ no @@W0] [W1@@ but @@W1] [W2@@ here @@W2] [W3@@ atmosphere @@W3] [W4@@ weird @@W4]
[W0@@ mood @@W0] [W1@@ why @@W1] [W2@@ @@W2] [W3@@ here @@W3]
[W0@@ me @@W0] [W1@@ something @@W1] [W2@@ wrong @@W2] [W3@@ came in @@W3] [W4@@ something @@W4] [W5@@ same In the first place @@W5] [W6@@ here @@W6] [W7@@ was coming @@W7] [W8@@ wasn't @@W8]
[W0@@ call @@W0] [W1@@ sound @@W1] [W2@@ what @@W2]
[W0@@ there @@W0] [W1@@ in @@W1] [W2@@ call @@W2]
[W0@@ phone @@W0] [W1@@ write @@W1] [W2@@ structure @@W2] [W3@@ must request @@W3] [W4@@ can @@W4]
[W0@@ this is @@W0] [W1@@ what exit is @@W1] [W2@@ here @@W2] [W3@@ there @@W3]
[W0@@ but @@W0] [W1@@ bought @@W1] [W2@@ string @@W2] [W3@@ find something @@W3] [W4@@ find @@W4] [W5@ @ Habolt @@W5] [W6@@ Cutter @@W6]
[W0@@ ever @@W0] [W1@@ something @@W1] [W2@@ but @@W2] [W3@@ no money @@W3] [W4@@ no lever @@W4] [W5@ @ Something like @@W5] [There's a W6@@ @@W6] [W7@@ on the vending machine @@W7]
[W0@@ flashlight @@W0] [W1@@ where @@W1] [W2@@ gone @@W2] [W3@@ go @@W3] [W4@@ that @@W4] [W5@@ uh Barely @@W5]
[W0@@ What happened yesterday @@W0] [W1@@ situation @@W1] [W2@@ Suddenly @@W2] [W3@@ Why @@W3]
[W0@@ What's up @@W0] [W1@@ flashlight @@W1] [W2@@ suddenly @@W2] [W3@@ deleted @@W3]
[W0@@ here @@W0] [W1@@ say go in @@W1] [W2@@ is @@W2]
[W0@@ scared @@W0]
[W0@@ don @@W0] [W1@@ find @@W1] [W2@@ become @@W2] [W3@@ or @@W3] [W4@@ don @@W4]
[W0@@ will not die @@W0]
[W0@@ Elevator is @@W0] [W1@@ not working @@W1] [W2@@ is not on generator @@W2] [W3@@ out of fuel @@W3] [W4@@ dropping @@W4] [W5@@ start @@W5] [W6@@ lever is @@W6]
[W0@@ Malfunction @@W0] [W1@@ Got fuel @@W1] [W2@@ Find @@W2] [W3@@ Could be @@W3] [W4@@ Lever is @@W4] [W5 @@ Earlier @@W5]
[W0@@ vending machine @@W0] [W1@@ was @@W1]
[W0@@ This is @@W0]
[W0@@ on the lever @@W0] [W1@@ gasoline lemon @@W1] [W2@@ earlier @@W2] [W3@@ saw @@W3]
[W0@@ Gasoline [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ @@W0 just now] [W1@@ in hand @@W1]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ Ah @@W0] [W1@@ outside @@W1] [W2@@ is out @@W2]
[W0@@ [MUSIC] Enclosed @@W0] [W1@@ space @@W1] [W2@@ not @@W2]
[W0@@ Ah @@W0] [W1@@ What @@W1] [W2@@ This @@W2] [W3@@ It's easy @@W3] [W4@@ now @@W4]
[W0@@ [Music] Separation @@W0] [W1@@ I don't have @@W1]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ I'll show you @@W0] [W1@@ I have @@W1] [W2@@ seesaw @@W2] [W3@@ side @@W3] [W4@@ rock @@W4] [W5@@ Check the bottom @@W5] [W6@@ look @@W6]
[W0@@ [music] seesaw @@W0] [next to W1@@ @@W1]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ It's all here @@W0]
[W0@@ Is this @@W0] [W1@@ Rock [Music] @@W1]
[W0@@ hahaha @@W0] [W1@@ now @@W1] [W2@@ red @@W2] [W3@@ to the refrigerator @@W3] [W4@@ move @@W4]
[W0@@ @@W0 with me] [W1@@ playing around @@W1] [W2@@ is that @@W2]
[W0@@ [Music] Earlier @@W0] [W1@@ That @@W1] [W2@@ It's a refrigerator @@W2]
[W0@@ Refrigerator @@W0] [W1@@ moves @@W1]
[W0@@ open [music] @@W0]
[W0@@ in the yard @@W0] [W1@@ in @@W1] [W2@@ pink @@W2] [W3@@ cloth @@W3] [W4@@ saw @@W4] [W5@@ What's behind that @@W5] [W6@@ @@W6] [W7@@ sure @@W7] [W8@@ wonder @@W8] [W9@@ not @@W9] [W10@@ in the yard @ @W10]
[W0@@@@W0] [W1@@ Pink @@W1] [W2@@ Cloth[Music] @@W2]
[W0@@ I love @@W0] [W1@@ too @@W1] [W2@@ a lot @@W2] [W3@@ just @@W3] [W4@@ too @@W4] [W5@ @ a lot @@W5] [W6@@ just @@W6]
[W0@@ was also @@W0]
[W0@@ no @@W0] [W1@@ now @@W1] [W2@@ grandma @@W2] [W3@@ isn't it @@W3]
[W0@@ Residents @@W0] [W1@@ Crazy @@W1] [W2@@ Look [Music] @@W2]
[W0@@ quickly @@W0] [W1@@ something pink @@W1] [W2@@ cloth @@W2] [W3@@ in the yard @@W3]
[W0@@ that's @@W0] [W1@@ which @@W1] [W2@@ side @@W2] [W3@@ wait @@W3] [W4@@ here @@W4]
[W0@@ only @@W0] [W1@@ once @@W1] [W2@@ just @@W2] [W3@@ look more @@W3] [W4@@ more than @@W4] [W5@ @ Ozzy @@W5] [Let's not W6@@ @@W6]
[W0@@ No way @@W0] [W1@@ Is this [Music] @@W1]
[W0@@ uh @@W0] [W1@@ what @@W1]
[W0@@ This is @@W0]
[W0@@ What @@W0] [W1@@ Hideout @@W1] [Same as W2@@ @@W2]
[W0@@ My @@W0] [W1@@ Hideout @@W1] [W2@@ Isn't it beautiful @@W2] [W3@@ Isn't it @@W3] [W4@@ I'm us @@W4] [W5 @@ Family @@W5] [W6@@ Village @@W6] [W7@@ All @@W7] [W8@@ Wake up @@W8]
[W0@@ started @@W0] [W1@@ all @@W1] [W2@@ horrendous @@W2] [W3@@ things @@W3] [W4@@ damage here @@W4] [W5 @@ Hiding @@W5] [W6@@ I've been @@W6] [W7@@ now @@W7] [W8@@ rather @@W8]
[W0@@ Kowloon @@W0] [W1@@ alive @@W1] [W2@@ no one @@W2] [W3@@ glad there's no @@W3] [W4@@ I think @@W4] [W5@@ that @@W5] [W6@@ @@W6 on coins] [W7@@ need @@W7]
[W0@@ will [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ coin @@W0]
[W0@@ Thank you @@W0]
[W0@@ Thank you [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ vending machine @@W0] [W1@@ go now @@W1]
[W0@@ Coins @@W0] [W1@@ Write @@W1] [W2@@ @@W2]
[W0@@ this is @@W0] [W1@@ what @@W1] [W2@@ is @@W2] [W3@@ is connected @@W3] [W4@@ is @@W4]
[W0@@ [Music]uh @@W0] [W1@@ Phone @@W1]
[W0@@ now @@W0] [W1@@ not @@W1] [W2@@ now @@W2]
[W0@@ Here @@W0] [W1@@ Oil @@W1] [W2@@ Same as @@W2] [W3@@ Something @@W3] [W4@@ I hope @@W4] [W5@@ Gasoline @@W5]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ just passed @@W0] [W1@@ person @@W1] [W2@@ just passed @@W2]
[W0@@ vending machine @@W0]
[W0@@ vending machine @@W0] [W1@@ go to [Music] @@W1]
[W0@@ to the vending machine @@W0] [W1@@ go to @@W1]
[W0@@ take out the lever @@W0]
[W0@@ that @@W0] [W1@@ then now @@W1]
[W0@@ [MUSIC] Gasoline @@W0] [W1@@ Find @@W1]
[W0@@ that @@W0] [W1@@ in front of @@W1] [W2@@ person @@W2] [W3@@ is near @@W3] [W4@@ go @@W4] [W5@@ Out of nowhere @@W5] [W6@@ comes out @@W6] [W7@@ like before @@W7]
[W0@@ screaming @@W0] [W1@@ screaming @@W1] [W2@@ might come running @@W2] [W3@@ I don't know @@W3] [W4@@ absolutely not @@W4] [W5 @@ Up @@W5]
[W0@@ Now @@W0] [W1@@ Heart @@W1] [W2@@ Ready @@W2]
[W0@@ ah @@W0]
[W0@@ [Music] Do @@W0] [W1@@ Just @@W1]
[W0@@ OK @@W0]
[W0@@ Once @@W0] [W1@@ Lever @@W1] [W2@@ Me @@W2] [W3@@ Looking back @@W3] [W4@@ Really @@W4] [W5@ @ No @@W5] [W6@@ please @@W6]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ Why @@W0] [W1@@ What is this @@W1] [W2@@ sounds @@W2] [W3@@ comes out @@W3] [W4@@ is @@W4] [W5@ @ background sound @@W5]
[W0@@ Here @@W0]
[W0@@ situation @@W0] [W1@@ good @@W1] [W2@@ not @@W2] [W3@@ my @@W3] [W4@@ my daughter ran away @@W4] [ W5@@ What @@W5] [W6@@ problem @@W6] [W7@@ I don't know @@W7]
[W0@@ My wife is @@W0] [W1@@ 3 days @@W1] [W2@@ during @@W2] [W3@@ in the bathtub @@W3] [W4@@ not coming out @@W4] [W5 @@ and @@W5] [W6@@ around @@W6] [W7@@ people @@W7] [W8@@ all @@W8] [W9@@ crazy @@W9]
[W0@@ how @@W0] [W1@@ should be @@W1] [W2@@ should be @@W2] [W3@@ before @@W3] [W4@@ I didn't notice @@W4] [W5@ @ @@W5 at the coronation] [W6@@ gas @@W6] [W7@@ comes out @@W7]
[W0@@ all @@W0] [W1@@ that @@W1] [W2@@ person @@W2] [W3@@ that @@W3] [W4@@ that @@W4] [W5@@ I guess Please help @@W5]
[W0@@ now @@W0] [W1@@ 100 won @@W1] [W2@@ gas @@W2] [W3@@ comes out @@W3] [W4@@ did it anytime @@W4] [ W5@@ pops out @@W5] [W6@@ pops out @@W6] [W7@@ can @@W7] [W8@@ has @@W8]
[W0@@ gas @@W0] [W1@@ sound @@W1]
[W0@@ It's okay @@W0] [W1@@ They're in the neighborhood @@W1] [W2@@ try to kick us out @@W2] [W3@@ try to kick them out @@W3] [W4@@ do @@W4]
[W0@@ the government is @@W0] [W1@@ the fact that we are @@W1] [W2@@ where @@W2] [W3@@ is dying @@W3] [W4@@ is @@W4] [W5@@ Hide @@W5] [W6@@ Hide @@W6]
[W0@@ Here @@W0] [W1@@ Gasoline @@W1] [W2@@ Got @@W2]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ [music] characters @@W0]
[W0@@ Suddenly @@W0] [W1@@ Be careful @@W1]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ not @@W0] [W1@@ That's scary @@W1]
[W0@@ not one @@W0] [W1@@ not @@W1] [W2@@ scared @@W2]
[W0@@ lever lever @@W0]
[W0@@ Oil @@W0] [W1@@ Insert Lever @@W1]
[W0@@ on @@W0]
[W0@@ Elevator @@W0] [W1@@ Working @@W1] [W2@@ Possible @@W2]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ ah @@W0] [W1@@ what @@W1]
[W0@@ once @@W0] [W1@@ came out @@W1] [W2@@ for the time being @@W2] [W3@@ again @@W3] [W4@@ won't come out @@W4]
[W0@@ Elevator @@W0] [W1@@ Like a dog @@W1] [W2@@ Scary @@W2] [Looks like W3@@ @@W3]
[W0@@ at the elevator @@W0] [W1@@ away @@W1] [W2@@ away @@W2] [W3@@ you know @@W3]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ I @@W0] [W1@@ Dreaming @@W1] [W2@@ Dreaming @@W2] [W3@@ @@W3] [W4@@ I @@W4]
[W0@@ what @@W0] [W1@@ do @@W1] [W2@@ place [music] @@W2]
[W0@@ Bolt @@W0] [W1@@ Cutter @@W1]
[W0@@ Finally, the World Cup @@W0]
[W0@@ Like this @@W0] [W1@@ Calm @@W1] [W2@@ Riga @@W2] [W3@@ What are you doing @@W3] [W4@@ atmosphere @@W4]
[W0@@ [Music] Go @@W0]
[W0@@ door @@W0] [W1@@ closed @@W1] [W2@@ when @@W2] [W3@@ what @@W3] [W4@@ cutting into @@W4] [W5 @@ do @@W5] [W6@@ do @@W6]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ now @@W0] [W1@@ now @@W1] [W2@@ bolt @@W2] [W3@@ cutter @@W3] [W4@@ write only @@W4] [W5@@ If you do @@W5] [W6@@ let's do it @@W6] [W7@@ everything @@W7] [W8@@ is here @@W8]
[W0@@ It's okay just go @@W0] [W1@@ @@W1] [W2@@ OK @@W2] [W3@@ difficult @@W3] [W4@@ that @@W4] [W5@ @ No @@W5] [W6@@ what @@W6]
[W0@@ @@W0] [W1@@ It's okay @@W1] [W2@@ Over there @@W2] [W3@@ It's a game anyway @@W3] [W4@@ It's a game @@W4]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ You @@W0] [W1@@ No way [Music] @@W1]
[W0@@ Eunhye @@W0] [W1@@ Envious @@W1] [W2@@ Goonie @@W2] [W3@@ Back @@W3] [W4@@ Well @@W4] [W5@ @ Must see @@W5] [W6@@ can @@W6]
[W0@@ Me @@W0] [W1@@ I live for you @@W1] [W2@@ Jun @@W2] [W3@@ that @@W3] [W4@@ I don't remember @@W4]
[W0@@ uh[music] @@W0]
[W0@@ look at @@W0] [W1@@ don't @@W1] [W2@@ I'm scared @@W2]
[W0@@ Finally @@W0] [W1@@ came out @@W1] [W2@@ is it @@W2]
[W0@@ joke @@W0] [W1@@ not @@W1]
[W0@@ Honey @@W0] [W1@@ What @@W1] [W2@@ Village @@W2] [W3@@ Residents @@W3] [W4@@ What @@W4] [W5@@ Why is this @@W5]
[W0@@ here @@W0] [W1@@ weird @@W1]
[W0@@ I @@W0] [W1@@ too @@W1] [W2@@ earlier @@W2]
[W0@@ [Music] Go @@W0] [W1@@ Go @@W1]
[W0@@ [Music] Gas @@W0] [W1@@ Affected @@W1] [W2@@ Received @@W2] [W3@@ So @@W3] [W4@@ Been @@W4] [W5@@ or @@W5]
[W0@@ residents @@W0]
[W0@@ Where @@W0]
[W0@@ Ah @@W0] [W1@@ Finally, finally @@W1] [W2@@ is out @@W2] [W3@@ go home @@W3] [W4@@ go @@W4] [W5@ @can @@W5] [W6@@ have @@W6]
[W0@@ Must come @@W0] [W1@@ After a while @@W1] [W2@@ Really @@W2] [W3@@ uh @@W3]
[W0@@ Quality @@W0] [W1@@ Crazy @@W1] [W2@@ Atmosphere @@W2]
[W0@@ Amazing cost performance @@W0] [W1@@ Best @@W1] [W2@@ 7,800 won @@W2] [W3@@ around @@W3]
[W0@@ Quality is @@W0]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ what is it yet @@W0] [W1@@ not over @@W1] [W2@@ not @@W2] [W3@@ is it @@W3] [W4@@ latest @@W4] [W5@@ Kowloon @@W5]
[W0@@ went to @@W0] [W1@@ from people @@W1] [W2@@ police @@W2] [W3@@ reported @@W3] [W4@@ a lot came in @@W4] [ W5@@ exists @@W5] [W6@@ these are @@W6] [W7@@ do not exist @@W7]
[W0@@ does @@W0] [W1@@ city @@W1] [W2@@ saw @@W2] [W3@@ claims 5 years @@W3] [W4@@ before @@W4] [ W5@@ Demolished @@W5] [W6@@ Kowloon @@W6] [W7@@ Walls @@W7] [W8@@ Cities are @@W8]
[W0@@ China @@W0] [W1@@ Worst @@W1] [W2@@ Cities @@W2] [W3@@ Of @@W3] [W4@@ Was One Demolition @@W4] [W5 Just before @@ @@W5] [W6@@ here @@W6] [W7@@ crime and @@W7]
[W0@@ Unsavory @@W0] [W1@@ Murder @@W1] [W2@@ cases @@W2] [W3@@ soared @@W3] [W4@@ people @@W4] [W5@@ Government @@W5] [W6@@ Kowloon @@W6] [W7@@ demolition @@W7]
[W0@@ for @@W0] [W1@@ cruel @@W1] [W2@@ means @@W2] [W3@@ mobilized @@W3] [W4@@ I believe @@W4]
[W0@@ But @@W0] [W1@@ Until the end @@W1] [W2@@ Why @@W2] [W3@@ Yes @@W3]
[W0@@ ugh @@W0] [W1@@ press @@W1] [W2@@ again @@W2] [W3@@ what @@W3] [W4@@ comes out @@W4] [W5@@ That @@W5] [W6@@ no @@W6]
[W0@@ well @@W0] [W1@@ made @@W1]
[W0@@ Really @@W0] [W1@@ Quality @@W1] [W2@@ Good atmosphere @@W2] [W3@@ Good @@W3]
[W0@@ WELCOME TO COOL @@W0] [W1@@ WELCOME TO @@W1] [W2@@ WELCOME TO @@W2] [W3@@ WELCOME TO @@W3] [W4@@ WELCOME @@W4]
[W0@@ Here @@W0] [W1@@ I'll finish @@W1] [W2@@ I like @@W2]
[W0@@ [Music] @@W0]
[W0@@ Yes @@W0] [W1@@ Ah @@W1] [W2@@ Too @@W2] [W3@@ Easy @@W3]