Now This time Welcome to the game Two Korun Kowloon Welcome to that
Welcome Steam New Horror game Game [ W5@@ price is
7,800 won. Bunny's Korean patch receive proceed
Game Story You're cheap Housing Find  Kowloon
@@W0 in the area] come done here residents at first glance [ W5@@ looks like plain like people
looks like more depth digging into their real look look would be would be
says then right away once I'll try
Kowloon Walled City Year 199
Foggy Foggy China Khan Under Population most many city interest poor and
gang violence rampant city Kowloon and is
[Music]
but yet young student  Cheap room get get best prefer
Urgent It's a job
but actually is is the place look at
atmosphere good
city wall inside what waiting for him Could it be
Now Now Building Came in Quite Quality I like it
very well [I made W2@@
Once Let's go
my home is where is but
something people sound hear
what party are you doing
Quality Really Nice
[Music] This is My Is this my house
here not that's looks like
Nothing Anything
Yeah Somehow Here looks like and here Isn't that I see
where song sound flows
It's locked, but the key is [Something like W1@@ is needed
Is this place uh open
just ghost come out thing like
This is is House price How much is
I am How many 10,000 won One 4th floor I must say 4th floor
Something It's ominous
here floor what guide not Can in
Something But Wait a minute It's like this Just Even if you go in will be will be
small pelvis looks like looks like
The atmosphere is It's creepy
Next time I need to look around
Here Wounded blocked is there
where dog grow look
ah somehow ghost come out would be looks like What sounds like
doorbell sound what
The dog is here What Hani
That's I feel sorry for you I'm hungry shows
I'll eat I don't have one
It's dark, it's locked
This is What is
Like this What's the smell It's so bad
Here Garbage Throw away This is where
is is is like this crap is
do well do ya hyung eat go Buy I'll give you
[Music]
why like this dark that
Here Go Be Got
here power like that than like
It's okay
This is Why like this couldn't block it let it go in
Up Going up
Length Blocked
bug sound
how not
Is this place here
this open immediately again home Not Tobogdo format
right
What That's what
Wrong Did you hear
Who Crying
Who are you
cries disappeared
Is this place went out Ohma The key is I left it at the store [ W5@@ entrance outside be be
What It's hard to hear came up uh
wearing outside entrance talking going Probably not No way
Building Wearing Talking Is it Leave it to the store I put outside there there
Somehow while running
again sound heard coming sound
For now Let's go down
uh why energy got it suddenly honor I'm hungry again
I am no uh
right
like that think not can
What just [I saw W1@@
here earlier
something was there
[Music]
no earlier here like this person Arm like this out then like this sprout disappeared
is this what is it
You Let's go
is out
@@W0 more than before] a bit louder more like looks like and
Stay [Music]
landlord wrote wrote wrote shop owner Looks like
key is here somewhere should be should be Uh dog food
uh feed take care be be uh I can give  look
but like this steal becomes get the key [ W5@@ Once [Let's find W6@@
[Music]
Ah This Detail It's okay Game Hey That's key
I got it
Let's go
stay like this go out will be
[Music]
what ah surprised surprised no suddenly The song is
Cut off Noise Sound I heard it too Immersed [ Was there W5@@ uh Samchi was
What did you just do
now again came in and got the key got it we
Puppy Give Food I got it Really not do ah
Surprise I was surprised What is it
What is
This building is It's old
Just Ringtone Doorbell
waited
now
no Eat [Music]
maybe don't know one once more look around Let's see
Gee Place Original
uh uh i like this statements Column [was the number of W6@@
@@W0 earlier] didn't did you see yet
Here goes in becomes
ah go or not
something close go sound well see
something first time goes beyond something but
people sounds can hear it, no matter what wouldn't
[Music] How not
One number curious
[Music] No No No No No
No No This is is not is is the same Not like like
what no in the first place going up length blocked uh
Just now like this I didn’t know So go here Go say that's
Mood [Music]
[Music]
now well came out now here my house Is it
House Easyline over there
Isn't It [Music]
That's right came out that's that's right
[Music]
just before couldn't entered door opened Go here [If you go to W6@@ you can
[Music] now home here
[Music]
The house is a lot How is it dark
bathroom
hey toilet this on in stuff Look
Nice view Nice
This is the warehouse Warehouse
uh better than I thought but here me Living alone Day Is that right isn't it with people
as as
ah landlord room joint that Maybe is more correct
This is Now my Homework Capital I have
It's different first once shall we go
Here This is the kitchen
[Music] Very Aged Seriously
Facility balcony The door is closed says
this moths what what the hell
This is My This is my room
first bed on load put
Once Door Let's close warm Tea A cup drink wanna
this why not open
crib because not open do
blocked stuff looks like
Once Tea One cup Drink Come
here go
wait will work
Now I'll eat I'll give you eat if you want two times talking
[Music]
just something sounds
something heard
one shot did
my into the room let's go like this sound
uh here original like this opened
now open
What is it I'm scared Home I'm going I want to landlord
Granny Crazy Like Like Long Go outside can't there I mean
[Music]
here what are you talking about
nonsense not ok but if Prepare the front door check would I wish
[Music] How check
[Music]
What is
here impatient
Hey Really Can't Get out I'm stuck
[Music] How
[Music] Hang Lock
Me Here Now Like Is [Music]
how not
ruined wrong got caught
[Music]
just saw saw people[music]
Shh
grandma me staring was originally
[MUSIC] Hey
[Music]
at night carelessly outside don't go out stop
Hey I need to find the exit now I need to find it No What is grandmother
[Music] How not
[Music]
Why This is This is everywhere Something Strange Now
Why Ask Yourself Ask[Music]
like this door opened now in the comic room sound hear
[Music]
stay
Now Taking a shower Did you go in Granny [Music]
It's now quickly something I need to find ok
I know It's a big deal This is here Crazy
Hurry up Gotta get out Go [Music]
how do [music]
heart ready, surprised not
[Music]
slowly slowly
how do [music]
how
Not [Music]
[Music] How not
Can't [Music]
Wait a minute
[Music] What should I do
big deal happened
[Music]
what me Caught No way Caught That no
Aigoo
Trouble
What is
Why The door is Only this not won't open
this look at that's it
ah really
how this
Flashlight Same Something No Too Dark That's right
Once Around Get Investigate
oops open that key is here Is that look at got that
all is here
uh here where are you
These days village situation strange like I'm in danger in danger that's same refurbishment
When it's over quickly I'm moving I have to go
Who is
Ah Why
what sounds like
stay
What is
What is what the hell
Refrigerator Door Why keeps open closed that's
It's dark I can't I can see
here now go in
be be key key
Ah Turning back too I hate
just saw saw
Kakao Talk Bouncing It wasn’t Who Everything I made you look at it
but key where key
It must be here
lock, password format  same as
Finish this
now we
I don't know
other where what need to know can be
[Music]
Kakao Talk Be careful first
Ah Surprise
Middle C Middle C Same City
this behind looking back in the middle and the rest [ W5@@ where
oxygen is is is
ah this too
Just now is here
no no
yes ah pictures single line
Mr. Lee Mr. Lee
Hit-and-Go Pictures Find Can
ah
ding CA ding e c a
Ding Mr. Lee a yecay then first th arrogant find
It's okay remember please
ok last one
here one maybe
cover one where is
sound
is no but last drawing Find progress can't won't
but here inside I draw
this is earlier lock click not That’s okay
Clues Everything must be gathered
go to be be be
bathroom on the floor
be be be
This is This is
Substitute ja d
[Let's solve W0@@ [Let's solve W1@@
to and
is out is out is is is
or just right
separately [There is W1@@
child corner why like this scary
now only here open
is here
Finally, finally is out
now get out be be
Go Go
quickly I have to run away I can
quickly
Earlier That Puppy Where went Eunhye Pay me back This It's not
Me In crisis Situation Help Even if the puppy survives gave it to me just feel good I like it
event
Why Why Why Why Why Why Running away suddenly
Suddenly told me to run away says wait a minute over uh embarrassed now
Where I have to run away will be I don't know now  ran away
well ran away go ok
exit way no password 5913
Run Run Run
uh what came out that no this It's outside
Weird
Terrain now distance is out out of town method find
Underground Let's go here not  [Same as W4@@
This is Hell [It looks like W2@@
Here it is
this is here okay please
Go here go in just before go there or
no but here atmosphere weird
mood why  here
me something wrong came in something same In the first place here was coming wasn't
call sound what
there in call
phone write structure must request can
this is what exit is here there
but bought string find something find Habolt Cutter
ever something but no money no lever Something like [There's a W6@@ on the vending machine
flashlight where gone go that uh Barely
What happened yesterday situation Suddenly Why
What's up flashlight suddenly deleted
here say go in is
scared
don find become or don
will not die
Elevator is not working is not on generator out of fuel dropping start lever is
Malfunction Got fuel Find Could be Lever is Earlier
vending machine was
This is
on the lever gasoline lemon earlier saw
Gasoline [Music]
@@W0 just now] in hand
[Music]
Ah outside is out
[MUSIC] Enclosed space not
Ah What This It's easy now
[Music] Separation I don't have
[Music]
I'll show you I have seesaw side rock Check the bottom look
[music] seesaw [next to W1@@
[Music]
It's all here
Is this Rock [Music]
hahaha now red to the refrigerator move
@@W0 with me] playing around is that
[Music] Earlier That It's a refrigerator
Refrigerator moves
open [music]
in the yard in pink cloth saw What's behind that  sure wonder not in the yard
Pink Cloth[Music]
I love too a lot just too a lot just
was also
no now grandma isn't it
Residents Crazy Look [Music]
quickly something pink cloth in the yard
that's which side wait here
only once just look more more than Ozzy [Let's not W6@@
No way Is this [Music]
uh what
This is
What Hideout [Same as W2@@
My Hideout Isn't it beautiful Isn't it I'm us Family Village All Wake up
started all horrendous things damage here Hiding I've been now rather
Kowloon alive no one glad there's no I think that @@W6 on coins] need
will [Music]
coin
Thank you
Thank you [Music]
vending machine go now
Coins Write
this is what is is connected is
[Music]uh Phone
now not now
Here Oil Same as Something I hope Gasoline
[Music]
just passed person just passed
vending machine
vending machine go to [Music]
to the vending machine go to
take out the lever
that then now
[MUSIC] Gasoline Find
that in front of person is near go Out of nowhere comes out like before
screaming screaming might come running I don't know absolutely not Up
Now Heart Ready
ah
[Music] Do Just
OK
Once Lever Me Looking back Really No please
[Music]
Why What is this sounds comes out is background sound
Here
situation good not my my daughter ran away [ W5@@ What problem I don't know
My wife is 3 days during in the bathtub not coming out and around people all crazy
how should be should be before I didn't notice @@W5 at the coronation] gas comes out
all that person that that I guess Please help
now 100 won gas comes out did it anytime [ W5@@ pops out pops out can has
gas sound
It's okay They're in the neighborhood try to kick us out try to kick them out do
the government is the fact that we are where is dying is Hide Hide
Here Gasoline Got
[Music]
[music] characters
Suddenly Be careful
[Music]
not That's scary
not one not scared
lever lever
Oil Insert Lever
on
Elevator Working Possible
[Music]
ah what
once came out for the time being again won't come out
Elevator Like a dog Scary [Looks like W3@@
at the elevator away away you know
[Music]
I Dreaming Dreaming  I
what do place [music]
Bolt Cutter
Finally, the World Cup
Like this Calm Riga What are you doing atmosphere
[Music] Go
door closed when what cutting into do do
[Music]
now now bolt cutter write only If you do let's do it everything is here
It's okay just go  OK difficult that No what
It's okay Over there It's a game anyway It's a game
[Music]
You No way [Music]
Eunhye Envious Goonie Back Well Must see can
Me I live for you Jun that I don't remember
uh[music]
look at don't I'm scared
Finally came out is it
joke not
Honey What Village Residents What Why is this
here weird
I too earlier
[Music] Go Go
[Music] Gas Affected Received So Been or
residents
Where
Ah Finally, finally is out go home go can have
Must come After a while Really uh
Quality Crazy Atmosphere
Amazing cost performance Best 7,800 won around
Quality is
[Music]
what is it yet not over not is it latest Kowloon
went to from people police reported a lot came in [ W5@@ exists these are do not exist
does city saw claims 5 years before [ W5@@ Demolished Kowloon Walls Cities are
China Worst Cities Of Was One Demolition [W5 Just before @@ here crime and
Unsavory Murder cases soared people Government Kowloon demolition
for cruel means mobilized I believe
But Until the end Why Yes
ugh press again what comes out That no
well made
Really Quality Good atmosphere Good
WELCOME TO COOL WELCOME TO WELCOME TO WELCOME TO WELCOME
Here I'll finish I like
[Music]
Yes Ah Too Easy