Now, this time the game is Welcome to Korun Kowloon
It's a new horror game on Steam called Welcome. The price of the game is
It is 7,800 won. I will proceed with the rabbit's Korean patch.
The story of this game is that you go to Kowloon to find cheap housing.
The residents here look like normal people at first glance.
But if you dig deeper, you will see their true face.
Well then, I'll try it right away
Kowloon Walled City 199 years
Beneath the foggy Chinese city of Cannes is the most populous city, poverty and
It is home to Kowloon, a city with rampant gang violence.
[music]
However, for young students, finding a cheap room is the first priority.
It's urgent.
But I guess it's a real place
good mood
What awaits him within the walls of the city
Now, I'm in the building. The quality is quite good.
I made it very well
let's go
where is my house
I hear some people
what party are you having
The quality is really good
[Music] Is this my home
I don't think it's here
is there anything
Yeah, somehow it seems like here, but it doesn't seem to be here either.
where does the sound of the song come from
It's locked, do you need a key or something?
Is this place open?
It looks like a ghost will come out
What is the price of a house here
I'm on the 4th floor for tens of thousands of won.
Something's on fire
There is no information about the number of floors here
Something, but the atmosphere is like this for a moment. You can just go in.
looks like a small pelvis
the atmosphere is eerie
I'll have to look around next time
The wound is blocked here too
look where the dog is
Oh, it seems like a ghost will come out. What are you talking about?
what's the doorbell sound
What is the puppy doing here
I feel sorry for him. He looks hungry.
there's nothing to eat
It's dark. It's locked.
what is this
It smells so bad
this is the garbage dump
There's a door, but there's garbage like this
Take care, I'll buy you something to eat later
[music]
why is it so dark
can i go here
It seems like this is a place like power
it's okay
Why is this place blocked like this so I can't enter?
going up
The road is blocked
bug sounds
What do we do
this is it
As soon as you open this, it's not a house again, it's a hallway again
yes
what are you talking about
did you hear wrong
who is crying
who are you
the cries are gone
Is this place gone? Oh, I left the key at the store. It will be outside the entrance.
What are you talking about?
I'm not talking about this entrance outside wearing it, no way
Are you wearing a building and talking? I left it to the store.
while going back
I heard a sound again
let's go down
Hey, why did you get your energy back?
I'm not
Right
don't think like that
what did you just see
here earlier
there was something
[music]
No, just now, a person was extending his arms like this and then he disappeared like this.
what is this
let's go out
came out
It seems to be a bit noisier than before.
Stay [Music]
It seems to be the store written in the landlord's writing
The key must be here somewhere, uh dog food
Uh, I can take care of the food, I guess I can give it to you
But you can steal it like this. Let's find the key.
[music]
Ah, this detail is ok, it's a game, it's a key
I got it
Let's go out
I can go out like this
[music]
What is it, I was surprised. No, suddenly the song
I heard noise as it cut off, but I was too immersed.
what did you just do
Well, I came back. I took the key and we
I also packed some food for the puppy. Really, don’t do that.
I'm surprised what is this
What
Because the building is old
The doorbell just rang
waited
ruler
no eat [music]
In case you don't know, let's look around one more time
this place was originally
How could I have opened the door like this?
Haven't you seen it before?
can i come in here
Oh, shouldn't I go
I'm getting close to something, so I can hear the sound
It's like going over something for the first time
You can hear people, it's nothing
[MUSIC] How do I do it
Curiosity
[Music] no no no no no
no no i don't think this is not i don't think it is
What is it? No, the way up was blocked in the first place.
I didn't do this before, but that's why I have to go here.
atmosphere [music]
[music]
Well, it came out well. Is this my house now?
that side of the house
Isn't it [music]
That's right, that's right
[music]
The door you couldn't enter earlier will open. You can go here.
[MUSIC] Now I'm home
[music]
The house is very dark
restroom
Hey, look at what's on the toilet
nice view nice
This is a warehouse. A warehouse.
Uh, it's better than I thought, but is it right for me to be alone here with people?
write together
Ah, the landlord's room is more like that, right?
This could be my home now
Shall we go somewhere else first?
here is the kitchen
[Music] Very old, really
The facility says the balcony door is closed
What the hell are these moths
this is my room
Let's put the luggage on the bed first
Let's close the door for now, I want to drink a cup of warm tea
why isn't this open
Doesn't it open because of the bed?
I think I'm stuck
Let's have a cup of tea and come
go here
You can wait
I'll let you eat now. If you want to eat, tell me twice.
[music]
just heard something
I heard something
one shot
Let's go to my room.
Uh, did it originally open like this?
now open
I'm scared of something, I want to go home, but the landlord
I think grandma is crazy. She hasn't been out for a long time.
[music]
what are you talking about here
No way, but you better check the front door just in case
[MUSIC] How to check
[music]
what
can't stand it here
Hey, I really couldn't go out, but the road was blocked.
[Music] How
[Music] Locked up
Am I here with you now [Music]
What do we do
ruined got it wrong
[music]
The One You Just Saw [Music]
Shh
Grandma was looking at me
[Music] Hey
[music]
Don't go out recklessly at night
Hey, I need to find an exit right now, no, what is it, grandma?
[MUSIC] How do I do it
[music]
Why is this happening? Something is strange everywhere right now
Ask yourself why [music]
The door opened like this, and now I can hear a sound from the comic room.
[music]
anybody home
Did you go to the shower now grandma [music]
Now is the time to find something
It was a big deal knowing this is crazy here
Gotta get out soon [Music]
how do i do it [music]
Prepare your mind, don't be surprised
[music]
slowly slowly
how do i do it [music]
how
not [music]
[MUSIC] How do I do it
can't [music]
wait for a sec
[Music] What can I do?
big trouble
[music]
What is it that I got caught?
Oh my, oh my
it's a big deal
what
Why does the door only open this way
You want me to look at this
Oh really
how is this
Is there such a thing as a flashlight? It's too dark
Do some research around
Heck, it's open. I think the key is here. I got it earlier.
I'm here
uh where are you
The situation in the village is strange these days. It seems like I am in danger.
I'm going to move soon after I'm done
who is this
Oh why
what are you talking about
anybody home
what
What
what the hell
Why does the refrigerator door keep opening and closing?
I can't see you because it's dark
now go in here
can key key
Oh, I hate turning back
just saw
It wasn't KakaoTalk that stood out because someone made everyone stare
But where is the key
I guess it's here
It's a lock, but I think it's in the form of a password
this is over
now we
I don't know
What else should I know
[music]
Be careful with KakaoTalk from the beginning
Oh surprise
Middle C, like C in the middle
If you turn this around, where is the middle of the field?
there will be oxygen
Oh this too
I just came
no big deal
Yes, the pictures are single line
Mr. Ddaeng Lee Ddaeng Lee
I need to find the paintings of Mr.
ah
Ding CA Ding eca
If you find the first one
please remember
ok last one
want to have one here
Where is the cover
sound
No, but I need to find the last picture.
But in here, I'm painting
He said the lock didn't click earlier.
Gather all the clues
can proceed
on the bathroom floor
there might be
this is this
substitute d
let's solve
Oh
I left, can I leave now?
Or right
stay apart
Why is the child's corner so scary?
Now, just open it here
I'm here
finally it finally came out
can i go now
I have to go out
I have to go
I have to run away quickly
hurry
Where did that puppy go earlier?
I gave it to the dog even if it was alive to help me in a crisis situation, but I just wanted it to feel good
event in
Why why why why why why why are you running away all of a sudden
Suddenly they tell me to run away
I don't know where to run, did you run away well now?
Did you run away okay?
There is no way out, password 5913
run run run
Uh, what's that? It's outside.
weird
It's the terrain, now that the streets are out, let's find a way to get out of town.
Let's go underground. I don't think it's here.
It looks like hell
here it is
here you come ok please
If you go in here, will you go in there?
No, but the atmosphere here is strange.
What's the atmosphere like here
I think something went wrong, I wasn't here in the first place
what's the phone call
call in there
I need to call for help on the phone
What is this? The exit is here
But I need to find something for the string I bought, the bolt cutter
I have an enemy, but I don't have money.
Where did the flashlight go?
What happened yesterday, why suddenly
What is it, the flashlight suddenly disappeared
Do you want to come in here?
scared
Should I find money? Money
die
Elevator does not workThe generator is running out of fuel and the start lever is
It's broken. Should I look for fuel? The lever was earlier.
there was a vending machine
this is it
Gasoline lemon on the lever. I saw it before.
petrol [music]
just in hand
[music]
oh i'm coming out
[Music] It's not an enclosed space
Oh well, this is easy now
[Music] Nothing special
[music]
I have something to show you, check under the rock next to the seesaw
[MUSIC] Next to the seesaw
[music]
It's all here
This Is Rock [Music]
Hahaha Now go to the red refrigerator
are you kidding me
[Music] It's that refrigerator.
refrigerator is moving
open [music]
I saw the pink cloth in the yard. I don't know what's behind it. In the yard
pink cloth [music]
Mom too much god too much god
was also
no, she's not a grandma anymore
Residents must be crazy [Music]
something soon on the pink cloth yard
Which side is it on? Wait here
Let's just take a look and don't come again
Could this be [Music]
uh what
here is
what a hideout
Isn't my hideout beautiful? I wake up my family and the whole village
I've been hiding in this place, avoiding all the terrible things that started, but now
I'm glad there's no one alive in Kowloon. I need that coin.
I'm gonna [music]
coin
thank you
thank you [music]
Go to the vending machine now
You can write a coin
What can I do here? Is this a connected place?
[MUSIC] Uh phone
not now
There's no such thing as oil here. Gasoline.
[music]
Someone just passed by
vending machine
Go to the vending machine [music]
go to vending machine
take out the lever
then now
[Music] Finding Gasoline
There's a person in front of me. If you go closer, it pops out like before.
They might come running screaming, they'll never climb
prepare your heart
ah
[Music] Say just
are you okay
First of all, Lever, I really hate looking back, please
[music]
Why is this sound coming out? The background sound
Here
Things are bad. My daughter ran away and I don't know what's wrong.
My wife hasn't gotten out of the bathtub for three days and everyone around me is crazy.
What should I do? I didn't notice it before, but gas is coming out of the gauze.
I think it's all because of him please help
Now, gas comes out of 100 won. It can pop out at any time.
gas sound
It's ok they're trying to kick us out of town
The government is hiding the fact that we are dying here
here in the gas tank
[music]
[music] Now
be careful
[music]
I'm not afraid
I'm not scared at all
lever
Add oil lever
on
Elevator can work
[music]
ah what
Once I came out, I won't come back for a while.
He looks like an elevator dog
You're far from the elevator
[music]
am i dreaming
What are you doing [music]
bolt cutter
Finally the World Cup
There's no way I could be this calm. What is this atmosphere?
[music] I'm going
When the door closes, I'm going to cut it to get out
[music]
Now all you have to do is use the bolt cutters.
It's okay, you just have to move on, there's nothing difficult
It's okay if I come out, over there, it's a game, it's a game anyway
[music]
You can't [music]
Are you envious of Eun-hye? You have to take good care of me
I remember giving you life
uh [music]
Don't look at me because I'm scared
did it finally come out
no kidding
Honey, what are the villagers, what are you doing?
it's weird here
i was too soon
[MUSIC] I gotta get out
[Music] Did it happen because of the gas?
residents
where
Ah, finally, I'm finally out, I can go home
It's been a while, really
quality crazy atmosphere
It's amazing, it's the best value for money. It's about 7,800 won.
quality is
[music]
What's not over yet? Recently in Kowloon
There are a lot of police reports coming in from people who have been there, but they don't exist.
Claims to have seen a city that does not
It was one of China's worst cities. Prior to demolition, it was home to crime and
There has also been a spike in unsavory murders. People say that the government wants to demolish Kowloon.
I believe he used cruel means to
But why are you like that until the end?
If you press this, nothing else comes out
well made
The quality was really good and the atmosphere was good.
Welcome to Cole welcomes you to Guryung
I'll finish here. Okay
[music]
yes ah so easy