Now This time Welcome to the game Too Kolun Kowloon Coming to
Welcome Steam new horror game game price
7,800 won. Rabbit's   Hangul patch   receive   to proceed
The   story of this   game is   you find   an affordable   house
The   of the region  has come  The residents of this place   look like   ordinary   people at first glance.
If you look  more  and dig deeper  , you will   see their real
Then Immediately I'll try it once
Kowloon Fortress City 199 years
Foggy fog China Khan below is the  most  city with the most population and poverty and
Gangsters violence plenty cityin Kowloon is located
[music]
However,   for   still   young   students,   finding an inexpensive room  is   the most  priority.
It's urgent
But is it actually a   place   look
atmosphere   good
In the city wall  what is   waiting for him
Now   now   the building   came in   quite   the quality is   good
I made it very   well
let's go
My   home  where is   but
I can hear something people sounds
What   party  are you doing?
Quality Really It's good
[Music] Is this   my   home?
It's like   not   here
nothing
Yeah Somehow Here It looks like   and here too   Isn't it   I see
Where does the   song  sound   come from?
It's locked, but I need a key
Is this place   uh   open
Just like a   ghost  will come out
how much is the house price
I'm   how many   10,000 won   one 4th floor   all the way   4th floor
Something   is on fire
Here   number of floors  what  guide not  available
Something   but   the atmosphere is like this for a moment   it's like this   just go in
It looks like a small pelvis
The atmosphere is   spooky
Next time   I'll have to look around
There are also   wounds   blocked
Where   dogs   grow   look
Ah   somehow   it seems like a ghost   will come out   what   is that sound
Doorbell Sound What is it?
The dog is here   what
Yeah, he's   pitiful   hungry   I can see
I have nothing to eat
It's dark. It's locked.
What is
Like this   what it smells like   it's so bad
This is the  garbage dumping  place
There is a door , but   like this   trash
Well   get by   later hyung  I'll buy you   something   to eat   I'll give it to you
[music]
Why   is this   dark
can you go  here
Here   electric power   is that a place  than   just like
it's okay
This is   why  like this   I couldn't block it   let me in
Going up
The road   is blocked
bug sound
What do we do
this is it
This open right again home not tto-hallway it's hyung
yes
What   is that
did you hear wrong
who   is crying
who are you
The cries   are gone
Is this place  out   Oma  I left the key   at the store  there will be   outside the entrance
What   is that so hard   I came up   uh
Dressed  outside entrance talking wasn't it  no way
The building wearing talking is it  leaving it to the store I put it outside it will be
Somehow   while going back
I heard the   sound  again   the coming   sound
Let's go down
Uh Why Cheer up Suddenly Ahner Because I'm hungry  Again
I'm   no   uh
Right
If you think   like that,   no  you can
what is it i just saw
here
there was something
[music]
No  before here like this someone extended like this and stayed there like this sprout disappeared
what is this
you   let's go
came out
Compared to before
Stay [Music]
It looks like   the owner of the house  and   the shopkeeper
The key is  here somewhere  it must be  uh dog food
Uh Food I can take care of it I can I can I I can give it to you I can  Look
But   like this   even if you steal it   it'll work   Let's find the key  once
[music]
Ah This Detail It's okay Game Hey it's  Key
I got it
Let's go out
I can go out like this
[music]
What is it  Ah Surprised I was surprised No Suddenly The song
As it cut off  Noise Sound I heard it, but it was so I was immersed was it  uh Samchi
what did you just do
Now  I came in again  I also got the key  and   we
I got   food for the dog  too   I really did  I don't do it   don't   ah
Surprised   I was surprised   what is it
What
The building is   old
Just   Another ringing   Doorbell
waited
ruler
no   eat [music]
Maybe   don't know  once  once  more  let's look around
This   place is   originally
How   was it   was I   able to   open the door   like this
Did you   not   see it before   yet
can I go in here
Ah   should I go   or not?
Something  is getting closer  so   the sound  look well
Something   for the first time   it's like passing
You can hear people sounds , nothing will happen
[Music] How to
Curiosity
[Music] No No No No No
No No This is  Not  It’s like  It’s not  It’s like
What is it no   in the first place   the way up   was blocked
I didn't do this   earlier   but   so   I have to go   here   it's saying
atmosphere [music]
[music]
Now  well I came out now here is this my house?
Home there Easyline
Isn't it [music]
That's right   came out   that's   that's right
[music]
I couldn't go in earlier   The door  will open  and go here   and you can
[Music] Now I'm home
[music]
The house is   very   dark, how can you
restroom
Hey Toilet Look at this  on the   thing
nice view   nice
This is a warehouse   warehouse
Uh It's more than I thought But Here Me I'm living alone Destination Is that right Isn't it With people
write   together
Ah Landlord's  room joint That's  That's more correct than
This is   Now my   I work at home   I can do it
It's different   first   once   should I go?
This is the   kitchen
[Music] Very   old   really
Facility Balcony Door Closed They say
These   moths   what the hell   what the heck
This is   my   room
First, let's put the   luggage  on the   bed
Let's close the door I want to drink a cup of warm tea
This   why  not   open
Because of the bed  Not Is it open
I think it's blocked
Let's go   for a cup of tea  and have a drink
go here
If you wait   it will work
Now   eat   how much   eat  if you want   two   times   talk
[music]
I just heard   something
I heard something
One shot   I did
Let's go to my room You  like this
Uh here originally was it open like this
Now   is open
What is it?
My grandma is  crazy   for a long time and she  hasn't been able to
[music]
What   is this
No It's okay But Just in case It's better  to check the front door
[Music] How to check
[music]
what
I can't stand it
Hey   I really can't   I can't get out   I'm blocked
[Music] How
[Music] Walk it   I locked it
Me here  now  is it like   [Music]
What do we do
It's ruined Wrong Caught
[music]
The  person I just saw [Music]
Shh
Grandmother I  was looking  Originally
[Music] Hey
[music]
At night   recklessly   go out   stop
Hey  I need to find an exit  No What is it Grandma
[Music] How to
[music]
Why   is this   this is everywhere   something   strange   right now
Why   ask yourself   [Music]
Like this  door opened now I can hear   from the comic room for a while
[music]
anybody home
Now I went to take a shower  Grandma [Music]
It's now quickly something you have to find it
I know It's a big problem This is here It's crazy
Hurry up   I have to get out   I can [Music]
How to   [Music]
Heart of  preparation I'm not surprised
[music]
slowly slowly
How to   [Music]
how
not [music]
[Music] How to
can't [music]
wait for a sec
[Music] What can I do?
A big deal   happened
[music]
What is  I caught I can't believe it I'm trapped it's not
Oh my, oh my
it's a big deal
what
Why does the   door  only open   this one?
This   is what you mean by looking
Oh really
how   this
Is there any  like a flashlight  It's too dark
First of all,   the surroundings   a little   research
Heck It's open That Is the key here  Look earlier I got it
Everything   is here
uh here where are you
These days The situation  is strange It's like I'm in danger It's like  Repair works
When it's over  I'm going to move   quickly
who is this
ah  why
what   are you talking about
anybody home
what
What
what the hell
Refrigerator Door Why Keep  open It's closed
It's dark   I can't see it
here   now   go in
can  have key key
Ah   I hate turning around   so much
I just saw
KakaoTalk It wasn't bouncing  Who  made everyone look at it
But   the key  where is the   key
I guess it's here
It's a lock, but it's the same as the password type
this is over
now we
I don't know
In another   place  What  I need to know
[music]
Kakao Talk  Be careful
Ah   surprise
Middle Cmiddle C  Same as City
After this  , if you look back   in the middle,   and the rest of   where
There will be   oxygen
Ah  this too
I came earlier
nothing
Yes Ah Pictures Danseon Gattaengi
Lee
Hit-and-run pictures   I have to find them   I can
ah
Ddaeng CA Ddaeng e c a
Ttaeng   Mr. Lee a yecay  Then   first   second   arrogant
It's okay   remember   please
Okay   the last   one
Would you like to be here   Hana
Garim Hana Where  is it?
sound
Go   no   but   I have to find the last   drawing   to make progress   wouldn't it be
But   here   inside   I draw
This guy   just now   clicked   on the lock  it didn't work
Clues   all   must be gathered
Because progress can be
bathroom on the floor
maybe there is
this is   this
Substitute  ja d
Now   let's solve
Oh
I'm out   I'm leaving now   I can   is there
Or   right away
Separate
Ai corner why  is this   scary
Now   just open it here
I'm here
Finally, finally   came out
Now   can you go out
I have to go   okay
go   yes
Hurry up   run away   okay
hurry
Earlier   that   puppy   where   went   Grace   pay me back   this   it's not
Me Crisis Situation I tried to help Even if the dog was alive I gave it to you Just Feel good
there event
Why Why Why Why Why Why are you running away Suddenly
Suddenly   they say to run away   wait a minute   go over it   uh   I'm embarrassed   now
Where   should I run away  I don't know if it will be   now   well   did you run away?
Well   ran away   Geongaok
There is no   way to escape. Password  5913
run   run   run
Uh   what is this   that came out   no this is   it's outside
weird
It's terrain  Now that   the streets  are out, let's find a way  to get out of town
Let's go to the basement Here It's not like
This place seems like   hell
here it is
Here it is   you are here ok  please
If you go   here,   will you go there   before?
No   but   here   the atmosphere   is weird
Atmosphere   why   like this   here
I  something wrong I think I came in in the first place here wasn't coming
Call Sound What is it?
Over there   inside   phone
Phone Use Rescue You have to request
This is   what is the exit   here
But   I bought   string   I need to find   something   bolt   cutter
There is an enemy something  There is no money Lever There is something  At the vending machine
Flashlight Where  went  it's  that
What was yesterday   situation   suddenly   why
What is it  Flashlight Suddenly It got erased
is this saying   to enter?
scared
Money   I have to find it   I wonder if it is
die
The elevator  does not work  the generator is out of   fuel  and the starter   lever is
It's out of order I have to find fuel .
There was a vending machine
this is it
On the lever gasoline lemon  I saw it earlier
petrol [music]
Just now   in your hand
[music]
Ah   because it comes out
[Music] It's not an enclosed   space
Ah   what   this   is so easy   now
[Music] Nothing special
[music]
I'll show you   I have it   seesaw   next to   rock   check under it   look
[Music] Next to the seesaw
[music]
It's all here
This is  rock [music]
Hahaha now red go to the refrigerator
Are you playing   with me?
[Music] Before That It's a refrigerator
The refrigerator   moves
open [music]
in the yard Pink cloth I saw what  is behind it I wonder I don't know in the yard
there pink cloth [music]
My gosh   so   a lot   god   so   a lot   god
was also
No now isn’t it the grandmother
Residents Crazy Look [Music]
Hurry up something pink cloth in the yard
Which side  is it on? Wait a minute  here
Only   once   just   look through   more than   don't come
No way   this [music]
uh   what
here is
What   hideout  is like
My  hideout isn't it beautiful isn't it my family and  town whole wake up
I started  all the   cruel   things  I was hiding   in this place   but now
I think it's a relief that   there are no   people   living in Kowloon.
I'm gonna [music]
coin
thank you
thank you [music]
Vending machine   go now
If you write a coin  , it's okay
Is this a   place that connects to   if I do  ?
[MUSIC] Uh phone
not   now
Here oil there is no  thing gasoline
[music]
people  just passed by
vending machine
Go   to the vending machine [music]
Go   to the vending machine
take out the lever
That   then now
[MUSIC] Finding Gas
That   there is a   person in front of you   close to you   and you go   out of nowhere   will come out   just like before
While screaming  may come running I don't know absolutely not go up
Now   heart   preparation
ah
[Music] Seriously just
are you okay
First of all  Lever Me Looking back Really I hate it Please
[music]
Why  why is this   the sound   coming out   the background sound
Here
The situation is  not good not  my my daughter ran away from home what  is the problem I don't know
My wife   for three days    did not come out of the bathtub  and   the people around her   everyone   went crazy
What should I do   I didn't notice  before, but  Gas comes out of  .
It's all   that   person   I think it's   please help
Now From 100 won Gas comes out That's right  A sudden burst  It can come out
gas   sound
It's okay They're trying to kick us  out of the neighborhood
The government   is hiding  the fact that we are   here   dying .
It's here  at the gas tank
[music]
[music] Now
Suddenly   be careful
[music]
An  that's scary
Not at all  I'm scared
lever
Oil   put lever
on
Elevator  works  is possible
[music]
ah  what
Once   came out   for the time being   again   won't come out
Elevator  looks like a dog  scary
From the elevator far away  you know
[music]
Am I   dreaming   or am I
What  is the   place [Music]
bolt   cutter
Finally the World Cup
Like this   calm   Lee   what is this   atmosphere
[music] I'm going
When the door   is closed  what  will   do   by cutting to come out
[music]
Now now bolt cutter Just write  and you can do it   everything  is here
It's okay, just get out  and it's okay It's difficult There's no   what
Even with me   It's okay   over there   it's a game anyway   it's a game
[music]
You   No way [Music]
Eunhye I'm envious Gunnie You should look after me  well
I I live for you Jun Geo I remember
uh [music]
Don't look at me  because I'm scared
Is it finally   out
joking   no
Honey What The village Residents What What are you doing?
It's weird here
I   so   not too long ago
[Music] Gotta go   Yes
[Music] Was it   affected by the gas ?
residents
where
Ah   finally   I came out   I can go   home   I can
Come on   long time no see   really   uh
Quality Crazy Atmosphere
Incredible cost performance   best   7,800 won   about
quality is
[music]
What is it yet   not over   not   is it   recently   in Kowloon
There are a lot of   police   reports from   people who have been there  , but they are   real.
claims to have seen a  city that does not exist that was demolished 5 years  ago
China was one of the worst cities demolition just before  in this place crime and
Unsavory  murder  incidents  also increased  people  government Kowloon demolished
I believe that   cruel   means   were mobilized for
But   until the end   why   do you do that
Oops Press it  Again What comes out That's not
Well done
Really   the quality   was good and the atmosphere was also   good
Welcome to Coul
I'll finish here   I like it
[music]
Yes   ah   it's so   easy